[
  {
    "question": "de accijns",
    "options": [
      "excise duty",
      "army",
      "forest",
      "benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "excise duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "de belasting",
    "options": [
      "tax",
      "engine",
      "levee",
      "cigarette"
    ],
    "answer": "tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "de benzine",
    "options": [
      "gasoline",
      "sewer",
      "van",
      "government"
    ],
    "answer": "gasoline"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bestelauto",
    "options": [
      "delivery van",
      "truck",
      "tax money",
      "child benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "delivery van"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dijk",
    "options": [
      "levee",
      "wage tax",
      "army",
      "motor vehicle tax"
    ],
    "answer": "levee"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huurtoeslag",
    "options": [
      "rent benefit",
      "motor vehicle",
      "forest",
      "passenger car"
    ],
    "answer": "rent benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kinderbijslag",
    "options": [
      "child benefit",
      "cigarette",
      "council",
      "tax money"
    ],
    "answer": "child benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de loonbelasting",
    "options": [
      "wage tax",
      "excise duty",
      "army",
      "motor"
    ],
    "answer": "wage tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "de motor",
    "options": [
      "engine",
      "gasoline",
      "sewer",
      "government"
    ],
    "answer": "engine"
  },
  {
    "question": "de motorrijtuigenbelasting",
    "options": [
      "motor vehicle tax",
      "benefit",
      "delivery van",
      "tax"
    ],
    "answer": "motor vehicle tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "de overheid",
    "options": [
      "government",
      "tax money",
      "child benefit",
      "army"
    ],
    "answer": "government"
  },
  {
    "question": "de personenauto",
    "options": [
      "passenger car",
      "healthcare benefit",
      "levee",
      "truck"
    ],
    "answer": "passenger car"
  },
  {
    "question": "de regering",
    "options": [
      "government",
      "forest",
      "motor",
      "tax money"
    ],
    "answer": "government"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sigaret",
    "options": [
      "cigarette",
      "wage tax",
      "delivery van",
      "healthcare benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "cigarette"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toeslag",
    "options": [
      "benefit",
      "engine",
      "army",
      "sewer"
    ],
    "answer": "benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vrachtauto",
    "options": [
      "truck",
      "excise duty",
      "council",
      "passenger car"
    ],
    "answer": "truck"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgtoeslag",
    "options": [
      "healthcare benefit",
      "motor vehicle",
      "van",
      "forest"
    ],
    "answer": "healthcare benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "het belastinggeld",
    "options": [
      "tax money",
      "benefit",
      "motor vehicle tax",
      "engine"
    ],
    "answer": "tax money"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bestuur",
    "options": [
      "council",
      "gasoline",
      "sewer",
      "rent benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "council"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bos",
    "options": [
      "forest",
      "motor vehicle",
      "army",
      "tax"
    ],
    "answer": "forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "het busje",
    "options": [
      "van",
      "tax money",
      "child benefit",
      "delivery van"
    ],
    "answer": "van"
  },
  {
    "question": "het leger",
    "options": [
      "army",
      "motor",
      "wage tax",
      "council"
    ],
    "answer": "army"
  },
  {
    "question": "het motorrijtuig",
    "options": [
      "motor vehicle",
      "levee",
      "engine",
      "truck"
    ],
    "answer": "motor vehicle"
  },
  {
    "question": "het riool",
    "options": [
      "sewer",
      "rent benefit",
      "gasoline",
      "benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "sewer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de afvoer",
    "options": [
      "drain",
      "object",
      "support",
      "pen"
    ],
    "answer": "drain"
  },
  {
    "question": "de balie",
    "options": [
      "reception desk",
      "building",
      "exception",
      "authority"
    ],
    "answer": "reception desk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de factuur",
    "options": [
      "invoice",
      "finances",
      "to tell",
      "pen"
    ],
    "answer": "invoice"
  },
  {
    "question": "de factuurdatum",
    "options": [
      "invoice date",
      "support",
      "very crowded",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "invoice date"
  },
  {
    "question": "de financiën",
    "options": [
      "finances",
      "authority",
      "diverse",
      "to postpone"
    ],
    "answer": "finances"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inhoud",
    "options": [
      "content",
      "building",
      "invoice",
      "pen"
    ],
    "answer": "content"
  },
  {
    "question": "de instantie",
    "options": [
      "authority",
      "object",
      "to tell",
      "support"
    ],
    "answer": "authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pen",
    "options": [
      "pen",
      "drain",
      "invoice number",
      "postponement"
    ],
    "answer": "pen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pomp",
    "options": [
      "pump",
      "support",
      "serious",
      "to increase"
    ],
    "answer": "pump"
  },
  {
    "question": "de steun",
    "options": [
      "support",
      "financial",
      "invoice",
      "reception desk"
    ],
    "answer": "support"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitzondering",
    "options": [
      "exception",
      "customer number",
      "building",
      "to vary"
    ],
    "answer": "exception"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voorrijkosten",
    "options": [
      "call-out charge",
      "finances",
      "object",
      "pen"
    ],
    "answer": "call-out charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "divers",
    "options": [
      "diverse",
      "serious",
      "to increase",
      "authority"
    ],
    "answer": "diverse"
  },
  {
    "question": "financieel",
    "options": [
      "financial",
      "invoice",
      "support",
      "postponement of payment"
    ],
    "answer": "financial"
  },
  {
    "question": "groeien",
    "options": [
      "to increase",
      "to be located",
      "to postpone",
      "diverse"
    ],
    "answer": "to increase"
  },
  {
    "question": "het factuurnummer",
    "options": [
      "invoice number",
      "drain",
      "to tell",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "invoice number"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gebouw",
    "options": [
      "building",
      "serious",
      "reception desk",
      "invoice"
    ],
    "answer": "building"
  },
  {
    "question": "het klantnummer",
    "options": [
      "customer number",
      "to vary",
      "content",
      "very crowded"
    ],
    "answer": "customer number"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uitstel",
    "options": [
      "postponement",
      "to postpone",
      "invoice number",
      "authority"
    ],
    "answer": "postponement"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uitstel van betaling",
    "options": [
      "postponement of payment",
      "finances",
      "pen",
      "support"
    ],
    "answer": "postponement of payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "het voorwerp",
    "options": [
      "object",
      "call-out charge",
      "invoice date",
      "to tell"
    ],
    "answer": "object"
  },
  {
    "question": "serieus",
    "options": [
      "serious",
      "financial",
      "building",
      "to be located"
    ],
    "answer": "serious"
  },
  {
    "question": "stampvol",
    "options": [
      "very crowded",
      "drain",
      "to vary",
      "invoice"
    ],
    "answer": "very crowded"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitstellen",
    "options": [
      "to postpone",
      "diverse",
      "to tell",
      "exception"
    ],
    "answer": "to postpone"
  },
  {
    "question": "variëren",
    "options": [
      "to vary",
      "object",
      "customer number",
      "support"
    ],
    "answer": "to vary"
  },
  {
    "question": "vertellen",
    "options": [
      "to tell",
      "building",
      "to increase",
      "drain"
    ],
    "answer": "to tell"
  },
  {
    "question": "zitten",
    "options": [
      "to be located",
      "invoice date",
      "reception desk",
      "to postpone"
    ],
    "answer": "to be located"
  },
  {
    "question": "afbetalen",
    "options": [
      "pay off",
      "to end",
      "installment",
      "rule"
    ],
    "answer": "pay off"
  },
  {
    "question": "beëindigen",
    "options": [
      "to end",
      "installment",
      "arrangement",
      "interest"
    ],
    "answer": "to end"
  },
  {
    "question": "de afbetaling",
    "options": [
      "installment",
      "rule",
      "interest",
      "contract"
    ],
    "answer": "installment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de regel",
    "options": [
      "rule",
      "arrangement",
      "part",
      "leather"
    ],
    "answer": "rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "de regeling",
    "options": [
      "arrangement",
      "interest",
      "to sign",
      "couch"
    ],
    "answer": "arrangement"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rente",
    "options": [
      "interest",
      "purchase amount",
      "contract",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "gespreid",
    "options": [
      "in installments",
      "part",
      "term",
      "to be left with"
    ],
    "answer": "in installments"
  },
  {
    "question": "het aankoopbedrag",
    "options": [
      "purchase amount",
      "leather",
      "rule",
      "to end"
    ],
    "answer": "purchase amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bankstel",
    "options": [
      "couch",
      "to sign",
      "installment",
      "more comfortable"
    ],
    "answer": "couch"
  },
  {
    "question": "het contract",
    "options": [
      "contract",
      "something like that",
      "rule",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "contract"
  },
  {
    "question": "het deel",
    "options": [
      "part",
      "arrangement",
      "to save",
      "contract"
    ],
    "answer": "part"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gedeelte",
    "options": [
      "part",
      "rule",
      "interest",
      "to learn"
    ],
    "answer": "part"
  },
  {
    "question": "het leer",
    "options": [
      "leather",
      "to end",
      "to sign",
      "rule"
    ],
    "answer": "leather"
  },
  {
    "question": "lekkerder",
    "options": [
      "more comfortable",
      "leather",
      "term",
      "contract"
    ],
    "answer": "more comfortable"
  },
  {
    "question": "leren",
    "options": [
      "to learn",
      "pay off",
      "contract",
      "couch"
    ],
    "answer": "to learn"
  },
  {
    "question": "overhouden",
    "options": [
      "to be left with",
      "interest",
      "just",
      "something like that"
    ],
    "answer": "to be left with"
  },
  {
    "question": "pas",
    "options": [
      "just",
      "rule",
      "arrangement",
      "to save"
    ],
    "answer": "just"
  },
  {
    "question": "sparen",
    "options": [
      "to save",
      "leather",
      "more comfortable",
      "purchase amount"
    ],
    "answer": "to save"
  },
  {
    "question": "tegelijkertijd",
    "options": [
      "at the same time",
      "to sign",
      "contract",
      "installment"
    ],
    "answer": "at the same time"
  },
  {
    "question": "tekenen",
    "options": [
      "to sign",
      "interest",
      "term",
      "couch"
    ],
    "answer": "to sign"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoiets",
    "options": [
      "something like that",
      "purchase amount",
      "to end",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "something like that"
  },
  {
    "question": "de termijn",
    "options": [
      "term",
      "to learn",
      "to save",
      "in installments"
    ],
    "answer": "term"
  },
  {
    "question": "even",
    "options": [
      "for a while",
      "interest",
      "arrangement",
      "couch"
    ],
    "answer": "for a while"
  },
  {
    "question": "absoluut",
    "options": [
      "absolutely",
      "detergent",
      "overview",
      "stupid"
    ],
    "answer": "absolutely"
  },
  {
    "question": "bezuinigen op",
    "options": [
      "to cut down on",
      "luxury",
      "dentist",
      "overview"
    ],
    "answer": "to cut down on"
  },
  {
    "question": "dagelijks",
    "options": [
      "daily",
      "to cancel",
      "poor",
      "income"
    ],
    "answer": "daily"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bezuiniging",
    "options": [
      "cutback",
      "rich",
      "absolutely",
      "social security benefits"
    ],
    "answer": "cutback"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bijstand",
    "options": [
      "social security benefits",
      "debt",
      "cable television",
      "luxury"
    ],
    "answer": "social security benefits"
  },
  {
    "question": "de caissière",
    "options": [
      "cashier",
      "expenses",
      "health insurance",
      "full-time"
    ],
    "answer": "cashier"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geldzaken",
    "options": [
      "financial matters",
      "recurring expenses",
      "to cancel",
      "absolutely"
    ],
    "answer": "financial matters"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inkomsten",
    "options": [
      "income",
      "stupid",
      "to get by",
      "cashier"
    ],
    "answer": "income"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kabel-tv",
    "options": [
      "cable television",
      "part-time",
      "detergent",
      "poor"
    ],
    "answer": "cable television"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schuld",
    "options": [
      "debt",
      "daily",
      "to get by",
      "rich"
    ],
    "answer": "debt"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tandarts",
    "options": [
      "dentist",
      "overview",
      "to cut down on",
      "stupid"
    ],
    "answer": "dentist"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitgaven",
    "options": [
      "expenses",
      "full-time",
      "cable television",
      "luxury"
    ],
    "answer": "expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vaste lasten",
    "options": [
      "recurring expenses",
      "absolutely",
      "social security benefits",
      "detergent"
    ],
    "answer": "recurring expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgverzekering",
    "options": [
      "health insurance",
      "thrifty",
      "income",
      "daily"
    ],
    "answer": "health insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gevolg",
    "options": [
      "consequence",
      "rich",
      "to cancel",
      "debt"
    ],
    "answer": "consequence"
  },
  {
    "question": "het overzicht",
    "options": [
      "overview",
      "cashier",
      "luxury",
      "to get by"
    ],
    "answer": "overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "het wasmiddel",
    "options": [
      "detergent",
      "poor",
      "cable television",
      "dentist"
    ],
    "answer": "detergent"
  },
  {
    "question": "luxe",
    "options": [
      "luxury",
      "expenses",
      "to cancel",
      "part-time"
    ],
    "answer": "luxury"
  },
  {
    "question": "opzeggen",
    "options": [
      "to cancel",
      "overview",
      "income",
      "to get by"
    ],
    "answer": "to cancel"
  },
  {
    "question": "parttime",
    "options": [
      "part-time",
      "recurring expenses",
      "absolutely",
      "debt"
    ],
    "answer": "part-time"
  },
  {
    "question": "rijk",
    "options": [
      "rich",
      "detergent",
      "luxury",
      "to get by"
    ],
    "answer": "rich"
  },
  {
    "question": "rondkomen",
    "options": [
      "to get by",
      "cable television",
      "cashier",
      "consequence"
    ],
    "answer": "to get by"
  },
  {
    "question": "stom",
    "options": [
      "stupid",
      "to cancel",
      "part-time",
      "daily"
    ],
    "answer": "stupid"
  },
  {
    "question": "zuinig",
    "options": [
      "thrifty",
      "detergent",
      "expenses",
      "debt"
    ],
    "answer": "thrifty"
  },
  {
    "question": "arm",
    "options": [
      "poor",
      "income",
      "dentist",
      "cable television"
    ],
    "answer": "poor"
  },
  {
    "question": "fulltime",
    "options": [
      "full-time",
      "rich",
      "luxury",
      "to get by"
    ],
    "answer": "full-time"
  },
  {
    "question": "afwassen",
    "options": [
      "to do the dishes",
      "to deliver",
      "to bend down",
      "to reserve"
    ],
    "answer": "to do the dishes"
  },
  {
    "question": "bezorgen",
    "options": [
      "to deliver",
      "to carry",
      "to sleep in",
      "to reserve"
    ],
    "answer": "to deliver"
  },
  {
    "question": "bukken",
    "options": [
      "to bend down",
      "to break down",
      "to lift",
      "to call in sick"
    ],
    "answer": "to bend down"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bediening",
    "options": [
      "waiting staff",
      "restaurant",
      "plate",
      "profession"
    ],
    "answer": "waiting staff"
  },
  {
    "question": "de knie",
    "options": [
      "knee",
      "stiff",
      "gardener",
      "butcher"
    ],
    "answer": "knee"
  },
  {
    "question": "de metselaar",
    "options": [
      "mason",
      "carpenter",
      "housemate",
      "butcher"
    ],
    "answer": "mason"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schilder",
    "options": [
      "(house)painter",
      "gardener",
      "knee",
      "restaurant"
    ],
    "answer": "(house)painter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de slager",
    "options": [
      "butcher",
      "mason",
      "to carry",
      "waiting staff"
    ],
    "answer": "butcher"
  },
  {
    "question": "de timmerman",
    "options": [
      "carpenter",
      "painter",
      "gardener",
      "resident"
    ],
    "answer": "carpenter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tuinman",
    "options": [
      "gardener",
      "butcher",
      "restaurant",
      "to sleep in"
    ],
    "answer": "gardener"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verhuizing",
    "options": [
      "move",
      "profession",
      "to bend down",
      "constantly"
    ],
    "answer": "move"
  },
  {
    "question": "het beroep",
    "options": [
      "profession",
      "move",
      "both",
      "until"
    ],
    "answer": "profession"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bord",
    "options": [
      "plate",
      "to deliver",
      "to carry",
      "knee"
    ],
    "answer": "plate"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bovenhuis",
    "options": [
      "upstairs apartment",
      "restaurant",
      "housemate",
      "profession"
    ],
    "answer": "upstairs apartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "het restaurant",
    "options": [
      "restaurant",
      "plate",
      "move",
      "butcher"
    ],
    "answer": "restaurant"
  },
  {
    "question": "reserveren",
    "options": [
      "to reserve",
      "to deliver",
      "to sleep in",
      "to bend down"
    ],
    "answer": "to reserve"
  },
  {
    "question": "sjouwen",
    "options": [
      "to carry",
      "to lift",
      "to call in sick",
      "to break down"
    ],
    "answer": "to carry"
  },
  {
    "question": "stijf",
    "options": [
      "stiff",
      "knee",
      "plate",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "stiff"
  },
  {
    "question": "stukgaan",
    "options": [
      "to break down",
      "to bend down",
      "to reserve",
      "to carry"
    ],
    "answer": "to break down"
  },
  {
    "question": "tillen",
    "options": [
      "to lift",
      "to sleep in",
      "to do the dishes",
      "to call in sick"
    ],
    "answer": "to lift"
  },
  {
    "question": "totdat",
    "options": [
      "until",
      "both",
      "important",
      "resident"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitslapen",
    "options": [
      "to sleep in",
      "to carry",
      "to lift",
      "to deliver"
    ],
    "answer": "to sleep in"
  },
  {
    "question": "voortdurend",
    "options": [
      "constantly",
      "until",
      "to do the dishes",
      "to reserve"
    ],
    "answer": "constantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich ziek melden",
    "options": [
      "to call in sick",
      "to break down",
      "to carry",
      "to lift"
    ],
    "answer": "to call in sick"
  },
  {
    "question": "serveren",
    "options": [
      "to serve",
      "to deliver",
      "to bend down",
      "to call in sick"
    ],
    "answer": "to serve"
  },
  {
    "question": "basketball",
    "options": [
      "basketball",
      "surfing",
      "rafting",
      "image"
    ],
    "answer": "basketball"
  },
  {
    "question": "dansen",
    "options": [
      "to dance",
      "extreme",
      "rowing",
      "challenge"
    ],
    "answer": "to dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de afbeelding",
    "options": [
      "image",
      "to sweat",
      "person",
      "ball sport"
    ],
    "answer": "image"
  },
  {
    "question": "de balsport",
    "options": [
      "ball sport",
      "rafting",
      "to fight",
      "strength training"
    ],
    "answer": "ball sport"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inspanning",
    "options": [
      "exertion",
      "surfing",
      "basketball",
      "to win"
    ],
    "answer": "exertion"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kracht",
    "options": [
      "strength",
      "image",
      "to work together",
      "rowing"
    ],
    "answer": "strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "de krachttraining",
    "options": [
      "strength training",
      "team sport",
      "horseback riding",
      "to google"
    ],
    "answer": "strength training"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mens",
    "options": [
      "person",
      "to fight",
      "rafting",
      "image"
    ],
    "answer": "person"
  },
  {
    "question": "de teamsport",
    "options": [
      "team sport",
      "strength",
      "challenge",
      "mountain biking"
    ],
    "answer": "team sport"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tegenstander",
    "options": [
      "opponent",
      "to win",
      "wild",
      "to sweat"
    ],
    "answer": "opponent"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitdaging",
    "options": [
      "challenge",
      "person",
      "ball sport",
      "to google"
    ],
    "answer": "challenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voorkeur",
    "options": [
      "preference",
      "rafting",
      "to dance",
      "image"
    ],
    "answer": "preference"
  },
  {
    "question": "extreem",
    "options": [
      "extreme",
      "strength",
      "surfing",
      "basketball"
    ],
    "answer": "extreme"
  },
  {
    "question": "googelen",
    "options": [
      "to google",
      "challenge",
      "team sport",
      "to fight"
    ],
    "answer": "to google"
  },
  {
    "question": "het rondje",
    "options": [
      "lap",
      "to sweat",
      "rowing",
      "opponent"
    ],
    "answer": "lap"
  },
  {
    "question": "individueel",
    "options": [
      "individually",
      "mountain biking",
      "to win",
      "image"
    ],
    "answer": "individually"
  },
  {
    "question": "mountainbiken",
    "options": [
      "mountain biking",
      "to google",
      "wild",
      "exertion"
    ],
    "answer": "mountain biking"
  },
  {
    "question": "paardrijden",
    "options": [
      "horseback riding",
      "to dance",
      "challenge",
      "rafting"
    ],
    "answer": "horseback riding"
  },
  {
    "question": "roeien",
    "options": [
      "rowing",
      "surfing",
      "to win",
      "strength"
    ],
    "answer": "rowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "samenwerken",
    "options": [
      "to work together",
      "image",
      "team sport",
      "horseback riding"
    ],
    "answer": "to work together"
  },
  {
    "question": "surfen",
    "options": [
      "surfing",
      "exertion",
      "to sweat",
      "person"
    ],
    "answer": "surfing"
  },
  {
    "question": "varen",
    "options": [
      "rafting",
      "strength training",
      "to google",
      "ball sport"
    ],
    "answer": "rafting"
  },
  {
    "question": "vechten",
    "options": [
      "to fight",
      "wild",
      "rowing",
      "to work together"
    ],
    "answer": "to fight"
  },
  {
    "question": "waterpolo",
    "options": [
      "water polo",
      "preference",
      "to dance",
      "strength"
    ],
    "answer": "water polo"
  },
  {
    "question": "wild",
    "options": [
      "wild",
      "to win",
      "to sweat",
      "image"
    ],
    "answer": "wild"
  },
  {
    "question": "winnen",
    "options": [
      "to win",
      "challenge",
      "basketball",
      "to google"
    ],
    "answer": "to win"
  },
  {
    "question": "zweten",
    "options": [
      "to sweat",
      "rowing",
      "horseback riding",
      "lap"
    ],
    "answer": "to sweat"
  },
  {
    "question": "afstappen",
    "options": [
      "get off",
      "interest",
      "email",
      "instruction"
    ],
    "answer": "get off"
  },
  {
    "question": "anderhalf",
    "options": [
      "one and a half",
      "slow",
      "to take place",
      "to get on"
    ],
    "answer": "one and a half"
  },
  {
    "question": "de begeleiding",
    "options": [
      "supervision",
      "community centre",
      "professional",
      "moment"
    ],
    "answer": "supervision"
  },
  {
    "question": "de belangstelling",
    "options": [
      "interest",
      "size",
      "to get on",
      "to send to your home"
    ],
    "answer": "interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "de deelname",
    "options": [
      "participation",
      "to participate",
      "public transport",
      "instruction"
    ],
    "answer": "participation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inschrijving",
    "options": [
      "registration",
      "moment",
      "email",
      "formal"
    ],
    "answer": "registration"
  },
  {
    "question": "de instructie",
    "options": [
      "instruction",
      "public transport",
      "to participate",
      "slow"
    ],
    "answer": "instruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "de maat",
    "options": [
      "size",
      "supervision",
      "moment",
      "registration"
    ],
    "answer": "size"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verkeersregel",
    "options": [
      "traffic rule",
      "email",
      "interest",
      "community centre"
    ],
    "answer": "traffic rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "formeel",
    "options": [
      "formal",
      "slow",
      "to get on",
      "to participate"
    ],
    "answer": "formal"
  },
  {
    "question": "het buurthuis",
    "options": [
      "community centre",
      "traffic rule",
      "moment",
      "supervision"
    ],
    "answer": "community centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "het mailtje",
    "options": [
      "email",
      "instruction",
      "participation",
      "professional"
    ],
    "answer": "email"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ogenblik",
    "options": [
      "moment",
      "formal",
      "public transport",
      "slow"
    ],
    "answer": "moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "het openbaar vervoer",
    "options": [
      "public transport",
      "registration",
      "size",
      "instruction"
    ],
    "answer": "public transport"
  },
  {
    "question": "hopelijk",
    "options": [
      "hopefully",
      "get off",
      "to take place",
      "interest"
    ],
    "answer": "hopefully"
  },
  {
    "question": "meedoen",
    "options": [
      "to participate",
      "registration",
      "formal",
      "slow"
    ],
    "answer": "to participate"
  },
  {
    "question": "opstappen",
    "options": [
      "to get on",
      "to send to your home",
      "moment",
      "hopefully"
    ],
    "answer": "to get on"
  },
  {
    "question": "professioneel",
    "options": [
      "professional",
      "email",
      "to get off",
      "traffic rule"
    ],
    "answer": "professional"
  },
  {
    "question": "thuissturen",
    "options": [
      "to send to your home",
      "get off",
      "formal",
      "size"
    ],
    "answer": "to send to your home"
  },
  {
    "question": "traag",
    "options": [
      "slow",
      "supervision",
      "moment",
      "hopefully"
    ],
    "answer": "slow"
  },
  {
    "question": "vooraf",
    "options": [
      "in advance",
      "traffic rule",
      "community centre",
      "email"
    ],
    "answer": "in advance"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorgaan",
    "options": [
      "to take place",
      "interest",
      "formal",
      "to send to your home"
    ],
    "answer": "to take place"
  },
  {
    "question": "staan",
    "options": [
      "to mention",
      "public transport",
      "hopefully",
      "supervision"
    ],
    "answer": "to mention"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ademhaling",
    "options": [
      "breathing",
      "movement",
      "condition",
      "chance"
    ],
    "answer": "breathing"
  },
  {
    "question": "de beweging",
    "options": [
      "chance",
      "movement",
      "chore",
      "muscle"
    ],
    "answer": "movement"
  },
  {
    "question": "de conditie",
    "options": [
      "(physical) condition",
      "toilet",
      "fit",
      "guilty"
    ],
    "answer": "(physical) condition"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kans",
    "options": [
      "chance",
      "running",
      "intensive",
      "used"
    ],
    "answer": "chance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klus",
    "options": [
      "chore",
      "kickboxing",
      "guilty",
      "to reduce"
    ],
    "answer": "chore"
  },
  {
    "question": "de spier",
    "options": [
      "muscle",
      "kickboxing",
      "guilty",
      "to reduce"
    ],
    "answer": "muscle"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wc",
    "options": [
      "toilet",
      "movement",
      "condition",
      "chance"
    ],
    "answer": "toilet"
  },
  {
    "question": "fit",
    "options": [
      "fit",
      "used",
      "guilty",
      "moderately"
    ],
    "answer": "fit"
  },
  {
    "question": "fitness",
    "options": [
      "fitness",
      "to vacuum",
      "to climb the stairs",
      "kickboxing"
    ],
    "answer": "fitness"
  },
  {
    "question": "gewend",
    "options": [
      "used",
      "running",
      "physical",
      "domestic"
    ],
    "answer": "used"
  },
  {
    "question": "hardlopen",
    "options": [
      "running",
      "toilet",
      "to reduce",
      "to continue doing something"
    ],
    "answer": "running"
  },
  {
    "question": "het hart",
    "options": [
      "heart",
      "kickboxing",
      "to climb the stairs",
      "moderately"
    ],
    "answer": "heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "het overgewicht",
    "options": [
      "overweight",
      "guilty",
      "to vacuum",
      "chore"
    ],
    "answer": "overweight"
  },
  {
    "question": "huishoudelijk",
    "options": [
      "domestic",
      "intensive",
      "guilty",
      "used"
    ],
    "answer": "domestic"
  },
  {
    "question": "intensief",
    "options": [
      "intensive",
      "chore",
      "kickboxing",
      "to reduce"
    ],
    "answer": "intensive"
  },
  {
    "question": "kickboksen",
    "options": [
      "kickboxing",
      "running",
      "guilty",
      "chance"
    ],
    "answer": "kickboxing"
  },
  {
    "question": "lichamelijk",
    "options": [
      "physical",
      "used",
      "to vacuum",
      "to continue doing something"
    ],
    "answer": "physical"
  },
  {
    "question": "matig",
    "options": [
      "moderately",
      "running",
      "chore",
      "muscle"
    ],
    "answer": "moderately"
  },
  {
    "question": "minstens",
    "options": [
      "at least",
      "to reduce",
      "used",
      "toilet"
    ],
    "answer": "at least"
  },
  {
    "question": "schuldig",
    "options": [
      "guilty",
      "fitness",
      "kickboxing",
      "chore"
    ],
    "answer": "guilty"
  },
  {
    "question": "stofzuigen",
    "options": [
      "to vacuum",
      "running",
      "movement",
      "condition"
    ],
    "answer": "to vacuum"
  },
  {
    "question": "traplopen",
    "options": [
      "to climb the stairs",
      "to continue doing something",
      "to reduce",
      "guilty"
    ],
    "answer": "to climb the stairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "verminderen",
    "options": [
      "to reduce",
      "kickboxing",
      "used",
      "running"
    ],
    "answer": "to reduce"
  },
  {
    "question": "volhouden",
    "options": [
      "to continue doing something",
      "chore",
      "movement",
      "to vacuum"
    ],
    "answer": "to continue doing something"
  },
  {
    "question": "kloppen",
    "options": [
      "to beat",
      "used",
      "moderately",
      "chore"
    ],
    "answer": "to beat"
  },
  {
    "question": "alledaags",
    "options": [
      "everyday",
      "skill",
      "to click",
      "foreign"
    ],
    "answer": "everyday"
  },
  {
    "question": "bestaan uit",
    "options": [
      "to consist of",
      "interest",
      "to practice",
      "use"
    ],
    "answer": "to consist of"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bankzaken",
    "options": [
      "banking",
      "walk-in consulting hours",
      "to have",
      "to go on"
    ],
    "answer": "banking"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buitenlander",
    "options": [
      "foreigner",
      "learning material",
      "customer service",
      "pace"
    ],
    "answer": "foreigner"
  },
  {
    "question": "de interesse",
    "options": [
      "interest",
      "to improve",
      "subject",
      "digital signature"
    ],
    "answer": "interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klantenservice",
    "options": [
      "customer service",
      "to click",
      "foreign",
      "to practice"
    ],
    "answer": "customer service"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lesstof",
    "options": [
      "learning material",
      "to have",
      "to improve",
      "pace"
    ],
    "answer": "learning material"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vaardigheid",
    "options": [
      "skill",
      "banking",
      "to consist of",
      "to go on"
    ],
    "answer": "skill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zoekmachine",
    "options": [
      "search engine",
      "interest",
      "to have",
      "walk-in consulting hours"
    ],
    "answer": "search engine"
  },
  {
    "question": "DigiD",
    "options": [
      "DigiD (digital signature)",
      "to go on",
      "to click",
      "customer service"
    ],
    "answer": "DigiD (digital signature)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gebruik",
    "options": [
      "use",
      "foreign",
      "to practice",
      "to consist of"
    ],
    "answer": "use"
  },
  {
    "question": "het inloopspreekuur",
    "options": [
      "walk-in consulting hours",
      "skill",
      "banking",
      "interest"
    ],
    "answer": "walk-in consulting hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "het onderwerp",
    "options": [
      "subject",
      "to click",
      "digital signature",
      "to go on"
    ],
    "answer": "subject"
  },
  {
    "question": "het tempo",
    "options": [
      "pace",
      "to have",
      "to improve",
      "learning material"
    ],
    "answer": "pace"
  },
  {
    "question": "klikken",
    "options": [
      "to click",
      "customer service",
      "interest",
      "skill"
    ],
    "answer": "to click"
  },
  {
    "question": "oefenen",
    "options": [
      "to practice",
      "to consist of",
      "foreign",
      "banking"
    ],
    "answer": "to practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "opgaan",
    "options": [
      "to go on",
      "to have",
      "digital signature",
      "walk-in consulting hours"
    ],
    "answer": "to go on"
  },
  {
    "question": "tijdens",
    "options": [
      "during",
      "to practice",
      "to improve",
      "to click"
    ],
    "answer": "during"
  },
  {
    "question": "verbeteren",
    "options": [
      "to improve",
      "to go on",
      "customer service",
      "pace"
    ],
    "answer": "to improve"
  },
  {
    "question": "voeren",
    "options": [
      "to have",
      "interest",
      "skill",
      "use"
    ],
    "answer": "to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanmelden",
    "options": [
      "to sign up",
      "upcoming",
      "to activate",
      "registration"
    ],
    "answer": "to sign up"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanstaande",
    "options": [
      "upcoming",
      "to sign up",
      "to activate",
      "registration"
    ],
    "answer": "upcoming"
  },
  {
    "question": "activeren",
    "options": [
      "to activate",
      "to sign up",
      "to delete",
      "to steal"
    ],
    "answer": "to activate"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aanmelding",
    "options": [
      "registration",
      "insurance",
      "subscription",
      "airline ticket"
    ],
    "answer": "registration"
  },
  {
    "question": "de basis",
    "options": [
      "base",
      "to download",
      "to copy",
      "to drink coffee"
    ],
    "answer": "base"
  },
  {
    "question": "de betaling",
    "options": [
      "payment",
      "criminal",
      "to activate",
      "to warn"
    ],
    "answer": "payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gebruikersnaam",
    "options": [
      "username",
      "insurance",
      "to steal",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "username"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kleindochter",
    "options": [
      "granddaughter",
      "to download",
      "to be bored",
      "to sign up"
    ],
    "answer": "granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de misdadiger",
    "options": [
      "criminal",
      "to warn",
      "to pick out",
      "to activate"
    ],
    "answer": "criminal"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verzekering",
    "options": [
      "insurance",
      "to steal",
      "upcoming",
      "to activate"
    ],
    "answer": "insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "downloaden",
    "options": [
      "to download",
      "to activate",
      "to be bored",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "to download"
  },
  {
    "question": "het abonnement",
    "options": [
      "subscription",
      "to delete",
      "base",
      "to warn"
    ],
    "answer": "subscription"
  },
  {
    "question": "het programma",
    "options": [
      "programme",
      "to pick out",
      "to copy",
      "to activate"
    ],
    "answer": "programme"
  },
  {
    "question": "het risico",
    "options": [
      "risk",
      "to be bored",
      "to steal",
      "to activate"
    ],
    "answer": "risk"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vliegticket",
    "options": [
      "airline ticket",
      "registration",
      "to copy",
      "to warn"
    ],
    "answer": "airline ticket"
  },
  {
    "question": "het wachtwoord",
    "options": [
      "password",
      "to warn",
      "to pick out",
      "to be bored"
    ],
    "answer": "password"
  },
  {
    "question": "ingewikkeld",
    "options": [
      "complicated",
      "to steal",
      "to activate",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "complicated"
  },
  {
    "question": "koffiedrinken",
    "options": [
      "to drink coffee",
      "to warn",
      "to sign up",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "to drink coffee"
  },
  {
    "question": "kopiëren",
    "options": [
      "to copy",
      "to be bored",
      "registration",
      "to warn"
    ],
    "answer": "to copy"
  },
  {
    "question": "onzeker",
    "options": [
      "insecure",
      "to steal",
      "to pick out",
      "to activate"
    ],
    "answer": "insecure"
  },
  {
    "question": "stelen",
    "options": [
      "to steal",
      "to warn",
      "to sign up",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "to steal"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitkiezen",
    "options": [
      "to pick out",
      "to activate",
      "to be bored",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "to pick out"
  },
  {
    "question": "verwijderen",
    "options": [
      "to delete",
      "to warn",
      "registration",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "to delete"
  },
  {
    "question": "waarschuwen",
    "options": [
      "to warn",
      "to steal",
      "to be bored",
      "to sign up"
    ],
    "answer": "to warn"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich ontwikkelen",
    "options": [
      "to develop",
      "to warn",
      "to steal",
      "to copy"
    ],
    "answer": "to develop"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich vervelen",
    "options": [
      "to be bored",
      "to pick out",
      "to warn",
      "to activate"
    ],
    "answer": "to be bored"
  },
  {
    "question": "achteraf",
    "options": [
      "in hindsight",
      "brilliant",
      "evening",
      "paper"
    ],
    "answer": "in hindsight"
  },
  {
    "question": "briljant",
    "options": [
      "motivated",
      "brilliant",
      "cool",
      "to stimulate"
    ],
    "answer": "brilliant"
  },
  {
    "question": "de avond",
    "options": [
      "evening",
      "unsatisfactory (grade)",
      "report card",
      "reasonable"
    ],
    "answer": "evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "de onvoldoende",
    "options": [
      "unsatisfactory (grade)",
      "to lose",
      "to worry",
      "little man"
    ],
    "answer": "unsatisfactory (grade)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voldoende",
    "options": [
      "satisfactory (grade)",
      "childish",
      "stubborn",
      "total"
    ],
    "answer": "satisfactory (grade)"
  },
  {
    "question": "eigenwijs",
    "options": [
      "reasonble",
      "stubborn",
      "to recognize",
      "motivated"
    ],
    "answer": "stubborn"
  },
  {
    "question": "gemotiveerd",
    "options": [
      "motivated",
      "report card",
      "to stimulate",
      "cool"
    ],
    "answer": "motivated"
  },
  {
    "question": "herkennen",
    "options": [
      "to recognize",
      "evening",
      "to lose",
      "insufficient"
    ],
    "answer": "to recognize"
  },
  {
    "question": "het mannetje",
    "options": [
      "little man",
      "childish",
      "to worry",
      "reasonable"
    ],
    "answer": "little man"
  },
  {
    "question": "het papier",
    "options": [
      "paper",
      "to stimulate",
      "report card",
      "cool"
    ],
    "answer": "paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "het rapport",
    "options": [
      "report card",
      "brilliant",
      "motivated",
      "to worry"
    ],
    "answer": "report card"
  },
  {
    "question": "het resultaat",
    "options": [
      "result",
      "childish",
      "unsatisfactory (grade)",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "result"
  },
  {
    "question": "kinderachtig",
    "options": [
      "childish",
      "total",
      "to recognize",
      "to stimulate"
    ],
    "answer": "childish"
  },
  {
    "question": "kwijtraken",
    "options": [
      "to lose",
      "insufficient",
      "cool",
      "reasonable"
    ],
    "answer": "to lose"
  },
  {
    "question": "onvoldoende",
    "options": [
      "insufficient",
      "stubborn",
      "motivated",
      "report card"
    ],
    "answer": "insufficient"
  },
  {
    "question": "redelijk",
    "options": [
      "reasonable",
      "to worry",
      "little man",
      "childish"
    ],
    "answer": "reasonable"
  },
  {
    "question": "stimuleren",
    "options": [
      "to stimulate",
      "to recognize",
      "unsatisfactory (grade)",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "to stimulate"
  },
  {
    "question": "tof",
    "options": [
      "cool",
      "satisfactory (grade)",
      "brilliant",
      "evening"
    ],
    "answer": "cool"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich zorgen maken",
    "options": [
      "to worry",
      "report card",
      "childish",
      "motivated"
    ],
    "answer": "to worry"
  },
  {
    "question": "het totaal",
    "options": [
      "total",
      "insufficient",
      "to stimulate",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "total"
  },
  {
    "question": "toen",
    "options": [
      "when",
      "reasonble",
      "cool",
      "paper"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "binnenlopen",
    "options": [
      "to walk in",
      "promotion",
      "library",
      "choice"
    ],
    "answer": "to walk in"
  },
  {
    "question": "de actie",
    "options": [
      "promotion",
      "loan period",
      "possibility",
      "member"
    ],
    "answer": "promotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bibliotheek",
    "options": [
      "library",
      "to set up",
      "monitor",
      "WiFi"
    ],
    "answer": "library"
  },
  {
    "question": "de keuze",
    "options": [
      "choice",
      "membership",
      "digital",
      "to reserve"
    ],
    "answer": "choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "de leentermijn",
    "options": [
      "loan period",
      "trial membership",
      "tablet",
      "exciting"
    ],
    "answer": "loan period"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mogelijkheid",
    "options": [
      "possibility",
      "item",
      "to study",
      "reading book"
    ],
    "answer": "possibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pc",
    "options": [
      "pc",
      "special",
      "library",
      "promotion"
    ],
    "answer": "pc"
  },
  {
    "question": "de strip",
    "options": [
      "comic book",
      "member",
      "tablet",
      "to finish reading"
    ],
    "answer": "comic book"
  },
  {
    "question": "de studieplek",
    "options": [
      "place to study",
      "WiFi",
      "unlimited",
      "digital"
    ],
    "answer": "place to study"
  },
  {
    "question": "digitaal",
    "options": [
      "digital",
      "promotion",
      "to reserve",
      "thousands"
    ],
    "answer": "digital"
  },
  {
    "question": "duizenden",
    "options": [
      "thousands",
      "library",
      "trial membership",
      "to study"
    ],
    "answer": "thousands"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lid",
    "options": [
      "member",
      "choice",
      "tablet",
      "special"
    ],
    "answer": "member"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lidmaatschap",
    "options": [
      "membership",
      "item",
      "monitor",
      "exciting"
    ],
    "answer": "membership"
  },
  {
    "question": "het luisterboek",
    "options": [
      "listening book",
      "promotion",
      "unlimited",
      "to finish reading"
    ],
    "answer": "listening book"
  },
  {
    "question": "het proeflidmaatschap",
    "options": [
      "trial membership",
      "WiFi",
      "to walk in",
      "library"
    ],
    "answer": "trial membership"
  },
  {
    "question": "het scherm",
    "options": [
      "monitor",
      "to reserve",
      "special",
      "promotion"
    ],
    "answer": "monitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "het voorleesboek",
    "options": [
      "reading book",
      "member",
      "tablet",
      "exciting"
    ],
    "answer": "reading book"
  },
  {
    "question": "informatief",
    "options": [
      "informative",
      "to study",
      "unlimited",
      "item"
    ],
    "answer": "informative"
  },
  {
    "question": "inrichten",
    "options": [
      "to set up",
      "promotion",
      "library",
      "WiFi"
    ],
    "answer": "to set up"
  },
  {
    "question": "onbeperkt",
    "options": [
      "unlimited",
      "trial membership",
      "special",
      "monitor"
    ],
    "answer": "unlimited"
  },
  {
    "question": "reserveren",
    "options": [
      "to reserve",
      "to walk in",
      "membership",
      "choice"
    ],
    "answer": "to reserve"
  },
  {
    "question": "spannend",
    "options": [
      "exciting",
      "digital",
      "item",
      "WiFi"
    ],
    "answer": "exciting"
  },
  {
    "question": "speciaal",
    "options": [
      "special",
      "member",
      "library",
      "to study"
    ],
    "answer": "special"
  },
  {
    "question": "studeren",
    "options": [
      "to study",
      "promotion",
      "monitor",
      "thousands"
    ],
    "answer": "to study"
  },
  {
    "question": "stuk",
    "options": [
      "item",
      "trial membership",
      "choice",
      "WiFi"
    ],
    "answer": "item"
  },
  {
    "question": "uithebben",
    "options": [
      "to finish reading",
      "membership",
      "to walk in",
      "digital"
    ],
    "answer": "to finish reading"
  },
  {
    "question": "verlengen",
    "options": [
      "to extend",
      "special",
      "tablet",
      "monitor"
    ],
    "answer": "to extend"
  },
  {
    "question": "wifi",
    "options": [
      "WiFi",
      "promotion",
      "library",
      "exciting"
    ],
    "answer": "WiFi"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tablet",
    "options": [
      "tablet",
      "to study",
      "choice",
      "to reserve"
    ],
    "answer": "tablet"
  },
  {
    "question": "bereid",
    "options": [
      "prepared",
      "accessible",
      "to offer",
      "gross"
    ],
    "answer": "prepared"
  },
  {
    "question": "bereikbaar",
    "options": [
      "accessible",
      "prepared",
      "wage",
      "pack"
    ],
    "answer": "accessible"
  },
  {
    "question": "bieden",
    "options": [
      "to offer",
      "perseverance",
      "salary",
      "mix"
    ],
    "answer": "to offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "bruto",
    "options": [
      "gross",
      "monthly",
      "both",
      "weekly"
    ],
    "answer": "gross"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bereikbaarheid",
    "options": [
      "accessibility",
      "physical",
      "application form",
      "wage"
    ],
    "answer": "accessibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inpakker",
    "options": [
      "packer",
      "to wrap",
      "magazine",
      "mentalilty"
    ],
    "answer": "packer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de instelling",
    "options": [
      "mentality",
      "mix",
      "salary",
      "gross"
    ],
    "answer": "mentality"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mix",
    "options": [
      "mix",
      "prepared",
      "application form",
      "physical"
    ],
    "answer": "mix"
  },
  {
    "question": "de omschrijving",
    "options": [
      "description",
      "salary",
      "both",
      "to offer"
    ],
    "answer": "description"
  },
  {
    "question": "de persoonsgegevens",
    "options": [
      "personal details",
      "weekly",
      "perseverance",
      "to sort"
    ],
    "answer": "personal details"
  },
  {
    "question": "de productiemedewerker",
    "options": [
      "production worker",
      "accessible",
      "pack",
      "psychological"
    ],
    "answer": "production worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werktijden",
    "options": [
      "working hours",
      "gross",
      "both",
      "to wrap"
    ],
    "answer": "working hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werkzaamheden",
    "options": [
      "activities",
      "mix",
      "to offer",
      "monthly"
    ],
    "answer": "activities"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorwerken",
    "options": [
      "to continue working",
      "physical",
      "wage",
      "pack"
    ],
    "answer": "to continue working"
  },
  {
    "question": "fysiek",
    "options": [
      "physical",
      "prepared",
      "salary",
      "personal details"
    ],
    "answer": "physical"
  },
  {
    "question": "het doorzettingsvermogen",
    "options": [
      "perseverance",
      "to offer",
      "gross",
      "to wrap"
    ],
    "answer": "perseverance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het loon",
    "options": [
      "wage",
      "weekly",
      "mentalilty",
      "monthly"
    ],
    "answer": "wage"
  },
  {
    "question": "het minimumloon",
    "options": [
      "minimum wage",
      "pack",
      "salary",
      "prepared"
    ],
    "answer": "minimum wage"
  },
  {
    "question": "het salaris",
    "options": [
      "salary",
      "physical",
      "weekly",
      "application form"
    ],
    "answer": "salary"
  },
  {
    "question": "het sollicitatieformulier",
    "options": [
      "application form",
      "pack",
      "to sort",
      "psychological"
    ],
    "answer": "application form"
  },
  {
    "question": "het talent",
    "options": [
      "talent",
      "both",
      "gross",
      "prepared"
    ],
    "answer": "talent"
  },
  {
    "question": "het tijdschrift",
    "options": [
      "magazine",
      "mentalilty",
      "accessible",
      "wage"
    ],
    "answer": "magazine"
  },
  {
    "question": "inpakken",
    "options": [
      "to wrap",
      "wage",
      "salary",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "to wrap"
  },
  {
    "question": "maandelijks",
    "options": [
      "monthly",
      "minimum wage",
      "perseverance",
      "pack"
    ],
    "answer": "monthly"
  },
  {
    "question": "netto",
    "options": [
      "net",
      "to offer",
      "psychological",
      "wage"
    ],
    "answer": "net"
  },
  {
    "question": "psychisch",
    "options": [
      "psychological",
      "physical",
      "wage",
      "prepared"
    ],
    "answer": "psychological"
  },
  {
    "question": "sorteren",
    "options": [
      "to sort",
      "to continue working",
      "minimum wage",
      "pack"
    ],
    "answer": "to sort"
  },
  {
    "question": "uiteraard",
    "options": [
      "of course",
      "personal details",
      "gross",
      "to wrap"
    ],
    "answer": "of course"
  },
  {
    "question": "wekelijks",
    "options": [
      "weekly",
      "mentalilty",
      "salary",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "weekly"
  },
  {
    "question": "zowel … als",
    "options": [
      "both",
      "prepared",
      "pack",
      "to wrap"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "passen",
    "options": [
      "to suit",
      "pack",
      "gross",
      "minimum wage"
    ],
    "answer": "to suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanpakken",
    "options": [
      "to handle",
      "to advise",
      "listener",
      "radio"
    ],
    "answer": "to handle"
  },
  {
    "question": "adviseren",
    "options": [
      "to advise",
      "to contact someone",
      "network",
      "unemployed"
    ],
    "answer": "to advise"
  },
  {
    "question": "behoorlijk",
    "options": [
      "quite",
      "temporary",
      "employee",
      "sports club"
    ],
    "answer": "quite"
  },
  {
    "question": "contact opnemen met iemand",
    "options": [
      "to contact someone",
      "to hear about",
      "older person",
      "unemployment"
    ],
    "answer": "to contact someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "de luisteraar",
    "options": [
      "listener",
      "jobseeker",
      "network",
      "temporary"
    ],
    "answer": "listener"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oudere",
    "options": [
      "older person",
      "unemployment benefits",
      "to network",
      "employer"
    ],
    "answer": "older person"
  },
  {
    "question": "de radio",
    "options": [
      "radio",
      "employee",
      "to handle",
      "unemployed"
    ],
    "answer": "radio"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sportclub",
    "options": [
      "sports club",
      "contact",
      "to advise",
      "jobseeker"
    ],
    "answer": "sports club"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werkgever",
    "options": [
      "employer",
      "to contact someone",
      "older person",
      "to hear about"
    ],
    "answer": "employer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werkloosheid",
    "options": [
      "unemployment",
      "to handle",
      "listener",
      "network"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werkzoekende",
    "options": [
      "jobseeker",
      "to advise",
      "temporary",
      "employee"
    ],
    "answer": "jobseeker"
  },
  {
    "question": "het contact",
    "options": [
      "contact",
      "unemployed",
      "employer",
      "radio"
    ],
    "answer": "contact"
  },
  {
    "question": "het netwerk",
    "options": [
      "network",
      "to network",
      "unemployment benefits",
      "sports club"
    ],
    "answer": "network"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uitzendbureau",
    "options": [
      "temp agency",
      "to hear about",
      "jobseeker",
      "to advise"
    ],
    "answer": "temp agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "horen van",
    "options": [
      "to hear about",
      "employee",
      "contact",
      "temporary"
    ],
    "answer": "to hear about"
  },
  {
    "question": "netwerken",
    "options": [
      "to network",
      "unemployed",
      "older person",
      "to handle"
    ],
    "answer": "to network"
  },
  {
    "question": "tijdelijk",
    "options": [
      "temporary",
      "network",
      "to contact someone",
      "listener"
    ],
    "answer": "temporary"
  },
  {
    "question": "vast",
    "options": [
      "permanent",
      "to advise",
      "sports club",
      "jobseeker"
    ],
    "answer": "permanent"
  },
  {
    "question": "werkloos",
    "options": [
      "unemployed",
      "to handle",
      "employer",
      "to network"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployed"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitkering",
    "options": [
      "unemployment benefits",
      "listener",
      "to contact someone",
      "older person"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployment benefits"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werknemer",
    "options": [
      "employee",
      "to advise",
      "temporary",
      "network"
    ],
    "answer": "employee"
  },
  {
    "question": "afwisselend",
    "options": [
      "varied",
      "reliable",
      "fascinating",
      "requirement"
    ],
    "answer": "varied"
  },
  {
    "question": "betrouwbaar",
    "options": [
      "reliable",
      "varied",
      "fascinating",
      "position"
    ],
    "answer": "reliable"
  },
  {
    "question": "boeiend",
    "options": [
      "fascinating",
      "motivation",
      "cleaner",
      "vacancy"
    ],
    "answer": "fascinating"
  },
  {
    "question": "de eis",
    "options": [
      "requirement",
      "vacancy",
      "fashion",
      "position"
    ],
    "answer": "requirement"
  },
  {
    "question": "de functie",
    "options": [
      "position",
      "clothing",
      "cleaner",
      "fashion"
    ],
    "answer": "position"
  },
  {
    "question": "de functie-eisen",
    "options": [
      "job requirements",
      "to strengthen",
      "customer-oriented",
      "to apply (for a job)"
    ],
    "answer": "job requirements"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kleding",
    "options": [
      "clothing",
      "day care centre",
      "place",
      "reliable"
    ],
    "answer": "clothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mode",
    "options": [
      "fashion",
      "vacancy",
      "motivation",
      "to deal"
    ],
    "answer": "fashion"
  },
  {
    "question": "de motivatie",
    "options": [
      "motivation",
      "chambermaid",
      "reliable",
      "to apply (for a job)"
    ],
    "answer": "motivation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schoonmaker",
    "options": [
      "cleaner",
      "position",
      "to strengthen",
      "fashion"
    ],
    "answer": "cleaner"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vacature",
    "options": [
      "vacancy",
      "customer-oriented",
      "varied",
      "motivation"
    ],
    "answer": "vacancy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Engeland",
    "options": [
      "England",
      "clothing",
      "job requirements",
      "to deal"
    ],
    "answer": "England"
  },
  {
    "question": "geschikt",
    "options": [
      "suitable",
      "vacancy",
      "to apply (for a job)",
      "day care centre"
    ],
    "answer": "suitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kamermeisje",
    "options": [
      "chambermaid",
      "to strengthen",
      "fashion",
      "cleaner"
    ],
    "answer": "chambermaid"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kantoor",
    "options": [
      "office",
      "vacancy",
      "fashion",
      "varied"
    ],
    "answer": "office"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kinderdagverblijf",
    "options": [
      "day care centre",
      "position",
      "customer-oriented",
      "reliable"
    ],
    "answer": "day care centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "klantgericht",
    "options": [
      "customer-oriented",
      "requirement",
      "vacancy",
      "fascinating"
    ],
    "answer": "customer-oriented"
  },
  {
    "question": "omgaan met",
    "options": [
      "to deal",
      "motivation",
      "fashion",
      "cleaner"
    ],
    "answer": "to deal"
  },
  {
    "question": "versterken",
    "options": [
      "to strengthen",
      "vacancy",
      "office",
      "fashion"
    ],
    "answer": "to strengthen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de plaats",
    "options": [
      "place",
      "reliable",
      "vacancy",
      "to apply (for a job)"
    ],
    "answer": "place"
  },
  {
    "question": "solliciteren",
    "options": [
      "to apply (for a job)",
      "customer-oriented",
      "fashion",
      "varied"
    ],
    "answer": "to apply (for a job)"
  },
  {
    "question": "aannemen",
    "options": [
      "to hire",
      "helpful",
      "goods",
      "manager"
    ],
    "answer": "to hire"
  },
  {
    "question": "behulpzaam",
    "options": [
      "helpful",
      "shift",
      "job interview",
      "accurate"
    ],
    "answer": "helpful"
  },
  {
    "question": "beschikbaar",
    "options": [
      "available",
      "employee",
      "flexible",
      "warehouse"
    ],
    "answer": "available"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dienst",
    "options": [
      "shift",
      "task",
      "to unload",
      "quality"
    ],
    "answer": "shift"
  },
  {
    "question": "de goederen",
    "options": [
      "goods",
      "good morning",
      "Human Resources",
      "to apply for a job"
    ],
    "answer": "goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "de manager",
    "options": [
      "manager",
      "to load",
      "example",
      "well"
    ],
    "answer": "manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "de medewerker",
    "options": [
      "employee",
      "to discuss",
      "full time",
      "independent"
    ],
    "answer": "employee"
  },
  {
    "question": "de taak",
    "options": [
      "task",
      "warehouse",
      "to take over",
      "diligent"
    ],
    "answer": "task"
  },
  {
    "question": "flexibel",
    "options": [
      "flexible",
      "to hire",
      "quality",
      "job interview"
    ],
    "answer": "flexible"
  },
  {
    "question": "fulltime",
    "options": [
      "full time",
      "to unload",
      "helpful",
      "to apply for a job"
    ],
    "answer": "full time"
  },
  {
    "question": "goedemorgen",
    "options": [
      "good morning",
      "to discuss",
      "Human Resources",
      "accurate"
    ],
    "answer": "good morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "het magazijn",
    "options": [
      "warehouse",
      "diligent",
      "shift",
      "to load"
    ],
    "answer": "warehouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "het sollicitatiegesprek",
    "options": [
      "job interview",
      "to take over",
      "helpful",
      "employee"
    ],
    "answer": "job interview"
  },
  {
    "question": "het voorbeeld",
    "options": [
      "example",
      "manager",
      "available",
      "well"
    ],
    "answer": "example"
  },
  {
    "question": "ijverig",
    "options": [
      "diligent",
      "goods",
      "full time",
      "to hire"
    ],
    "answer": "diligent"
  },
  {
    "question": "laden",
    "options": [
      "to load",
      "to discuss",
      "shift",
      "flexible"
    ],
    "answer": "to load"
  },
  {
    "question": "lossen",
    "options": [
      "to unload",
      "to apply for a job",
      "good morning",
      "independent"
    ],
    "answer": "to unload"
  },
  {
    "question": "nauwkeurig",
    "options": [
      "accurate",
      "employee",
      "manager",
      "to hire"
    ],
    "answer": "accurate"
  },
  {
    "question": "overleggen",
    "options": [
      "to discuss",
      "warehouse",
      "helpful",
      "full time"
    ],
    "answer": "to discuss"
  },
  {
    "question": "overnemen",
    "options": [
      "to take over",
      "to unload",
      "quality",
      "available"
    ],
    "answer": "to take over"
  },
  {
    "question": "solliciteren",
    "options": [
      "to apply for a job",
      "task",
      "to load",
      "diligent"
    ],
    "answer": "to apply for a job"
  },
  {
    "question": "tja",
    "options": [
      "well",
      "shift",
      "manager",
      "example"
    ],
    "answer": "well"
  },
  {
    "question": "zelfstandig",
    "options": [
      "independent",
      "to discuss",
      "to unload",
      "employee"
    ],
    "answer": "independent"
  },
  {
    "question": "personeelszaken",
    "options": [
      "Human Resources",
      "full time",
      "goods",
      "helpful"
    ],
    "answer": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kwaliteit",
    "options": [
      "quality",
      "to take over",
      "good morning",
      "to hire"
    ],
    "answer": "quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "apart",
    "options": [
      "battery",
      "air",
      "both",
      "separately"
    ],
    "answer": "separately"
  },
  {
    "question": "chemisch",
    "options": [
      "harmful",
      "chemical",
      "dust",
      "to burn"
    ],
    "answer": "chemical"
  },
  {
    "question": "de batterij",
    "options": [
      "battery",
      "garbage bag",
      "factory",
      "shell"
    ],
    "answer": "battery"
  },
  {
    "question": "de container",
    "options": [
      "pot",
      "container",
      "metal",
      "cardboard"
    ],
    "answer": "container"
  },
  {
    "question": "de fabriek",
    "options": [
      "factory",
      "to collect",
      "dust",
      "chewing gum"
    ],
    "answer": "factory"
  },
  {
    "question": "de frituurolie",
    "options": [
      "frying oil",
      "lost",
      "card",
      "air"
    ],
    "answer": "frying oil"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kauwgom",
    "options": [
      "frying oil",
      "chewing gum",
      "card",
      "factory"
    ],
    "answer": "chewing gum"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lucht",
    "options": [
      "air",
      "waste",
      "cardboard",
      "harmful"
    ],
    "answer": "air"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pas",
    "options": [
      "card",
      "to burn",
      "separately",
      "factory"
    ],
    "answer": "card"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pot",
    "options": [
      "shell",
      "dust",
      "pot",
      "battery"
    ],
    "answer": "pot"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schil",
    "options": [
      "shell",
      "to hand in",
      "to sort",
      "metal"
    ],
    "answer": "shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stof",
    "options": [
      "dust",
      "chemical",
      "factory",
      "pot"
    ],
    "answer": "dust"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verf",
    "options": [
      "paint",
      "container",
      "by telephone",
      "lost"
    ],
    "answer": "paint"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vuilniszak",
    "options": [
      "garbage bag",
      "battery",
      "to collect",
      "air"
    ],
    "answer": "garbage bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "het afval",
    "options": [
      "waste",
      "shell",
      "separately",
      "to hand in"
    ],
    "answer": "waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "het karton",
    "options": [
      "cardboard",
      "chemical",
      "pot",
      "to burn"
    ],
    "answer": "cardboard"
  },
  {
    "question": "het metaal",
    "options": [
      "metal",
      "frying oil",
      "air",
      "lost"
    ],
    "answer": "metal"
  },
  {
    "question": "inleveren",
    "options": [
      "to hand in",
      "to sort",
      "battery",
      "dust"
    ],
    "answer": "to hand in"
  },
  {
    "question": "kwijt",
    "options": [
      "lost",
      "paint",
      "garbage bag",
      "factory"
    ],
    "answer": "lost"
  },
  {
    "question": "schadelijk",
    "options": [
      "harmful",
      "card",
      "to collect",
      "separately"
    ],
    "answer": "harmful"
  },
  {
    "question": "scheiden",
    "options": [
      "to sort",
      "frying oil",
      "dust",
      "cardboard"
    ],
    "answer": "to sort"
  },
  {
    "question": "telefonisch",
    "options": [
      "by telephone",
      "to burn",
      "shell",
      "battery"
    ],
    "answer": "by telephone"
  },
  {
    "question": "terechtkomen",
    "options": [
      "to end up",
      "to hand in",
      "cardboard",
      "factory"
    ],
    "answer": "to end up"
  },
  {
    "question": "verbranden",
    "options": [
      "to burn",
      "to sort",
      "dust",
      "garbage bag"
    ],
    "answer": "to burn"
  },
  {
    "question": "verzamelen",
    "options": [
      "to collect",
      "air",
      "pot",
      "chemical"
    ],
    "answer": "to collect"
  },
  {
    "question": "aaien",
    "options": [
      "to pet",
      "to climb",
      "to shout",
      "to run"
    ],
    "answer": "to pet"
  },
  {
    "question": "afgelopen",
    "options": [
      "last",
      "ambulance",
      "step stool",
      "to break"
    ],
    "answer": "last"
  },
  {
    "question": "bijten",
    "options": [
      "to bite",
      "to lose",
      "highway",
      "to shout"
    ],
    "answer": "to bite"
  },
  {
    "question": "bloeden",
    "options": [
      "to bleed",
      "to bump into",
      "to be shocked",
      "to brake"
    ],
    "answer": "to bleed"
  },
  {
    "question": "breken",
    "options": [
      "to break",
      "to climb",
      "to shout",
      "blood"
    ],
    "answer": "to break"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ambulance",
    "options": [
      "ambulance",
      "ground",
      "to pet",
      "suddenly"
    ],
    "answer": "ambulance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de grond",
    "options": [
      "ground",
      "to lose",
      "to run",
      "to bite"
    ],
    "answer": "ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "de heup",
    "options": [
      "hip",
      "to be shocked",
      "step stool",
      "to shout"
    ],
    "answer": "hip"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kilometer",
    "options": [
      "kilometre",
      "ambulance",
      "to break",
      "to climb"
    ],
    "answer": "kilometre"
  },
  {
    "question": "de punt",
    "options": [
      "edge",
      "to pet",
      "blood",
      "to shout"
    ],
    "answer": "edge"
  },
  {
    "question": "de seconde",
    "options": [
      "second",
      "to bite",
      "to shout",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "second"
  },
  {
    "question": "de snelweg",
    "options": [
      "highway",
      "to brake",
      "to be shocked",
      "to climb"
    ],
    "answer": "highway"
  },
  {
    "question": "de taxi",
    "options": [
      "taxi",
      "to shout",
      "to lose",
      "step stool"
    ],
    "answer": "taxi"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vloer",
    "options": [
      "floor",
      "to pet",
      "to bite",
      "to break"
    ],
    "answer": "floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bloed",
    "options": [
      "blood",
      "to climb",
      "to shout",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "het evenwicht",
    "options": [
      "balance",
      "to shout",
      "to be shocked",
      "ambulance"
    ],
    "answer": "balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het hoofd",
    "options": [
      "head",
      "to brake",
      "to bite",
      "to pet"
    ],
    "answer": "head"
  },
  {
    "question": "het keukentrapje",
    "options": [
      "step stool",
      "to lose",
      "to shout",
      "to break"
    ],
    "answer": "step stool"
  },
  {
    "question": "ineens",
    "options": [
      "suddenly",
      "to be shocked",
      "to run",
      "to shout"
    ],
    "answer": "suddenly"
  },
  {
    "question": "klimmen",
    "options": [
      "to climb",
      "to brake",
      "to bite",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "to climb"
  },
  {
    "question": "opbotsen tegen",
    "options": [
      "to bump into",
      "to shout",
      "to break",
      "to pet"
    ],
    "answer": "to bump into"
  },
  {
    "question": "plotseling",
    "options": [
      "suddenly",
      "to run",
      "to shout",
      "to lose"
    ],
    "answer": "suddenly"
  },
  {
    "question": "remmen",
    "options": [
      "to brake",
      "to climb",
      "to lose",
      "to pet"
    ],
    "answer": "to brake"
  },
  {
    "question": "rennen",
    "options": [
      "to run",
      "to shout",
      "to bite",
      "blood"
    ],
    "answer": "to run"
  },
  {
    "question": "roepen",
    "options": [
      "to shout",
      "to break",
      "to pet",
      "to climb"
    ],
    "answer": "to shout"
  },
  {
    "question": "scherp",
    "options": [
      "sharp",
      "to lose",
      "to shout",
      "to pet"
    ],
    "answer": "sharp"
  },
  {
    "question": "schrikken",
    "options": [
      "to be shocked",
      "to run",
      "to bite",
      "to break"
    ],
    "answer": "to be shocked"
  },
  {
    "question": "stilstaan",
    "options": [
      "to stand still",
      "to shout",
      "to lose",
      "to run"
    ],
    "answer": "to stand still"
  },
  {
    "question": "verliezen",
    "options": [
      "to lose",
      "to break",
      "to pet",
      "to shout"
    ],
    "answer": "to lose"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bedoeling",
    "options": [
      "intention",
      "contribution",
      "toaster",
      "coat"
    ],
    "answer": "intention"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bijdrage",
    "options": [
      "contribution",
      "intention",
      "repair",
      "tools"
    ],
    "answer": "contribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "de broodrooster",
    "options": [
      "toaster",
      "coat",
      "leg",
      "hole"
    ],
    "answer": "toaster"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gebruiksaanwijzing",
    "options": [
      "operating instructions",
      "volunteer",
      "rip",
      "loose"
    ],
    "answer": "operating instructions"
  },
  {
    "question": "de jas",
    "options": [
      "coat",
      "sewing machine",
      "hole",
      "tools"
    ],
    "answer": "coat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de naaimachine",
    "options": [
      "sewing machine",
      "toaster",
      "knowledge",
      "repair"
    ],
    "answer": "sewing machine"
  },
  {
    "question": "de poot",
    "options": [
      "leg",
      "rip",
      "intention",
      "operating instructions"
    ],
    "answer": "leg"
  },
  {
    "question": "de reparatie",
    "options": [
      "repair",
      "volunteer",
      "coat",
      "to pay attention"
    ],
    "answer": "repair"
  },
  {
    "question": "de scheur",
    "options": [
      "rip",
      "tools",
      "sewing machine",
      "contribution"
    ],
    "answer": "rip"
  },
  {
    "question": "de smartphone",
    "options": [
      "smartphone",
      "voluntary",
      "while",
      "objective"
    ],
    "answer": "smartphone"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vrijwilliger",
    "options": [
      "volunteer",
      "material",
      "to solve",
      "coat"
    ],
    "answer": "volunteer"
  },
  {
    "question": "enthousiast",
    "options": [
      "enthusiastic",
      "repair",
      "loose",
      "knowledge"
    ],
    "answer": "enthusiastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "het doel",
    "options": [
      "objective",
      "operating instructions",
      "rip",
      "to pay attention"
    ],
    "answer": "objective"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gaatje",
    "options": [
      "hole",
      "contribution",
      "while",
      "toaster"
    ],
    "answer": "hole"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gereedschap",
    "options": [
      "tools",
      "to pay attention",
      "voluntary",
      "repair"
    ],
    "answer": "tools"
  },
  {
    "question": "het materiaal",
    "options": [
      "material",
      "sewing machine",
      "coat",
      "intention"
    ],
    "answer": "material"
  },
  {
    "question": "los",
    "options": [
      "loose",
      "while",
      "objective",
      "to solve"
    ],
    "answer": "loose"
  },
  {
    "question": "opletten",
    "options": [
      "to pay attention",
      "volunteer",
      "tools",
      "rip"
    ],
    "answer": "to pay attention"
  },
  {
    "question": "oplossen",
    "options": [
      "to solve",
      "coat",
      "operating instructions",
      "voluntary"
    ],
    "answer": "to solve"
  },
  {
    "question": "terwijl",
    "options": [
      "while",
      "toaster",
      "to pay attention",
      "material"
    ],
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "question": "verdwijnen",
    "options": [
      "to disappear",
      "to solve",
      "coat",
      "toaster"
    ],
    "answer": "to disappear"
  },
  {
    "question": "vrijwillig",
    "options": [
      "voluntary",
      "rip",
      "repair",
      "to pay attention"
    ],
    "answer": "voluntary"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kennis",
    "options": [
      "knowledge",
      "intention",
      "tools",
      "while"
    ],
    "answer": "knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "bezig",
    "options": [
      "busy",
      "pocket",
      "wallet",
      "broken"
    ],
    "answer": "busy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de band",
    "options": [
      "(conveyor) belt / tyre",
      "egg",
      "bad luck",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "(conveyor) belt / tyre"
  },
  {
    "question": "de fietsenmaker",
    "options": [
      "bicycle repair shop",
      "to come home",
      "awake",
      "incredible"
    ],
    "answer": "bicycle repair shop"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huissleutel",
    "options": [
      "house key",
      "then / afterwards",
      "spare",
      "pocket"
    ],
    "answer": "house key"
  },
  {
    "question": "de jaszak",
    "options": [
      "coat pocket",
      "broken",
      "wallet",
      "punctured"
    ],
    "answer": "coat pocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pech",
    "options": [
      "bad luck",
      "in the meantime",
      "over / past",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "bad luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "de portemonnee",
    "options": [
      "wallet",
      "spare",
      "pocket",
      "incredible"
    ],
    "answer": "wallet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de reserve",
    "options": [
      "spare",
      "bicycle repair shop",
      "broken",
      "awake"
    ],
    "answer": "spare"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zak",
    "options": [
      "pocket",
      "egg",
      "bad luck",
      "broken"
    ],
    "answer": "pocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "erachter komen",
    "options": [
      "to find out",
      "to come home",
      "then / afterwards",
      "incredible"
    ],
    "answer": "to find out"
  },
  {
    "question": "gebroken",
    "options": [
      "broken",
      "spare",
      "awake",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "broken"
  },
  {
    "question": "inmiddels",
    "options": [
      "in the meantime",
      "over / past",
      "to find out",
      "bad luck"
    ],
    "answer": "in the meantime"
  },
  {
    "question": "lek",
    "options": [
      "punctured",
      "egg",
      "to come home",
      "awake"
    ],
    "answer": "punctured"
  },
  {
    "question": "net",
    "options": [
      "just",
      "broken",
      "spare",
      "bad luck"
    ],
    "answer": "just"
  },
  {
    "question": "onderweg",
    "options": [
      "on the way",
      "pocket",
      "awake",
      "then / afterwards"
    ],
    "answer": "on the way"
  },
  {
    "question": "ongelofelijk",
    "options": [
      "incredible",
      "wallet",
      "egg",
      "to come home"
    ],
    "answer": "incredible"
  },
  {
    "question": "thuiskomen",
    "options": [
      "to come home",
      "in the meantime",
      "just",
      "bad luck"
    ],
    "answer": "to come home"
  },
  {
    "question": "uiteindelijk",
    "options": [
      "in the end",
      "punctured",
      "spare",
      "awake"
    ],
    "answer": "in the end"
  },
  {
    "question": "vervolgens",
    "options": [
      "then / afterwards",
      "egg",
      "wallet",
      "pocket"
    ],
    "answer": "then / afterwards"
  },
  {
    "question": "voorbij",
    "options": [
      "over / past",
      "awake",
      "bicycle repair shop",
      "to find out"
    ],
    "answer": "over / past"
  },
  {
    "question": "wakker",
    "options": [
      "awake",
      "broken",
      "bad luck",
      "pocket"
    ],
    "answer": "awake"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ei",
    "options": [
      "egg",
      "spare",
      "just",
      "incredible"
    ],
    "answer": "egg"
  },
  {
    "question": "alweer",
    "options": [
      "already",
      "advertisement",
      "playpen",
      "century"
    ],
    "answer": "already"
  },
  {
    "question": "de advertentie",
    "options": [
      "advertisement",
      "memory",
      "basement",
      "high chair"
    ],
    "answer": "advertisement"
  },
  {
    "question": "de box",
    "options": [
      "playpen",
      "stroller",
      "mattress",
      "remark"
    ],
    "answer": "playpen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de eeuw",
    "options": [
      "century",
      "cradle",
      "bed(stead)",
      "to keep"
    ],
    "answer": "century"
  },
  {
    "question": "de herinnering",
    "options": [
      "memory",
      "including",
      "to seem",
      "to add"
    ],
    "answer": "memory"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kelder",
    "options": [
      "basement",
      "worth",
      "to get rid of",
      "pity (it's a pity)"
    ],
    "answer": "basement"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kinderstoel",
    "options": [
      "high chair",
      "the other day",
      "characteristic",
      "bed(stead)"
    ],
    "answer": "high chair"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kinderwagen",
    "options": [
      "stroller",
      "playpen",
      "remark",
      "memory"
    ],
    "answer": "stroller"
  },
  {
    "question": "de matras",
    "options": [
      "mattress",
      "advertisement",
      "to keep",
      "including"
    ],
    "answer": "mattress"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opmerking",
    "options": [
      "remark",
      "cradle",
      "already",
      "pity (it's a pity)"
    ],
    "answer": "remark"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wieg",
    "options": [
      "cradle",
      "basement",
      "to add",
      "to seem"
    ],
    "answer": "cradle"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kenmerk",
    "options": [
      "characteristic",
      "high chair",
      "to get rid of",
      "the other day"
    ],
    "answer": "characteristic"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ledikant",
    "options": [
      "bed(stead)",
      "advertisement",
      "to keep",
      "already"
    ],
    "answer": "bed(stead)"
  },
  {
    "question": "houden",
    "options": [
      "to keep",
      "including",
      "memory",
      "playpen"
    ],
    "answer": "to keep"
  },
  {
    "question": "inclusief",
    "options": [
      "including",
      "worth",
      "remark",
      "to add"
    ],
    "answer": "including"
  },
  {
    "question": "lijken",
    "options": [
      "to seem",
      "advertisement",
      "the other day",
      "stroller"
    ],
    "answer": "to seem"
  },
  {
    "question": "toevoegen",
    "options": [
      "to add",
      "already",
      "bed(stead)",
      "pity (it's a pity)"
    ],
    "answer": "to add"
  },
  {
    "question": "waard",
    "options": [
      "worth",
      "playpen",
      "to seem",
      "memory"
    ],
    "answer": "worth"
  },
  {
    "question": "wegdoen",
    "options": [
      "to get rid of",
      "cradle",
      "high chair",
      "advertisement"
    ],
    "answer": "to get rid of"
  },
  {
    "question": "zonde",
    "options": [
      "pity (it's a pity)",
      "stroller",
      "bed(stead)",
      "already"
    ],
    "answer": "pity (it's a pity)"
  },
  {
    "question": "laatst",
    "options": [
      "the other day",
      "characteristic",
      "to keep",
      "to add"
    ],
    "answer": "the other day"
  },
  {
    "question": "aantal",
    "options": [
      "several",
      "to cancel",
      "doctor",
      "growth"
    ],
    "answer": "several"
  },
  {
    "question": "afzeggen",
    "options": [
      "to cancel",
      "unexpectedly",
      "nurse",
      "vaccination"
    ],
    "answer": "to cancel"
  },
  {
    "question": "bespreken",
    "options": [
      "to discuss",
      "to test",
      "child health centre",
      "letter"
    ],
    "answer": "to discuss"
  },
  {
    "question": "bijwerking",
    "options": [
      "side effect",
      "growth",
      "to inform",
      "measles"
    ],
    "answer": "side effect"
  },
  {
    "question": "de arts",
    "options": [
      "doctor",
      "rubella",
      "business day",
      "nutrition"
    ],
    "answer": "doctor"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bof",
    "options": [
      "mumps",
      "pregnancy",
      "extensive",
      "to cancel"
    ],
    "answer": "mumps"
  },
  {
    "question": "de brief",
    "options": [
      "letter",
      "unexpectedly",
      "doctor",
      "to discuss"
    ],
    "answer": "letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de groei",
    "options": [
      "growth",
      "to test",
      "nurse",
      "vaccination"
    ],
    "answer": "growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "de jeugd",
    "options": [
      "young people",
      "to inform",
      "child health centre",
      "side effect"
    ],
    "answer": "young people"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vaccinatie",
    "options": [
      "vaccination",
      "mumps",
      "growth",
      "business day"
    ],
    "answer": "vaccination"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verhoging",
    "options": [
      "elevation",
      "to cancel",
      "letter",
      "unexpectedly"
    ],
    "answer": "elevation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verpleegkundige",
    "options": [
      "nurse",
      "doctor",
      "to discuss",
      "disease"
    ],
    "answer": "nurse"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voeding",
    "options": [
      "nutrition",
      "to inform",
      "to test",
      "growth"
    ],
    "answer": "nutrition"
  },
  {
    "question": "de werkdag",
    "options": [
      "business day",
      "mumps",
      "child health centre",
      "pregnancy"
    ],
    "answer": "business day"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ziekte",
    "options": [
      "disease",
      "to cancel",
      "rubella",
      "to discuss"
    ],
    "answer": "disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zwangerschap",
    "options": [
      "pregnancy",
      "doctor",
      "to test",
      "nutrition"
    ],
    "answer": "pregnancy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het consultatiebureau",
    "options": [
      "child health centre",
      "growth",
      "to inform",
      "letter"
    ],
    "answer": "child health centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gehoor",
    "options": [
      "hearing",
      "nurse",
      "side effect",
      "to cancel"
    ],
    "answer": "hearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "het recht",
    "options": [
      "right",
      "unexpectedly",
      "to test",
      "to discuss"
    ],
    "answer": "right"
  },
  {
    "question": "informeren",
    "options": [
      "to inform",
      "pregnancy",
      "business day",
      "mumps"
    ],
    "answer": "to inform"
  },
  {
    "question": "mazelen",
    "options": [
      "measles",
      "letter",
      "doctor",
      "growth"
    ],
    "answer": "measles"
  },
  {
    "question": "onverwacht",
    "options": [
      "unexpectedly",
      "nutrition",
      "to cancel",
      "disease"
    ],
    "answer": "unexpectedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "rodehond",
    "options": [
      "rubella",
      "to discuss",
      "nurse",
      "business day"
    ],
    "answer": "rubella"
  },
  {
    "question": "testen",
    "options": [
      "to test",
      "doctor",
      "mumps",
      "letter"
    ],
    "answer": "to test"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitgebreid",
    "options": [
      "extensive",
      "side effect",
      "to inform",
      "growth"
    ],
    "answer": "extensive"
  },
  {
    "question": "bereikbaar",
    "options": [
      "accessible",
      "pregnancy",
      "child health centre",
      "to cancel"
    ],
    "answer": "accessible"
  },
  {
    "question": "brengen",
    "options": [
      "to bring",
      "to hug",
      "to rub / to spread",
      "to cut"
    ],
    "answer": "to bring"
  },
  {
    "question": "dankbaar",
    "options": [
      "grateful",
      "beautiful",
      "love (closing phrase)",
      "habit"
    ],
    "answer": "grateful"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bek",
    "options": [
      "beak",
      "front yard",
      "bird",
      "stork"
    ],
    "answer": "beak"
  },
  {
    "question": "de beschuit",
    "options": [
      "Dutch rusk",
      "bird",
      "doll",
      "cloth"
    ],
    "answer": "Dutch rusk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de doek",
    "options": [
      "cloth",
      "kernel",
      "wooden",
      "habit"
    ],
    "answer": "cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "de felicitatie",
    "options": [
      "congratulation(s)",
      "habit",
      "luck",
      "mail"
    ],
    "answer": "congratulation(s)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gewoonte",
    "options": [
      "habit",
      "bird",
      "visitors",
      "birth announcement card"
    ],
    "answer": "habit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kennis",
    "options": [
      "acquaintance",
      "habit",
      "pink",
      "bird"
    ],
    "answer": "acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kleertjes",
    "options": [
      "(baby) clothes",
      "luck",
      "bird",
      "to bring"
    ],
    "answer": "(baby) clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "de korrel",
    "options": [
      "kernel",
      "front yard",
      "to cut",
      "love (closing phrase)"
    ],
    "answer": "kernel"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ooievaar",
    "options": [
      "stork",
      "congratulation(s)",
      "to bring",
      "habit"
    ],
    "answer": "stork"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pop",
    "options": [
      "doll",
      "grateful",
      "bird",
      "to hug"
    ],
    "answer": "doll"
  },
  {
    "question": "de post",
    "options": [
      "mail",
      "bird",
      "habit",
      "to cut"
    ],
    "answer": "mail"
  },
  {
    "question": "de visite",
    "options": [
      "visitors",
      "to bring",
      "kernel",
      "habit"
    ],
    "answer": "visitors"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vogel",
    "options": [
      "bird",
      "habit",
      "to hug",
      "pink"
    ],
    "answer": "bird"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voortuin",
    "options": [
      "front yard",
      "luck",
      "habit",
      "cloth"
    ],
    "answer": "front yard"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geboortekaartje",
    "options": [
      "birth announcement card",
      "congratulation(s)",
      "habit",
      "to cut"
    ],
    "answer": "birth announcement card"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geluk",
    "options": [
      "luck",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "pink"
    ],
    "answer": "luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "houten",
    "options": [
      "wooden",
      "to rub / to spread",
      "habit",
      "grateful"
    ],
    "answer": "wooden"
  },
  {
    "question": "knippen",
    "options": [
      "to cut",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "bird"
    ],
    "answer": "to cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "knuffelen",
    "options": [
      "to hug",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "pink"
    ],
    "answer": "to hug"
  },
  {
    "question": "liefs",
    "options": [
      "love (closing phrase)",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "bird"
    ],
    "answer": "love (closing phrase)"
  },
  {
    "question": "prachtig",
    "options": [
      "beautiful",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "to cut"
    ],
    "answer": "beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "roze",
    "options": [
      "pink",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "to rub / to spread"
    ],
    "answer": "pink"
  },
  {
    "question": "smeren",
    "options": [
      "to rub / to spread",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "grateful"
    ],
    "answer": "to rub / to spread"
  },
  {
    "question": "wensen",
    "options": [
      "to wish",
      "habit",
      "to bring",
      "bird"
    ],
    "answer": "to wish"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoals",
    "options": [
      "such as",
      "to bring",
      "habit",
      "beautiful"
    ],
    "answer": "such as"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanwezig",
    "options": [
      "present",
      "to scream",
      "shortly",
      "registration"
    ],
    "answer": "present"
  },
  {
    "question": "brullen",
    "options": [
      "to scream",
      "childbirth",
      "person",
      "toe"
    ],
    "answer": "to scream"
  },
  {
    "question": "dadelijk",
    "options": [
      "shortly",
      "grandson",
      "once again",
      "hospital"
    ],
    "answer": "shortly"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aangifte",
    "options": [
      "registration",
      "birth",
      "tall",
      "proof of identity"
    ],
    "answer": "registration"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bevalling",
    "options": [
      "childbirth",
      "hospital",
      "thousand",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "childbirth"
  },
  {
    "question": "de centimeter",
    "options": [
      "centimetre",
      "relieved",
      "awful",
      "to name"
    ],
    "answer": "centimetre"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geboorte",
    "options": [
      "birth",
      "once again",
      "extremely tired",
      "international"
    ],
    "answer": "birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kleinzoon",
    "options": [
      "grandson",
      "tall",
      "proof of identity",
      "to scream"
    ],
    "answer": "grandson"
  },
  {
    "question": "de persoon",
    "options": [
      "person",
      "registration",
      "traditional",
      "childbirth"
    ],
    "answer": "person"
  },
  {
    "question": "de teen",
    "options": [
      "toe",
      "to send",
      "present",
      "hospital"
    ],
    "answer": "toe"
  },
  {
    "question": "doodmoe",
    "options": [
      "extremely tired",
      "thousand",
      "shortly",
      "hospital"
    ],
    "answer": "extremely tired"
  },
  {
    "question": "duizend",
    "options": [
      "thousand",
      "to scream",
      "childbirth",
      "person"
    ],
    "answer": "thousand"
  },
  {
    "question": "eerste",
    "options": [
      "first",
      "awful",
      "tall",
      "grandson"
    ],
    "answer": "first"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bezoekuur",
    "options": [
      "visiting hours",
      "relieved",
      "international",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "visiting hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "het legitimatiebewijs",
    "options": [
      "proof of identity",
      "shortly",
      "once again",
      "hospital"
    ],
    "answer": "proof of identity"
  },
  {
    "question": "het totaal",
    "options": [
      "total",
      "childbirth",
      "to scream",
      "tall"
    ],
    "answer": "total"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ziekenhuis",
    "options": [
      "hospital",
      "to name",
      "present",
      "registration"
    ],
    "answer": "hospital"
  },
  {
    "question": "internationaal",
    "options": [
      "international",
      "person",
      "to send",
      "extremely tired"
    ],
    "answer": "international"
  },
  {
    "question": "lang",
    "options": [
      "tall",
      "awful",
      "first",
      "to scream"
    ],
    "answer": "tall"
  },
  {
    "question": "nogmaals",
    "options": [
      "once again",
      "registration",
      "childbirth",
      "grandson"
    ],
    "answer": "once again"
  },
  {
    "question": "opgelucht",
    "options": [
      "relieved",
      "shortly",
      "person",
      "hospital"
    ],
    "answer": "relieved"
  },
  {
    "question": "opsturen",
    "options": [
      "to send",
      "childbirth",
      "proof of identity",
      "tall"
    ],
    "answer": "to send"
  },
  {
    "question": "traditioneel",
    "options": [
      "traditional",
      "to scream",
      "grandson",
      "visiting hours"
    ],
    "answer": "traditional"
  },
  {
    "question": "naar",
    "options": [
      "awful",
      "birth",
      "registration",
      "present"
    ],
    "answer": "awful"
  },
  {
    "question": "noemen",
    "options": [
      "to name",
      "to send",
      "person",
      "once again"
    ],
    "answer": "to name"
  },
  {
    "question": "allang",
    "options": [
      "already a long time ago",
      "curl",
      "nose",
      "cigarette"
    ],
    "answer": "already a long time ago"
  },
  {
    "question": "de krul",
    "options": [
      "curl",
      "already a long time ago",
      "nose",
      "cigarette"
    ],
    "answer": "curl"
  },
  {
    "question": "de neus",
    "options": [
      "nose",
      "curl",
      "already a long time ago",
      "cigarette"
    ],
    "answer": "nose"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sigaret",
    "options": [
      "cigarette",
      "nose",
      "curl",
      "already a long time ago"
    ],
    "answer": "cigarette"
  },
  {
    "question": "dezelfde",
    "options": [
      "the same",
      "hot-tempered",
      "enormously",
      "patient"
    ],
    "answer": "the same"
  },
  {
    "question": "driftig",
    "options": [
      "hot-tempered",
      "the same",
      "enormously",
      "patient"
    ],
    "answer": "hot-tempered"
  },
  {
    "question": "enorm",
    "options": [
      "enormously",
      "patient",
      "hot-tempered",
      "the same"
    ],
    "answer": "enormously"
  },
  {
    "question": "geduldig",
    "options": [
      "patient",
      "hot-tempered",
      "enormously",
      "the same"
    ],
    "answer": "patient"
  },
  {
    "question": "het grapje",
    "options": [
      "joke",
      "character",
      "jealous",
      "to chat"
    ],
    "answer": "joke"
  },
  {
    "question": "het karakter",
    "options": [
      "character",
      "joke",
      "jealous",
      "to chat"
    ],
    "answer": "character"
  },
  {
    "question": "jaloers",
    "options": [
      "jealous",
      "to chat",
      "joke",
      "character"
    ],
    "answer": "jealous"
  },
  {
    "question": "kletsen",
    "options": [
      "to chat",
      "joke",
      "character",
      "jealous"
    ],
    "answer": "to chat"
  },
  {
    "question": "lijken op",
    "options": [
      "to resemble",
      "just as …. as",
      "impatient",
      "straight"
    ],
    "answer": "to resemble"
  },
  {
    "question": "net zo …. als",
    "options": [
      "just as …. as",
      "to resemble",
      "impatient",
      "straight"
    ],
    "answer": "just as …. as"
  },
  {
    "question": "ongeduldig",
    "options": [
      "impatient",
      "just as …. as",
      "to resemble",
      "straight"
    ],
    "answer": "impatient"
  },
  {
    "question": "recht",
    "options": [
      "straight",
      "impatient",
      "just as …. as",
      "to resemble"
    ],
    "answer": "straight"
  },
  {
    "question": "sociaal",
    "options": [
      "social",
      "to die",
      "sturdy (looking)",
      "out of tune"
    ],
    "answer": "social"
  },
  {
    "question": "sterven",
    "options": [
      "to die",
      "social",
      "sturdy (looking)",
      "out of tune"
    ],
    "answer": "to die"
  },
  {
    "question": "stoer",
    "options": [
      "sturdy (looking)",
      "to die",
      "social",
      "out of tune"
    ],
    "answer": "sturdy (looking)"
  },
  {
    "question": "vals",
    "options": [
      "out of tune",
      "sturdy (looking)",
      "to die",
      "social"
    ],
    "answer": "out of tune"
  },
  {
    "question": "vrolijk",
    "options": [
      "cheerful",
      "to walk",
      "gentle",
      "to remember"
    ],
    "answer": "cheerful"
  },
  {
    "question": "wandelen",
    "options": [
      "to walk",
      "cheerful",
      "gentle",
      "to remember"
    ],
    "answer": "to walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "zacht",
    "options": [
      "gentle",
      "to walk",
      "cheerful",
      "to remember"
    ],
    "answer": "gentle"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich herinneren",
    "options": [
      "to remember",
      "gentle",
      "to walk",
      "cheerful"
    ],
    "answer": "to remember"
  },
  {
    "question": "zingen",
    "options": [
      "to sing",
      "such",
      "appearance",
      "to chat"
    ],
    "answer": "to sing"
  },
  {
    "question": "zulk",
    "options": [
      "such",
      "to sing",
      "appearance",
      "to chat"
    ],
    "answer": "such"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uiterlijk",
    "options": [
      "appearance",
      "such",
      "to sing",
      "to chat"
    ],
    "answer": "appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bloem",
    "options": [
      "flower",
      "wedding",
      "photo",
      "guest"
    ],
    "answer": "flower"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bruiloft",
    "options": [
      "wedding",
      "photographer",
      "hairdresser",
      "ring"
    ],
    "answer": "wedding"
  },
  {
    "question": "de foto",
    "options": [
      "photo",
      "hotel",
      "bouquet",
      "grandpa"
    ],
    "answer": "photo"
  },
  {
    "question": "de fotograaf",
    "options": [
      "photographer",
      "city hall",
      "bouquet",
      "flower"
    ],
    "answer": "photographer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gast",
    "options": [
      "guest",
      "grandma",
      "space",
      "men's suit"
    ],
    "answer": "guest"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huwelijksreis",
    "options": [
      "honeymoon",
      "hairdresser",
      "to pick out",
      "modern"
    ],
    "answer": "honeymoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kapper",
    "options": [
      "hairdresser",
      "to forget",
      "bouquet",
      "ring"
    ],
    "answer": "hairdresser"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oma",
    "options": [
      "Grandma",
      "exciting",
      "wedding dress",
      "to expect"
    ],
    "answer": "Grandma"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opa",
    "options": [
      "Grandpa",
      "to take place",
      "flower",
      "mailbox"
    ],
    "answer": "Grandpa"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ring",
    "options": [
      "ring",
      "photo",
      "to pick up",
      "bouquet"
    ],
    "answer": "ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ruimte",
    "options": [
      "space",
      "hotel",
      "men's suit",
      "modern"
    ],
    "answer": "space"
  },
  {
    "question": "de trouwjurk",
    "options": [
      "wedding dress",
      "grandma",
      "to expect",
      "to forget"
    ],
    "answer": "wedding dress"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorgaan",
    "options": [
      "to take place",
      "exciting",
      "hairdresser",
      "city hall"
    ],
    "answer": "to take place"
  },
  {
    "question": "het boeket",
    "options": [
      "bouquet",
      "to pick up",
      "flower",
      "to pick out"
    ],
    "answer": "bouquet"
  },
  {
    "question": "het hotel",
    "options": [
      "hotel",
      "wedding",
      "photo",
      "modern"
    ],
    "answer": "hotel"
  },
  {
    "question": "het pak",
    "options": [
      "men's suit",
      "honeymoon",
      "grandpa",
      "to forget"
    ],
    "answer": "men's suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "het stadhuis",
    "options": [
      "city hall",
      "to expect",
      "guest",
      "mailbox"
    ],
    "answer": "city hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "modern",
    "options": [
      "modern",
      "bouquet",
      "grandma",
      "to take place"
    ],
    "answer": "modern"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitzoeken",
    "options": [
      "to pick (out)",
      "exciting",
      "flower",
      "wedding dress"
    ],
    "answer": "to pick (out)"
  },
  {
    "question": "vergeten",
    "options": [
      "to forget",
      "photographer",
      "hairdresser",
      "honeymoon"
    ],
    "answer": "to forget"
  },
  {
    "question": "verwachten",
    "options": [
      "to expect",
      "wedding",
      "photo",
      "space"
    ],
    "answer": "to expect"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bus",
    "options": [
      "(mail)box",
      "to pick up",
      "men's suit",
      "city hall"
    ],
    "answer": "(mail)box"
  },
  {
    "question": "ophalen",
    "options": [
      "to pick up",
      "exciting",
      "bouquet",
      "guest"
    ],
    "answer": "to pick up"
  },
  {
    "question": "spannend",
    "options": [
      "exciting",
      "hotel",
      "grandpa",
      "to forget"
    ],
    "answer": "exciting"
  },
  {
    "question": "adopteren",
    "options": [
      "to adopt",
      "to change",
      "to divorce",
      "to live together"
    ],
    "answer": "to adopt"
  },
  {
    "question": "automatisch",
    "options": [
      "obvious",
      "automatically",
      "unmarried",
      "love"
    ],
    "answer": "automatically"
  },
  {
    "question": "bepalen",
    "options": [
      "to determine",
      "to exist",
      "average",
      "care"
    ],
    "answer": "to determine"
  },
  {
    "question": "bestaan",
    "options": [
      "to exist",
      "to change",
      "one",
      "grandparent"
    ],
    "answer": "to exist"
  },
  {
    "question": "bovendien",
    "options": [
      "moreover",
      "average",
      "partner",
      "partly"
    ],
    "answer": "moreover"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ene",
    "options": [
      "one",
      "love",
      "law",
      "to adopt"
    ],
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "question": "de grootouder",
    "options": [
      "grandparent",
      "care",
      "to live together",
      "unmarried"
    ],
    "answer": "grandparent"
  },
  {
    "question": "de liefde",
    "options": [
      "love",
      "to determine",
      "to divorce",
      "average"
    ],
    "answer": "love"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opvoeding",
    "options": [
      "upbringing",
      "moreover",
      "to exist",
      "partner"
    ],
    "answer": "upbringing"
  },
  {
    "question": "de partner",
    "options": [
      "partner",
      "marriage",
      "to change",
      "obvious"
    ],
    "answer": "partner"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wet",
    "options": [
      "law",
      "to adopt",
      "care",
      "automatically"
    ],
    "answer": "law"
  },
  {
    "question": "deels",
    "options": [
      "partly",
      "love",
      "to divorce",
      "grandparent"
    ],
    "answer": "partly"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huwelijk",
    "options": [
      "marriage",
      "to determine",
      "one",
      "average"
    ],
    "answer": "marriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "ongetrouwd",
    "options": [
      "unmarried",
      "to live together",
      "law",
      "to adopt"
    ],
    "answer": "unmarried"
  },
  {
    "question": "samenwonen",
    "options": [
      "to live together",
      "to divorce",
      "to determine",
      "care"
    ],
    "answer": "to live together"
  },
  {
    "question": "scheiden",
    "options": [
      "to divorce",
      "moreover",
      "automatically",
      "love"
    ],
    "answer": "to divorce"
  },
  {
    "question": "steeds",
    "options": [
      "increasingly",
      "partly",
      "law",
      "grandparent"
    ],
    "answer": "increasingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "tegenwoordig",
    "options": [
      "nowadays",
      "partner",
      "to adopt",
      "to change"
    ],
    "answer": "nowadays"
  },
  {
    "question": "vanzelfsprekend",
    "options": [
      "obvious",
      "to divorce",
      "upbringing",
      "one"
    ],
    "answer": "obvious"
  },
  {
    "question": "veranderen",
    "options": [
      "to change",
      "average",
      "to live together",
      "love"
    ],
    "answer": "to change"
  },
  {
    "question": "vroeger",
    "options": [
      "in the past",
      "care",
      "unmarried",
      "moreover"
    ],
    "answer": "in the past"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorg",
    "options": [
      "care",
      "automatically",
      "to adopt",
      "to determine"
    ],
    "answer": "care"
  },
  {
    "question": "gemiddeld",
    "options": [
      "average",
      "partner",
      "to live together",
      "law"
    ],
    "answer": "average"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanhebben",
    "options": [
      "to wear",
      "to bake",
      "to complain",
      "to skype"
    ],
    "answer": "to wear"
  },
  {
    "question": "afschuwelijk",
    "options": [
      "terrible",
      "special",
      "funny",
      "lousy"
    ],
    "answer": "terrible"
  },
  {
    "question": "bakken",
    "options": [
      "to bake",
      "to wear",
      "to crack",
      "to complain"
    ],
    "answer": "to bake"
  },
  {
    "question": "bijzonder",
    "options": [
      "special",
      "terrible",
      "lousy",
      "funny"
    ],
    "answer": "special"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bal",
    "options": [
      "ball",
      "movie",
      "foot",
      "voice"
    ],
    "answer": "ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "de film",
    "options": [
      "movie",
      "meatball",
      "stripe",
      "relationship"
    ],
    "answer": "movie"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gehaktbal",
    "options": [
      "meatball",
      "kiss (small)",
      "stripe",
      "climate"
    ],
    "answer": "meatball"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kus",
    "options": [
      "kiss (small)",
      "foot",
      "voice",
      "stripe"
    ],
    "answer": "kiss (small)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de relatie",
    "options": [
      "relationship",
      "climate",
      "special",
      "foot"
    ],
    "answer": "relationship"
  },
  {
    "question": "de smaak",
    "options": [
      "taste",
      "voice",
      "movie",
      "zero"
    ],
    "answer": "taste"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stem",
    "options": [
      "voice",
      "kiss (small)",
      "funny",
      "terrible"
    ],
    "answer": "voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "de streep",
    "options": [
      "stripe",
      "movie",
      "foot",
      "relationship"
    ],
    "answer": "stripe"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voet",
    "options": [
      "foot",
      "special",
      "climate",
      "kiss (small)"
    ],
    "answer": "foot"
  },
  {
    "question": "grappig",
    "options": [
      "funny",
      "terrible",
      "how sad",
      "special"
    ],
    "answer": "funny"
  },
  {
    "question": "het klimaat",
    "options": [
      "climate",
      "zero",
      "relationship",
      "foot"
    ],
    "answer": "climate"
  },
  {
    "question": "hip",
    "options": [
      "hip (trendy)",
      "terrible",
      "special",
      "to crack"
    ],
    "answer": "hip (trendy)"
  },
  {
    "question": "klagen",
    "options": [
      "to complain",
      "to bake",
      "to wear",
      "to skype"
    ],
    "answer": "to complain"
  },
  {
    "question": "kraken",
    "options": [
      "to crack",
      "to complain",
      "to bake",
      "to skype"
    ],
    "answer": "to crack"
  },
  {
    "question": "nul",
    "options": [
      "zero",
      "terrible",
      "special",
      "foot"
    ],
    "answer": "zero"
  },
  {
    "question": "oei",
    "options": [
      "oops",
      "special",
      "how sad",
      "funny"
    ],
    "answer": "oops"
  },
  {
    "question": "omdat",
    "options": [
      "because",
      "to bake",
      "to crack",
      "terrible"
    ],
    "answer": "because"
  },
  {
    "question": "rot",
    "options": [
      "lousy",
      "special",
      "terrible",
      "funny"
    ],
    "answer": "lousy"
  },
  {
    "question": "skypen",
    "options": [
      "to skype",
      "to complain",
      "to bake",
      "to wear"
    ],
    "answer": "to skype"
  },
  {
    "question": "zielig",
    "options": [
      "how sad",
      "funny",
      "special",
      "terrible"
    ],
    "answer": "how sad"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zweden",
    "options": [
      "Sweden",
      "foot",
      "kiss (small)",
      "movie"
    ],
    "answer": "Sweden"
  },
  {
    "question": "checken",
    "options": [
      "to check",
      "warranty",
      "towel",
      "mechanic"
    ],
    "answer": "to check"
  },
  {
    "question": "de garantie",
    "options": [
      "warranty",
      "to check",
      "solution",
      "pizza"
    ],
    "answer": "warranty"
  },
  {
    "question": "de handdoek",
    "options": [
      "towel",
      "mechanic",
      "initial (letter)",
      "defective"
    ],
    "answer": "towel"
  },
  {
    "question": "de monteur",
    "options": [
      "mechanic",
      "soaking wet",
      "to work (to succeed)",
      "broken"
    ],
    "answer": "mechanic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oplossing",
    "options": [
      "solution",
      "odd",
      "to try",
      "monitor"
    ],
    "answer": "solution"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pizza",
    "options": [
      "pizza",
      "to respond",
      "strange",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "pizza"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voorletter",
    "options": [
      "initial (letter)",
      "again",
      "programme",
      "underwear"
    ],
    "answer": "initial (letter)"
  },
  {
    "question": "defect",
    "options": [
      "defective",
      "broken",
      "odd",
      "to try"
    ],
    "answer": "defective"
  },
  {
    "question": "het beeldscherm",
    "options": [
      "monitor",
      "soaking wet",
      "to check",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "monitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "het laken",
    "options": [
      "sheet",
      "solution",
      "to work (to succeed)",
      "to respond"
    ],
    "answer": "sheet"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ondergoed",
    "options": [
      "underwear",
      "again",
      "strange",
      "broken"
    ],
    "answer": "underwear"
  },
  {
    "question": "kletsnat",
    "options": [
      "soaking wet",
      "to try",
      "mechanic",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "soaking wet"
  },
  {
    "question": "lukken",
    "options": [
      "to work (to succeed)",
      "to check",
      "odd",
      "warranty"
    ],
    "answer": "to work (to succeed)"
  },
  {
    "question": "meevallen",
    "options": [
      "to turn out better than expected",
      "broken",
      "monitor",
      "pizza"
    ],
    "answer": "to turn out better than expected"
  },
  {
    "question": "opeens",
    "options": [
      "suddenly",
      "underwear",
      "mechanic",
      "initial (letter)"
    ],
    "answer": "suddenly"
  },
  {
    "question": "opnieuw",
    "options": [
      "again",
      "to respond",
      "solution",
      "odd"
    ],
    "answer": "again"
  },
  {
    "question": "proberen",
    "options": [
      "to try",
      "soaking wet",
      "pizza",
      "to check"
    ],
    "answer": "to try"
  },
  {
    "question": "raar",
    "options": [
      "odd",
      "warranty",
      "monitor",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "odd"
  },
  {
    "question": "reageren",
    "options": [
      "to respond",
      "broken",
      "initial (letter)",
      "to turn out better than expected"
    ],
    "answer": "to respond"
  },
  {
    "question": "vanmorgen",
    "options": [
      "this morning",
      "defective",
      "mechanic",
      "solution"
    ],
    "answer": "this morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "verzenden",
    "options": [
      "to send",
      "to try",
      "pizza",
      "soaking wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to send"
  },
  {
    "question": "vreemd",
    "options": [
      "strange",
      "monitor",
      "warranty",
      "to respond"
    ],
    "answer": "strange"
  },
  {
    "question": "het programma",
    "options": [
      "programme",
      "odd",
      "underwear",
      "to check"
    ],
    "answer": "programme"
  },
  {
    "question": "stuk",
    "options": [
      "broken",
      "to work (to succeed)",
      "initial (letter)",
      "pizza"
    ],
    "answer": "broken"
  },
  {
    "question": "besparen",
    "options": [
      "to save",
      "shower",
      "hallway",
      "degree"
    ],
    "answer": "to save"
  },
  {
    "question": "de douche",
    "options": [
      "shower",
      "microwave",
      "sock",
      "laundry"
    ],
    "answer": "shower"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gang",
    "options": [
      "hallway",
      "temperature",
      "heating",
      "wool"
    ],
    "answer": "hallway"
  },
  {
    "question": "de graad",
    "options": [
      "degree",
      "simple",
      "half full",
      "ten euros"
    ],
    "answer": "degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "de magnetron",
    "options": [
      "microwave",
      "toilet",
      "short",
      "woollen"
    ],
    "answer": "microwave"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sok",
    "options": [
      "sock",
      "dirty",
      "sensible",
      "probably"
    ],
    "answer": "sock"
  },
  {
    "question": "de temperatuur",
    "options": [
      "temperature",
      "to fill",
      "to turn off",
      "to switch off"
    ],
    "answer": "temperature"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verwarming",
    "options": [
      "heating",
      "at least",
      "to notice",
      "under"
    ],
    "answer": "heating"
  },
  {
    "question": "de was",
    "options": [
      "laundry",
      "in the winter",
      "to save",
      "simple"
    ],
    "answer": "laundry"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wol",
    "options": [
      "wool",
      "dirty",
      "to fill",
      "short"
    ],
    "answer": "wool"
  },
  {
    "question": "eenvoudig",
    "options": [
      "simple",
      "sensible",
      "dirty",
      "to turn off"
    ],
    "answer": "simple"
  },
  {
    "question": "halfvol",
    "options": [
      "half full",
      "probably",
      "to switch off",
      "hallway"
    ],
    "answer": "half full"
  },
  {
    "question": "het tientje",
    "options": [
      "ten euros",
      "laundry",
      "woollen",
      "to notice"
    ],
    "answer": "ten euros"
  },
  {
    "question": "het toilet",
    "options": [
      "toilet",
      "under",
      "microwave",
      "simple"
    ],
    "answer": "toilet"
  },
  {
    "question": "kort",
    "options": [
      "short",
      "probably",
      "to fill",
      "dirty"
    ],
    "answer": "short"
  },
  {
    "question": "merken",
    "options": [
      "to notice",
      "woollen",
      "heating",
      "sock"
    ],
    "answer": "to notice"
  },
  {
    "question": "minimaal",
    "options": [
      "at least",
      "to switch off",
      "simple",
      "dirty"
    ],
    "answer": "at least"
  },
  {
    "question": "onder",
    "options": [
      "under",
      "laundry",
      "hallway",
      "short"
    ],
    "answer": "under"
  },
  {
    "question": "s winters",
    "options": [
      "in the winter",
      "microwave",
      "probably",
      "to save"
    ],
    "answer": "in the winter"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitdoen",
    "options": [
      "to switch off",
      "dirty",
      "to notice",
      "woollen"
    ],
    "answer": "to switch off"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitzetten",
    "options": [
      "to turn off",
      "sock",
      "to fill",
      "at least"
    ],
    "answer": "to turn off"
  },
  {
    "question": "verstandig",
    "options": [
      "sensible",
      "short",
      "to switch off",
      "in the winter"
    ],
    "answer": "sensible"
  },
  {
    "question": "vuil",
    "options": [
      "dirty",
      "hallway",
      "to save",
      "half full"
    ],
    "answer": "dirty"
  },
  {
    "question": "vullen",
    "options": [
      "to fill",
      "laundry",
      "to turn off",
      "probably"
    ],
    "answer": "to fill"
  },
  {
    "question": "waarschijnlijk",
    "options": [
      "probably",
      "to notice",
      "sock",
      "simple"
    ],
    "answer": "probably"
  },
  {
    "question": "wollen",
    "options": [
      "woollen",
      "heating",
      "to fill",
      "dirty"
    ],
    "answer": "woollen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de elektriciteit",
    "options": [
      "electricity",
      "supplier",
      "meter",
      "bill"
    ],
    "answer": "electricity"
  },
  {
    "question": "de leverancier",
    "options": [
      "supplier",
      "power",
      "heat",
      "plug"
    ],
    "answer": "supplier"
  },
  {
    "question": "de meter",
    "options": [
      "meter",
      "company",
      "future",
      "to dry"
    ],
    "answer": "meter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de meterkast",
    "options": [
      "meter cupboard",
      "windmill",
      "meter reading",
      "rarely"
    ],
    "answer": "meter cupboard"
  },
  {
    "question": "de meterstand",
    "options": [
      "meter reading",
      "immediately",
      "wind",
      "gas"
    ],
    "answer": "meter reading"
  },
  {
    "question": "de molen",
    "options": [
      "mill",
      "to think",
      "plug",
      "automatically"
    ],
    "answer": "mill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rekening",
    "options": [
      "bill",
      "company",
      "term",
      "to wash"
    ],
    "answer": "bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stekker",
    "options": [
      "plug",
      "electricity",
      "solar energy",
      "to supply"
    ],
    "answer": "plug"
  },
  {
    "question": "de storing",
    "options": [
      "outage",
      "heat",
      "rarely",
      "use"
    ],
    "answer": "outage"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stroom",
    "options": [
      "power",
      "electricity",
      "meter",
      "heat"
    ],
    "answer": "power"
  },
  {
    "question": "de termijn",
    "options": [
      "term",
      "company",
      "wind",
      "meter cupboard"
    ],
    "answer": "term"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toekomst",
    "options": [
      "future",
      "plug",
      "heat",
      "electricity"
    ],
    "answer": "future"
  },
  {
    "question": "de warmte",
    "options": [
      "heat",
      "supplier",
      "mill",
      "rarely"
    ],
    "answer": "heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wind",
    "options": [
      "wind",
      "to dry",
      "to wash",
      "company"
    ],
    "answer": "wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "de windmolen",
    "options": [
      "windmill",
      "electricity",
      "heat",
      "power"
    ],
    "answer": "windmill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zonne-energie",
    "options": [
      "solar energy",
      "plug",
      "company",
      "to think"
    ],
    "answer": "solar energy"
  },
  {
    "question": "drogen",
    "options": [
      "to dry",
      "immediately",
      "rarely",
      "to supply"
    ],
    "answer": "to dry"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bedrijf",
    "options": [
      "company",
      "wind",
      "term",
      "use"
    ],
    "answer": "company"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gas",
    "options": [
      "gas",
      "windmill",
      "bill",
      "to wash"
    ],
    "answer": "gas"
  },
  {
    "question": "het type",
    "options": [
      "type (of)",
      "electricity",
      "to think",
      "heat"
    ],
    "answer": "type (of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "leveren",
    "options": [
      "to supply",
      "power",
      "to dry",
      "meter reading"
    ],
    "answer": "to supply"
  },
  {
    "question": "nadenken",
    "options": [
      "to think",
      "plug",
      "electricity",
      "heat"
    ],
    "answer": "to think"
  },
  {
    "question": "onmiddellijk",
    "options": [
      "immediately",
      "wind",
      "company",
      "solar energy"
    ],
    "answer": "immediately"
  },
  {
    "question": "vanzelf",
    "options": [
      "automatically",
      "meter cupboard",
      "bill",
      "to dry"
    ],
    "answer": "automatically"
  },
  {
    "question": "wassen",
    "options": [
      "to wash",
      "future",
      "electricity",
      "to supply"
    ],
    "answer": "to wash"
  },
  {
    "question": "zelden",
    "options": [
      "rarely",
      "power",
      "to dry",
      "solar energy"
    ],
    "answer": "rarely"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gebruik",
    "options": [
      "use",
      "electricity",
      "meter",
      "plug"
    ],
    "answer": "use"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aankoop",
    "options": [
      "purchase",
      "energy",
      "fries",
      "frying pan"
    ],
    "answer": "purchase"
  },
  {
    "question": "de energie",
    "options": [
      "energy",
      "purchase",
      "hair dryer",
      "mixer"
    ],
    "answer": "energy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de friet",
    "options": [
      "fries",
      "freezer",
      "tumble dryer",
      "iron"
    ],
    "answer": "fries"
  },
  {
    "question": "de frituurpan",
    "options": [
      "frying pan",
      "fries",
      "electric kettle",
      "device"
    ],
    "answer": "frying pan"
  },
  {
    "question": "de haardroger",
    "options": [
      "hair dryer",
      "mixer",
      "iron",
      "marketplace"
    ],
    "answer": "hair dryer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mixer",
    "options": [
      "mixer",
      "freezer",
      "device",
      "shaver"
    ],
    "answer": "mixer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vriezer",
    "options": [
      "freezer",
      "tumble dryer",
      "electrical",
      "iron"
    ],
    "answer": "freezer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wasdroger",
    "options": [
      "tumble dryer",
      "fries",
      "shaver",
      "useful"
    ],
    "answer": "tumble dryer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de waterkoker",
    "options": [
      "(electric) kettle",
      "hair dryer",
      "frying pan",
      "device"
    ],
    "answer": "(electric) kettle"
  },
  {
    "question": "elektrisch",
    "options": [
      "electrical",
      "useful",
      "marketplace",
      "beautiful"
    ],
    "answer": "electrical"
  },
  {
    "question": "flauw",
    "options": [
      "not very nice",
      "especially",
      "replace",
      "freeze"
    ],
    "answer": "not very nice"
  },
  {
    "question": "het apparaat",
    "options": [
      "device",
      "shaver",
      "iron",
      "marketplace"
    ],
    "answer": "device"
  },
  {
    "question": "het scheerapparaat",
    "options": [
      "shaver",
      "device",
      "iron",
      "tumble dryer"
    ],
    "answer": "shaver"
  },
  {
    "question": "het strijkijzer",
    "options": [
      "iron",
      "freeze",
      "fries",
      "useful"
    ],
    "answer": "iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "invriezen",
    "options": [
      "to freeze",
      "to iron",
      "to replace",
      "not very nice"
    ],
    "answer": "to freeze"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marktplaats",
    "options": [
      "marketplace",
      "purchase",
      "device",
      "beautiful"
    ],
    "answer": "marketplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "nuttig",
    "options": [
      "useful",
      "beautiful",
      "especially",
      "to replace"
    ],
    "answer": "useful"
  },
  {
    "question": "strijken",
    "options": [
      "to iron",
      "to freeze",
      "not very nice",
      "electrical"
    ],
    "answer": "to iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "vervangen",
    "options": [
      "to replace",
      "to freeze",
      "especially",
      "device"
    ],
    "answer": "to replace"
  },
  {
    "question": "vooral",
    "options": [
      "especially",
      "useful",
      "not very nice",
      "purchase"
    ],
    "answer": "especially"
  },
  {
    "question": "prachtig",
    "options": [
      "beautiful",
      "useful",
      "to iron",
      "fries"
    ],
    "answer": "beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "daarom",
    "options": [
      "that's why",
      "activity",
      "director",
      "parent volunteer"
    ],
    "answer": "that's why"
  },
  {
    "question": "de activiteit",
    "options": [
      "activity",
      "carer",
      "effort",
      "helpful"
    ],
    "answer": "activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "de directeur",
    "options": [
      "director",
      "only",
      "proud",
      "to paint"
    ],
    "answer": "director"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hulpouder",
    "options": [
      "parent volunteer",
      "outing",
      "to give (to take along)",
      "card"
    ],
    "answer": "parent volunteer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klassenouder",
    "options": [
      "class parent",
      "great",
      "to organize",
      "farewell (party)"
    ],
    "answer": "class parent"
  },
  {
    "question": "de moeite",
    "options": [
      "effort",
      "long lasting",
      "fantastic",
      "with great pleasure"
    ],
    "answer": "effort"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sfeer",
    "options": [
      "atmosphere",
      "incredible",
      "to do carpentry",
      "resident"
    ],
    "answer": "atmosphere"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sportdag",
    "options": [
      "sports day",
      "helpful",
      "to paint",
      "farewell (party)"
    ],
    "answer": "sports day"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verzorger",
    "options": [
      "carer",
      "card",
      "proud",
      "organize"
    ],
    "answer": "carer"
  },
  {
    "question": "dolgraag",
    "options": [
      "with great pleasure",
      "only",
      "great",
      "incredible"
    ],
    "answer": "with great pleasure"
  },
  {
    "question": "enig",
    "options": [
      "only",
      "activity",
      "to paint",
      "to organize"
    ],
    "answer": "only"
  },
  {
    "question": "fantastisch",
    "options": [
      "fantastic",
      "effort",
      "parent volunteer",
      "farewell (party)"
    ],
    "answer": "fantastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "geweldig",
    "options": [
      "great",
      "director",
      "carer",
      "proud"
    ],
    "answer": "great"
  },
  {
    "question": "het afscheid",
    "options": [
      "farewell (party)",
      "incredible",
      "to do carpentry",
      "class parent"
    ],
    "answer": "farewell (party)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uitstapje",
    "options": [
      "outing",
      "only",
      "helpful",
      "with great pleasure"
    ],
    "answer": "outing"
  },
  {
    "question": "langdurig",
    "options": [
      "long lasting",
      "to give (to take along)",
      "activity",
      "proud"
    ],
    "answer": "long lasting"
  },
  {
    "question": "meegeven",
    "options": [
      "to give (to take along)",
      "director",
      "great",
      "to paint"
    ],
    "answer": "to give (to take along)"
  },
  {
    "question": "organiseren",
    "options": [
      "to organize",
      "fantastic",
      "carer",
      "only"
    ],
    "answer": "to organize"
  },
  {
    "question": "timmeren",
    "options": [
      "(to do) carpentry",
      "helpful",
      "parent volunteer",
      "with great pleasure"
    ],
    "answer": "(to do) carpentry"
  },
  {
    "question": "trots",
    "options": [
      "proud",
      "incredible",
      "outing",
      "farewell (party)"
    ],
    "answer": "proud"
  },
  {
    "question": "verven",
    "options": [
      "to paint",
      "activity",
      "director",
      "carer"
    ],
    "answer": "to paint"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kaartje",
    "options": [
      "card",
      "fantastic",
      "class parent",
      "great"
    ],
    "answer": "card"
  },
  {
    "question": "nuttig",
    "options": [
      "helpful",
      "only",
      "with great pleasure",
      "to give (to take along)"
    ],
    "answer": "helpful"
  },
  {
    "question": "ongelooflijk",
    "options": [
      "incredible",
      "proud",
      "farewell (party)",
      "activity"
    ],
    "answer": "incredible"
  },
  {
    "question": "afhalen",
    "options": [
      "to pick up",
      "to read",
      "care",
      "cost"
    ],
    "answer": "to pick up"
  },
  {
    "question": "de administratie",
    "options": [
      "administrative department",
      "guide",
      "internship",
      "treat"
    ],
    "answer": "administrative department"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gids",
    "options": [
      "guide",
      "intern",
      "newsletter",
      "pupil"
    ],
    "answer": "guide"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kleuter",
    "options": [
      "preschool child",
      "teacher",
      "start",
      "school year"
    ],
    "answer": "preschool child"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kosten",
    "options": [
      "cost",
      "care",
      "version",
      "importance"
    ],
    "answer": "cost"
  },
  {
    "question": "de leerkracht",
    "options": [
      "teacher",
      "to sign up",
      "internship",
      "toddler"
    ],
    "answer": "teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "de leerling",
    "options": [
      "pupil",
      "to treat",
      "guide",
      "paper"
    ],
    "answer": "pupil"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nieuwsbrief",
    "options": [
      "newsletter",
      "administrative department",
      "start",
      "intern"
    ],
    "answer": "newsletter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opleiding",
    "options": [
      "education",
      "in between lessons",
      "care",
      "importance"
    ],
    "answer": "education"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opvang",
    "options": [
      "care",
      "to pick up",
      "intern",
      "school year"
    ],
    "answer": "care"
  },
  {
    "question": "de peuter",
    "options": [
      "toddler",
      "pupil",
      "guide",
      "to read"
    ],
    "answer": "toddler"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stage",
    "options": [
      "internship",
      "administrative department",
      "to treat",
      "cost"
    ],
    "answer": "internship"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stagiaire",
    "options": [
      "intern",
      "newsletter",
      "preschool child",
      "to sign up"
    ],
    "answer": "intern"
  },
  {
    "question": "de traktatie",
    "options": [
      "treat",
      "importance",
      "start",
      "education"
    ],
    "answer": "treat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de versie",
    "options": [
      "version",
      "toddler",
      "care",
      "to treat"
    ],
    "answer": "version"
  },
  {
    "question": "het begin",
    "options": [
      "start",
      "intern",
      "administrative department",
      "pupil"
    ],
    "answer": "start"
  },
  {
    "question": "het belang",
    "options": [
      "importance",
      "guide",
      "internship",
      "to sign up"
    ],
    "answer": "importance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het schooljaar",
    "options": [
      "school year",
      "to pick up",
      "newsletter",
      "preschool child"
    ],
    "answer": "school year"
  },
  {
    "question": "papieren",
    "options": [
      "(made of) paper",
      "intern",
      "teacher",
      "to treat"
    ],
    "answer": "(made of) paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "trakteren",
    "options": [
      "to treat",
      "cost",
      "care",
      "to read"
    ],
    "answer": "to treat"
  },
  {
    "question": "tussenschools",
    "options": [
      "in between lessons",
      "internship",
      "school year",
      "toddler"
    ],
    "answer": "in between lessons"
  },
  {
    "question": "voorlezen",
    "options": [
      "to read",
      "guide",
      "importance",
      "intern"
    ],
    "answer": "to read"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich inschrijven",
    "options": [
      "to sign up",
      "start",
      "newsletter",
      "preschool child"
    ],
    "answer": "to sign up"
  },
  {
    "question": "allemaal",
    "options": [
      "all of it",
      "yuck",
      "better",
      "school diary"
    ],
    "answer": "all of it"
  },
  {
    "question": "bah",
    "options": [
      "yuck",
      "hunger",
      "neck",
      "alarm clock"
    ],
    "answer": "yuck"
  },
  {
    "question": "beter",
    "options": [
      "better",
      "honey",
      "dear",
      "to take a shower"
    ],
    "answer": "better"
  },
  {
    "question": "de agenda",
    "options": [
      "school diary",
      "backpack",
      "to hurry up",
      "face"
    ],
    "answer": "school diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "de broodtrommel",
    "options": [
      "lunch box",
      "pencil case",
      "to get up",
      "to feel"
    ],
    "answer": "lunch box"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dorst",
    "options": [
      "thirst",
      "to come back",
      "yuck",
      "neck"
    ],
    "answer": "thirst"
  },
  {
    "question": "de honger",
    "options": [
      "hunger",
      "alarm clock",
      "school diary",
      "better"
    ],
    "answer": "hunger"
  },
  {
    "question": "de honing",
    "options": [
      "honey",
      "backpack",
      "to grab",
      "face"
    ],
    "answer": "honey"
  },
  {
    "question": "de keel",
    "options": [
      "throat",
      "dear",
      "last",
      "to take care of"
    ],
    "answer": "throat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nek",
    "options": [
      "neck",
      "to hurry up",
      "alarm clock",
      "all of it"
    ],
    "answer": "neck"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rugzak",
    "options": [
      "backpack",
      "to get up",
      "pencil case",
      "to feel"
    ],
    "answer": "backpack"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wekker",
    "options": [
      "alarm clock",
      "to come back",
      "to grab",
      "better"
    ],
    "answer": "alarm clock"
  },
  {
    "question": "douchen",
    "options": [
      "to take a shower",
      "yuck",
      "to hurry up",
      "hunger"
    ],
    "answer": "to take a shower"
  },
  {
    "question": "eens",
    "options": [
      "for a moment",
      "school diary",
      "dear",
      "backpack"
    ],
    "answer": "for a moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "het etui",
    "options": [
      "pencil case",
      "to feel",
      "to come back",
      "to get up"
    ],
    "answer": "pencil case"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gezicht",
    "options": [
      "face",
      "yuck",
      "to grab",
      "better"
    ],
    "answer": "face"
  },
  {
    "question": "het haar",
    "options": [
      "hair",
      "to hurry up",
      "hunger",
      "alarm clock"
    ],
    "answer": "hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "opschieten",
    "options": [
      "to hurry up",
      "to take care of",
      "neck",
      "thirst"
    ],
    "answer": "to hurry up"
  },
  {
    "question": "opstaan",
    "options": [
      "to get up",
      "school diary",
      "all of it",
      "honey"
    ],
    "answer": "to get up"
  },
  {
    "question": "pakken",
    "options": [
      "to grab",
      "dear",
      "last",
      "to come back"
    ],
    "answer": "to grab"
  },
  {
    "question": "regelen",
    "options": [
      "to take care of",
      "better",
      "pencil case",
      "face"
    ],
    "answer": "to take care of"
  },
  {
    "question": "schat",
    "options": [
      "dear",
      "backpack",
      "hunger",
      "to get up"
    ],
    "answer": "dear"
  },
  {
    "question": "terugkomen",
    "options": [
      "to come back",
      "throat",
      "to hurry up",
      "yuck"
    ],
    "answer": "to come back"
  },
  {
    "question": "voelen",
    "options": [
      "to feel",
      "alarm clock",
      "honey",
      "last"
    ],
    "answer": "to feel"
  },
  {
    "question": "vorig",
    "options": [
      "last",
      "to take a shower",
      "school diary",
      "yuck"
    ],
    "answer": "last"
  },
  {
    "question": "anders",
    "options": [
      "different",
      "amount",
      "biology",
      "uniform"
    ],
    "answer": "different"
  },
  {
    "question": "bouwen",
    "options": [
      "to build",
      "geography",
      "group",
      "game"
    ],
    "answer": "to build"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aardrijkskunde",
    "options": [
      "geography",
      "biology",
      "history",
      "subject"
    ],
    "answer": "geography"
  },
  {
    "question": "de biologie",
    "options": [
      "biology",
      "performance",
      "religion",
      "mandatory"
    ],
    "answer": "biology"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geschiedenis",
    "options": [
      "history",
      "male teacher",
      "school trip",
      "to run"
    ],
    "answer": "history"
  },
  {
    "question": "de groep",
    "options": [
      "group",
      "to do crafts",
      "thing",
      "development"
    ],
    "answer": "group"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gymnastiek",
    "options": [
      "physical education",
      "regularly",
      "different",
      "to sign"
    ],
    "answer": "physical education"
  },
  {
    "question": "de meester",
    "options": [
      "male teacher",
      "to come by",
      "uniform",
      "history"
    ],
    "answer": "male teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ontwikkeling",
    "options": [
      "development",
      "school trip",
      "to build",
      "biology"
    ],
    "answer": "development"
  },
  {
    "question": "de prestatie",
    "options": [
      "performance",
      "different",
      "amount",
      "to run"
    ],
    "answer": "performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de religie",
    "options": [
      "religion",
      "thing",
      "geography",
      "game"
    ],
    "answer": "religion"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bedrag",
    "options": [
      "amount",
      "biology",
      "to do crafts",
      "uniform"
    ],
    "answer": "amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ding",
    "options": [
      "thing",
      "to build",
      "school trip",
      "regularly"
    ],
    "answer": "thing"
  },
  {
    "question": "het rekenen",
    "options": [
      "mathematics",
      "to sign",
      "group",
      "development"
    ],
    "answer": "mathematics"
  },
  {
    "question": "het schoolreisje",
    "options": [
      "school trip",
      "performance",
      "physical education",
      "amount"
    ],
    "answer": "school trip"
  },
  {
    "question": "het spelletje",
    "options": [
      "game",
      "history",
      "to run",
      "biology"
    ],
    "answer": "game"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uniform",
    "options": [
      "uniform",
      "male teacher",
      "religion",
      "thing"
    ],
    "answer": "uniform"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vak",
    "options": [
      "subject",
      "amount",
      "different",
      "to build"
    ],
    "answer": "subject"
  },
  {
    "question": "hetzelfde",
    "options": [
      "the same",
      "development",
      "to come by",
      "to do crafts"
    ],
    "answer": "the same"
  },
  {
    "question": "knutselen",
    "options": [
      "to do crafts",
      "geography",
      "biology",
      "to run"
    ],
    "answer": "to do crafts"
  },
  {
    "question": "regelmatig",
    "options": [
      "regularly",
      "game",
      "uniform",
      "school trip"
    ],
    "answer": "regularly"
  },
  {
    "question": "rennen",
    "options": [
      "to run",
      "amount",
      "biology",
      "male teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to run"
  },
  {
    "question": "tekenen",
    "options": [
      "to sign",
      "performance",
      "different",
      "thing"
    ],
    "answer": "to sign"
  },
  {
    "question": "verplicht",
    "options": [
      "mandatory",
      "history",
      "to build",
      "regularly"
    ],
    "answer": "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "verschillend",
    "options": [
      "different",
      "religion",
      "subject",
      "to come by"
    ],
    "answer": "different"
  },
  {
    "question": "langskomen",
    "options": [
      "to come by",
      "biology",
      "development",
      "game"
    ],
    "answer": "to come by"
  },
  {
    "question": "bederven",
    "options": [
      "to spoil",
      "to mean",
      "to visit",
      "population"
    ],
    "answer": "to spoil"
  },
  {
    "question": "betekenen",
    "options": [
      "to mean",
      "to spoil",
      "to visit",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "to mean"
  },
  {
    "question": "bezoeken",
    "options": [
      "to visit",
      "to mean",
      "to spoil",
      "CD"
    ],
    "answer": "to visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bevolking",
    "options": [
      "population",
      "cake",
      "to spoil",
      "soda"
    ],
    "answer": "population"
  },
  {
    "question": "de cake",
    "options": [
      "cake",
      "population",
      "CD",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "cake"
  },
  {
    "question": "de cd",
    "options": [
      "CD",
      "cake",
      "king",
      "soda"
    ],
    "answer": "CD"
  },
  {
    "question": "de frisdrank",
    "options": [
      "soda",
      "king",
      "queen",
      "gift"
    ],
    "answer": "soda"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koning",
    "options": [
      "king",
      "queen",
      "birthday",
      "glass"
    ],
    "answer": "king"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koningin",
    "options": [
      "queen",
      "king",
      "gift",
      "can"
    ],
    "answer": "queen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verjaardag",
    "options": [
      "birthday",
      "walk",
      "glass",
      "CD"
    ],
    "answer": "birthday"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vrijmarkt",
    "options": [
      "unregulated street market",
      "King’s Day",
      "to congratulate",
      "plastic"
    ],
    "answer": "unregulated street market"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wandeling",
    "options": [
      "walk",
      "gift",
      "can",
      "to interview"
    ],
    "answer": "walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "enzovoort",
    "options": [
      "and so on",
      "King’s Day",
      "strictly",
      "forbidden"
    ],
    "answer": "and so on"
  },
  {
    "question": "extra",
    "options": [
      "extra",
      "plastic",
      "pocket money",
      "to give away"
    ],
    "answer": "extra"
  },
  {
    "question": "feliciteren",
    "options": [
      "to congratulate",
      "to interview",
      "to mean",
      "to spoil"
    ],
    "answer": "to congratulate"
  },
  {
    "question": "glazen",
    "options": [
      "(made of) glass",
      "can",
      "gift",
      "soda"
    ],
    "answer": "(made of) glass"
  },
  {
    "question": "het blikje",
    "options": [
      "can",
      "book",
      "pocket money",
      "glass"
    ],
    "answer": "can"
  },
  {
    "question": "het boek",
    "options": [
      "book",
      "can",
      "cake",
      "glass"
    ],
    "answer": "book"
  },
  {
    "question": "het cadeau",
    "options": [
      "gift",
      "cake",
      "can",
      "glass"
    ],
    "answer": "gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "interviewen",
    "options": [
      "to interview",
      "to give away",
      "to spoil",
      "to mean"
    ],
    "answer": "to interview"
  },
  {
    "question": "Koningsdag",
    "options": [
      "King’s Day",
      "walk",
      "birthday",
      "glass"
    ],
    "answer": "King’s Day"
  },
  {
    "question": "plastic",
    "options": [
      "plastic",
      "pocket money",
      "glass",
      "can"
    ],
    "answer": "plastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "streng",
    "options": [
      "strictly",
      "forbidden",
      "to spoil",
      "to interview"
    ],
    "answer": "strictly"
  },
  {
    "question": "verboden",
    "options": [
      "forbidden",
      "strictly",
      "extra",
      "to mean"
    ],
    "answer": "forbidden"
  },
  {
    "question": "verdienen",
    "options": [
      "to earn",
      "to visit",
      "to give away",
      "to congratulate"
    ],
    "answer": "to earn"
  },
  {
    "question": "vieren",
    "options": [
      "to celebrate",
      "to earn",
      "to mean",
      "to interview"
    ],
    "answer": "to celebrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "weggeven",
    "options": [
      "to give away",
      "to visit",
      "to earn",
      "to interview"
    ],
    "answer": "to give away"
  },
  {
    "question": "het zakgeld",
    "options": [
      "pocket money",
      "can",
      "cake",
      "glass"
    ],
    "answer": "pocket money"
  },
  {
    "question": "afwachten",
    "options": [
      "to wait for",
      "already",
      "boss",
      "uncle"
    ],
    "answer": "to wait for"
  },
  {
    "question": "alvast",
    "options": [
      "already",
      "to propose",
      "female teacher",
      "butchery"
    ],
    "answer": "already"
  },
  {
    "question": "antwoord",
    "options": [
      "answer",
      "permission",
      "row",
      "cheap / favorable"
    ],
    "answer": "answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "april",
    "options": [
      "April",
      "strange / crazy",
      "ticket",
      "schoolyard"
    ],
    "answer": "April"
  },
  {
    "question": "België",
    "options": [
      "Belgium",
      "to throw away",
      "uncle",
      "permission"
    ],
    "answer": "Belgium"
  },
  {
    "question": "de baas",
    "options": [
      "boss",
      "to wait for",
      "female teacher",
      "cheap / favorable"
    ],
    "answer": "boss"
  },
  {
    "question": "de collega",
    "options": [
      "colleague",
      "answer",
      "schoolyard",
      "already"
    ],
    "answer": "colleague"
  },
  {
    "question": "de juf",
    "options": [
      "female teacher",
      "to throw away",
      "thereafter",
      "to propose"
    ],
    "answer": "female teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kantine",
    "options": [
      "canteen",
      "row",
      "strange / crazy",
      "uncle"
    ],
    "answer": "canteen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oom",
    "options": [
      "uncle",
      "cheap / favorable",
      "ticket",
      "to wait for"
    ],
    "answer": "uncle"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rij",
    "options": [
      "row",
      "permission",
      "answer",
      "already"
    ],
    "answer": "row"
  },
  {
    "question": "de slagerij",
    "options": [
      "butchery",
      "female teacher",
      "schoolyard",
      "to throw away"
    ],
    "answer": "butchery"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tante",
    "options": [
      "aunt",
      "to propose",
      "thereafter",
      "cheap / favorable"
    ],
    "answer": "aunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toestemming",
    "options": [
      "permission",
      "strange / crazy",
      "answer",
      "to wait for"
    ],
    "answer": "permission"
  },
  {
    "question": "erna",
    "options": [
      "thereafter",
      "to wait for",
      "to throw away",
      "female teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "thereafter"
  },
  {
    "question": "gek",
    "options": [
      "strange / crazy",
      "uncle",
      "row",
      "cheap / favorable"
    ],
    "answer": "strange / crazy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geduld",
    "options": [
      "patience",
      "ticket",
      "to propose",
      "already"
    ],
    "answer": "patience"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kaartje",
    "options": [
      "ticket",
      "to throw away",
      "female teacher",
      "thereafter"
    ],
    "answer": "ticket"
  },
  {
    "question": "het schoolplein",
    "options": [
      "schoolyard",
      "to wait for",
      "answer",
      "cheap / favorable"
    ],
    "answer": "schoolyard"
  },
  {
    "question": "het Suikerfeest",
    "options": [
      "Sugar Feast",
      "strange / crazy",
      "uncle",
      "already"
    ],
    "answer": "Sugar Feast"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoeven",
    "options": [
      "to have to",
      "permission",
      "butchery",
      "aunt"
    ],
    "answer": "to have to"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoezo",
    "options": [
      "why do you ask?",
      "thereafter",
      "female teacher",
      "ticket"
    ],
    "answer": "why do you ask?"
  },
  {
    "question": "verkeerd",
    "options": [
      "wrong",
      "already",
      "to wait for",
      "uncle"
    ],
    "answer": "wrong"
  },
  {
    "question": "voordelig",
    "options": [
      "cheap / favorable",
      "answer",
      "row",
      "to throw away"
    ],
    "answer": "cheap / favorable"
  },
  {
    "question": "voorstellen",
    "options": [
      "to propose",
      "strange / crazy",
      "ticket",
      "aunt"
    ],
    "answer": "to propose"
  },
  {
    "question": "weggooien",
    "options": [
      "to throw away",
      "permission",
      "female teacher",
      "to wait for"
    ],
    "answer": "to throw away"
  },
  {
    "question": "antwoorden",
    "options": [
      "to answer",
      "mad",
      "baby-sitter",
      "honest"
    ],
    "answer": "to answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "beslist",
    "options": [
      "honest",
      "absolutely",
      "in-laws",
      "difficult"
    ],
    "answer": "absolutely"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bioscoop",
    "options": [
      "cinema",
      "selfish",
      "to lie",
      "family"
    ],
    "answer": "cinema"
  },
  {
    "question": "de familie",
    "options": [
      "different",
      "family",
      "to go out",
      "earlier"
    ],
    "answer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oppas",
    "options": [
      "to stay (over)",
      "baby-sitter",
      "to become",
      "test"
    ],
    "answer": "baby-sitter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schoonouders",
    "options": [
      "honest",
      "in-laws",
      "mad",
      "ago"
    ],
    "answer": "in-laws"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toets",
    "options": [
      "test",
      "to lie",
      "incredibly",
      "baby-sitter"
    ],
    "answer": "test"
  },
  {
    "question": "eerder",
    "options": [
      "earlier",
      "mad",
      "honest",
      "different"
    ],
    "answer": "earlier"
  },
  {
    "question": "eerlijk",
    "options": [
      "honest",
      "to go out",
      "baby-sitter",
      "in-laws"
    ],
    "answer": "honest"
  },
  {
    "question": "egoïstisch",
    "options": [
      "selfish",
      "cinema",
      "to stay (over)",
      "earlier"
    ],
    "answer": "selfish"
  },
  {
    "question": "geleden",
    "options": [
      "ago",
      "to answer",
      "honest",
      "absolutely"
    ],
    "answer": "ago"
  },
  {
    "question": "kwaad",
    "options": [
      "mad",
      "baby-sitter",
      "cinema",
      "different"
    ],
    "answer": "mad"
  },
  {
    "question": "lastig",
    "options": [
      "difficult",
      "honest",
      "to lie",
      "earlier"
    ],
    "answer": "difficult"
  },
  {
    "question": "liegen",
    "options": [
      "to lie",
      "in-laws",
      "selfish",
      "honest"
    ],
    "answer": "to lie"
  },
  {
    "question": "logeren",
    "options": [
      "to stay (over)",
      "to become",
      "honest",
      "earlier"
    ],
    "answer": "to stay (over)"
  },
  {
    "question": "ontzettend",
    "options": [
      "incredibly",
      "mad",
      "to lie",
      "different"
    ],
    "answer": "incredibly"
  },
  {
    "question": "toen",
    "options": [
      "when (past)",
      "test",
      "to answer",
      "earlier"
    ],
    "answer": "when (past)"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitgaan",
    "options": [
      "to go out",
      "to stay (over)",
      "honest",
      "baby-sitter"
    ],
    "answer": "to go out"
  },
  {
    "question": "worden",
    "options": [
      "to become",
      "to lie",
      "mad",
      "cinema"
    ],
    "answer": "to become"
  },
  {
    "question": "anders",
    "options": [
      "different",
      "honest",
      "baby-sitter",
      "earlier"
    ],
    "answer": "different"
  },
  {
    "question": "bewegen",
    "options": [
      "to move",
      "activity",
      "injury",
      "playground"
    ],
    "answer": "to move"
  },
  {
    "question": "de activiteit",
    "options": [
      "activity",
      "to be true for",
      "almost",
      "serious"
    ],
    "answer": "activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "de blessure",
    "options": [
      "injury",
      "gym",
      "to lift",
      "weekend"
    ],
    "answer": "injury"
  },
  {
    "question": "de speeltuin",
    "options": [
      "playground",
      "watch (children)",
      "heavy",
      "finge"
    ],
    "answer": "playground"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sportschool",
    "options": [
      "gym",
      "weekend",
      "to train",
      "serious"
    ],
    "answer": "gym"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vinger",
    "options": [
      "finger",
      "heavy",
      "to swim",
      "playground"
    ],
    "answer": "finger"
  },
  {
    "question": "ernstig",
    "options": [
      "serious",
      "to hope",
      "almost",
      "permanent"
    ],
    "answer": "serious"
  },
  {
    "question": "gelden",
    "options": [
      "to be true for",
      "activity",
      "to lift",
      "gym"
    ],
    "answer": "to be true for"
  },
  {
    "question": "gisteren",
    "options": [
      "yesterday",
      "swimming pool",
      "to train",
      "weekend"
    ],
    "answer": "yesterday"
  },
  {
    "question": "haast",
    "options": [
      "almost",
      "to swim",
      "permanent",
      "to hope"
    ],
    "answer": "almost"
  },
  {
    "question": "het zwembad",
    "options": [
      "swimming pool",
      "playground",
      "to move",
      "injury"
    ],
    "answer": "swimming pool"
  },
  {
    "question": "hopen",
    "options": [
      "to hope",
      "activity",
      "heavy",
      "to swim"
    ],
    "answer": "to hope"
  },
  {
    "question": "leven",
    "options": [
      "to live",
      "to train",
      "permanent",
      "weekend"
    ],
    "answer": "to live"
  },
  {
    "question": "niets",
    "options": [
      "nothing",
      "to lift",
      "heavy",
      "gym"
    ],
    "answer": "nothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "optillen",
    "options": [
      "to lift",
      "to move",
      "playground",
      "serious"
    ],
    "answer": "to lift"
  },
  {
    "question": "sporten",
    "options": [
      "to do sports",
      "injury",
      "almost",
      "permanent"
    ],
    "answer": "to do sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "trainen",
    "options": [
      "to train",
      "heavy",
      "activity",
      "to hope"
    ],
    "answer": "to train"
  },
  {
    "question": "vast",
    "options": [
      "permanent",
      "to be true for",
      "weekend",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "permanent"
  },
  {
    "question": "voorlopig",
    "options": [
      "for the time being",
      "to swim",
      "injury",
      "to lift"
    ],
    "answer": "for the time being"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwemmen",
    "options": [
      "to swim",
      "playground",
      "gym",
      "activity"
    ],
    "answer": "to swim"
  },
  {
    "question": "het weekend",
    "options": [
      "weekend",
      "to live",
      "serious",
      "to train"
    ],
    "answer": "weekend"
  },
  {
    "question": "oppassen",
    "options": [
      "watch (children)",
      "activity",
      "to hope",
      "almost"
    ],
    "answer": "watch (children)"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwaar",
    "options": [
      "heavy",
      "to move",
      "to train",
      "nothing"
    ],
    "answer": "heavy"
  },
  {
    "question": "allebei",
    "options": [
      "both",
      "important",
      "resident",
      "housemate"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "belangrijk",
    "options": [
      "important",
      "both",
      "resident",
      "housemate"
    ],
    "answer": "important"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bewoner",
    "options": [
      "resident",
      "important",
      "both",
      "housemate"
    ],
    "answer": "resident"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisgenoot",
    "options": [
      "housemate",
      "resident",
      "important",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "housemate"
  },
  {
    "question": "de krant",
    "options": [
      "newspaper",
      "resident",
      "housemate",
      "important"
    ],
    "answer": "newspaper"
  },
  {
    "question": "de leeftijd",
    "options": [
      "age",
      "newspaper",
      "resident",
      "housemate"
    ],
    "answer": "age"
  },
  {
    "question": "de omgeving",
    "options": [
      "environment",
      "age",
      "newspaper",
      "resident"
    ],
    "answer": "environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de reactie",
    "options": [
      "response",
      "environment",
      "age",
      "newspaper"
    ],
    "answer": "response"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rest",
    "options": [
      "rest",
      "response",
      "environment",
      "age"
    ],
    "answer": "rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "de slaapkamer",
    "options": [
      "bedroom",
      "rest",
      "response",
      "environment"
    ],
    "answer": "bedroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sport",
    "options": [
      "sport",
      "bedroom",
      "rest",
      "response"
    ],
    "answer": "sport"
  },
  {
    "question": "hen",
    "options": [
      "them",
      "sport",
      "bedroom",
      "rest"
    ],
    "answer": "them"
  },
  {
    "question": "het balkon",
    "options": [
      "balcony",
      "them",
      "sport",
      "bedroom"
    ],
    "answer": "balcony"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gesprek",
    "options": [
      "conversation",
      "balcony",
      "them",
      "sport"
    ],
    "answer": "conversation"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huisdier",
    "options": [
      "pet",
      "conversation",
      "balcony",
      "them"
    ],
    "answer": "pet"
  },
  {
    "question": "het plezier",
    "options": [
      "fun",
      "pet",
      "conversation",
      "balcony"
    ],
    "answer": "fun"
  },
  {
    "question": "het profiel",
    "options": [
      "profile",
      "fun",
      "pet",
      "conversation"
    ],
    "answer": "profile"
  },
  {
    "question": "het team",
    "options": [
      "team",
      "profile",
      "fun",
      "pet"
    ],
    "answer": "team"
  },
  {
    "question": "hun",
    "options": [
      "their",
      "team",
      "profile",
      "fun"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "ideaal",
    "options": [
      "ideal",
      "their",
      "team",
      "profile"
    ],
    "answer": "ideal"
  },
  {
    "question": "roken",
    "options": [
      "to smoke",
      "ideal",
      "their",
      "team"
    ],
    "answer": "to smoke"
  },
  {
    "question": "schoon",
    "options": [
      "clean",
      "to smoke",
      "ideal",
      "their"
    ],
    "answer": "clean"
  },
  {
    "question": "schoonmaken",
    "options": [
      "to clean",
      "clean",
      "to smoke",
      "ideal"
    ],
    "answer": "to clean"
  },
  {
    "question": "zelfs",
    "options": [
      "even",
      "to clean",
      "clean",
      "to smoke"
    ],
    "answer": "even"
  },
  {
    "question": "stellen",
    "options": [
      "to pose",
      "even",
      "to clean",
      "clean"
    ],
    "answer": "to pose"
  },
  {
    "question": "even",
    "options": [
      "equally",
      "to pose",
      "even",
      "to clean"
    ],
    "answer": "equally"
  },
  {
    "question": "een paar",
    "options": [
      "a few",
      "equally",
      "to pose",
      "even"
    ],
    "answer": "a few"
  },
  {
    "question": "bedoelen",
    "options": [
      "to mean",
      "a few",
      "equally",
      "to pose"
    ],
    "answer": "to mean"
  },
  {
    "question": "de computer",
    "options": [
      "computer",
      "to mean",
      "a few",
      "equally"
    ],
    "answer": "computer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de cursus",
    "options": [
      "course",
      "computer",
      "to mean",
      "a few"
    ],
    "answer": "course"
  },
  {
    "question": "de datum",
    "options": [
      "date",
      "course",
      "computer",
      "to mean"
    ],
    "answer": "date"
  },
  {
    "question": "de herfst",
    "options": [
      "autumn",
      "date",
      "course",
      "computer"
    ],
    "answer": "autumn"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kok",
    "options": [
      "cook",
      "autumn",
      "date",
      "course"
    ],
    "answer": "cook"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wachtlijst",
    "options": [
      "waiting list",
      "cook",
      "autumn",
      "date"
    ],
    "answer": "waiting list"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wijk",
    "options": [
      "district",
      "waiting list",
      "cook",
      "autumn"
    ],
    "answer": "district"
  },
  {
    "question": "Engels",
    "options": [
      "English",
      "district",
      "waiting list",
      "cook"
    ],
    "answer": "English"
  },
  {
    "question": "gratis",
    "options": [
      "free",
      "English",
      "district",
      "waiting list"
    ],
    "answer": "free"
  },
  {
    "question": "het najaar",
    "options": [
      "autumn",
      "free",
      "English",
      "district"
    ],
    "answer": "autumn"
  },
  {
    "question": "het voorjaar",
    "options": [
      "spring",
      "autumn",
      "free",
      "English"
    ],
    "answer": "spring"
  },
  {
    "question": "het wijkcentrum",
    "options": [
      "community centre",
      "spring",
      "autumn",
      "free"
    ],
    "answer": "community centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "laatst",
    "options": [
      "last",
      "community centre",
      "spring",
      "autumn"
    ],
    "answer": "last"
  },
  {
    "question": "leren",
    "options": [
      "to learn",
      "last",
      "community centre",
      "spring"
    ],
    "answer": "to learn"
  },
  {
    "question": "maart",
    "options": [
      "March",
      "to learn",
      "last",
      "community centre"
    ],
    "answer": "March"
  },
  {
    "question": "mailen",
    "options": [
      "to email",
      "March",
      "to learn",
      "last"
    ],
    "answer": "to email"
  },
  {
    "question": "mei",
    "options": [
      "May",
      "to email",
      "March",
      "to learn"
    ],
    "answer": "May"
  },
  {
    "question": "meteen",
    "options": [
      "straight away",
      "May",
      "to email",
      "March"
    ],
    "answer": "straight away"
  },
  {
    "question": "noteren",
    "options": [
      "to write down",
      "straight away",
      "May",
      "to email"
    ],
    "answer": "to write down"
  },
  {
    "question": "overdag",
    "options": [
      "during the day",
      "to write down",
      "straight away",
      "May"
    ],
    "answer": "during the day"
  },
  {
    "question": "'s morgens",
    "options": [
      "in the morning",
      "during the day",
      "to write down",
      "straight away"
    ],
    "answer": "in the morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "starten",
    "options": [
      "to start",
      "in the morning",
      "during the day",
      "to write down"
    ],
    "answer": "to start"
  },
  {
    "question": "super",
    "options": [
      "super",
      "to start",
      "in the morning",
      "during the day"
    ],
    "answer": "super"
  },
  {
    "question": "zullen",
    "options": [
      "shall",
      "super",
      "to start",
      "in the morning"
    ],
    "answer": "shall"
  },
  {
    "question": "de basisschool",
    "options": [
      "elementary school",
      "shall",
      "super",
      "to start"
    ],
    "answer": "elementary school"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boom",
    "options": [
      "tree",
      "elementary school",
      "shall",
      "super"
    ],
    "answer": "tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kerk",
    "options": [
      "church",
      "tree",
      "elementary school",
      "shall"
    ],
    "answer": "church"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kop",
    "options": [
      "cup",
      "church",
      "tree",
      "elementary school"
    ],
    "answer": "cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lift",
    "options": [
      "elevator",
      "cup",
      "church",
      "tree"
    ],
    "answer": "elevator"
  },
  {
    "question": "de moskee",
    "options": [
      "mosque",
      "elevator",
      "cup",
      "church"
    ],
    "answer": "mosque"
  },
  {
    "question": "de struik",
    "options": [
      "bush",
      "mosque",
      "elevator",
      "cup"
    ],
    "answer": "bush"
  },
  {
    "question": "elkaar",
    "options": [
      "each other",
      "bush",
      "mosque",
      "elevator"
    ],
    "answer": "each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "er",
    "options": [
      "there",
      "each other",
      "bush",
      "mosque"
    ],
    "answer": "there"
  },
  {
    "question": "fietsen",
    "options": [
      "to ride a bike",
      "there",
      "each other",
      "bush"
    ],
    "answer": "to ride a bike"
  },
  {
    "question": "gemakkelijk",
    "options": [
      "convenient",
      "to ride a bike",
      "there",
      "each other"
    ],
    "answer": "convenient"
  },
  {
    "question": "groen",
    "options": [
      "green",
      "convenient",
      "to ride a bike",
      "there"
    ],
    "answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "question": "het café",
    "options": [
      "cafe",
      "green",
      "convenient",
      "to ride a bike"
    ],
    "answer": "cafe"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gezin",
    "options": [
      "family",
      "cafe",
      "green",
      "convenient"
    ],
    "answer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "het park",
    "options": [
      "park",
      "family",
      "cafe",
      "green"
    ],
    "answer": "park"
  },
  {
    "question": "het praatje",
    "options": [
      "chat",
      "park",
      "family",
      "cafe"
    ],
    "answer": "chat"
  },
  {
    "question": "het rijtjeshuis",
    "options": [
      "terraced house",
      "chat",
      "park",
      "family"
    ],
    "answer": "terraced house"
  },
  {
    "question": "het verkeer",
    "options": [
      "traffic",
      "terraced house",
      "chat",
      "park"
    ],
    "answer": "traffic"
  },
  {
    "question": "lelijk",
    "options": [
      "ugly",
      "traffic",
      "terraced house",
      "chat"
    ],
    "answer": "ugly"
  },
  {
    "question": "missen",
    "options": [
      "to miss",
      "ugly",
      "traffic",
      "terraced house"
    ],
    "answer": "to miss"
  },
  {
    "question": "spelen",
    "options": [
      "to play",
      "to miss",
      "ugly",
      "traffic"
    ],
    "answer": "to play"
  },
  {
    "question": "voetballen",
    "options": [
      "to play football",
      "to play",
      "to miss",
      "ugly"
    ],
    "answer": "to play football"
  },
  {
    "question": "de trap",
    "options": [
      "stairs",
      "to play football",
      "to play",
      "to miss"
    ],
    "answer": "stairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "aardig",
    "options": [
      "nice",
      "stairs",
      "to play football",
      "to play"
    ],
    "answer": "nice"
  },
  {
    "question": "blaffen",
    "options": [
      "to bark",
      "nice",
      "stairs",
      "to play football"
    ],
    "answer": "to bark"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buurman",
    "options": [
      "(male) neighbour",
      "to bark",
      "nice",
      "stairs"
    ],
    "answer": "(male) neighbour"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hond",
    "options": [
      "dog",
      "(male) neighbour",
      "to bark",
      "nice"
    ],
    "answer": "dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "door",
    "options": [
      "throughout",
      "dog",
      "(male) neighbour",
      "to bark"
    ],
    "answer": "throughout"
  },
  {
    "question": "hard",
    "options": [
      "loud",
      "throughout",
      "dog",
      "(male) neighbour"
    ],
    "answer": "loud"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geluid",
    "options": [
      "sound",
      "loud",
      "throughout",
      "dog"
    ],
    "answer": "sound"
  },
  {
    "question": "huilen",
    "options": [
      "to cry",
      "sound",
      "loud",
      "throughout"
    ],
    "answer": "to cry"
  },
  {
    "question": "inderdaad",
    "options": [
      "indeed",
      "to cry",
      "sound",
      "loud"
    ],
    "answer": "indeed"
  },
  {
    "question": "irritant",
    "options": [
      "irritating",
      "indeed",
      "to cry",
      "sound"
    ],
    "answer": "irritating"
  },
  {
    "question": "jong",
    "options": [
      "young",
      "irritating",
      "indeed",
      "to cry"
    ],
    "answer": "young"
  },
  {
    "question": "klinken",
    "options": [
      "to sound",
      "young",
      "irritating",
      "indeed"
    ],
    "answer": "to sound"
  },
  {
    "question": "lachen",
    "options": [
      "to laugh",
      "to sound",
      "young",
      "irritating"
    ],
    "answer": "to laugh"
  },
  {
    "question": "nauwelijks",
    "options": [
      "barely",
      "to laugh",
      "to sound",
      "young"
    ],
    "answer": "barely"
  },
  {
    "question": "normaal",
    "options": [
      "normal",
      "barely",
      "to laugh",
      "to sound"
    ],
    "answer": "normal"
  },
  {
    "question": "opvoeden",
    "options": [
      "to train",
      "normal",
      "barely",
      "to laugh"
    ],
    "answer": "to train"
  },
  {
    "question": "prettig",
    "options": [
      "pleasant",
      "to train",
      "normal",
      "barely"
    ],
    "answer": "pleasant"
  },
  {
    "question": "sommige",
    "options": [
      "some",
      "pleasant",
      "to train",
      "normal"
    ],
    "answer": "some"
  },
  {
    "question": "sterk",
    "options": [
      "strong",
      "some",
      "pleasant",
      "to train"
    ],
    "answer": "strong"
  },
  {
    "question": "zacht",
    "options": [
      "gentle",
      "strong",
      "some",
      "pleasant"
    ],
    "answer": "gentle"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoveel",
    "options": [
      "that much",
      "gentle",
      "strong",
      "some"
    ],
    "answer": "that much"
  },
  {
    "question": "zelfstandig",
    "options": [
      "independent",
      "that much",
      "gentle",
      "strong"
    ],
    "answer": "independent"
  },
  {
    "question": "stevig",
    "options": [
      "firm",
      "independent",
      "that much",
      "gentle"
    ],
    "answer": "firm"
  },
  {
    "question": "beginnen",
    "options": [
      "to start",
      "firm",
      "independent",
      "that much"
    ],
    "answer": "to start"
  },
  {
    "question": "wandelen",
    "options": [
      "to walk",
      "to start",
      "firm",
      "independent"
    ],
    "answer": "to walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "wonen",
    "options": [
      "to live",
      "to walk",
      "to start",
      "firm"
    ],
    "answer": "to live"
  },
  {
    "question": "verhuizen",
    "options": [
      "to move (house)",
      "to live",
      "to walk",
      "to start"
    ],
    "answer": "to move (house)"
  },
  {
    "question": "bijna",
    "options": [
      "almost",
      "to move (house)",
      "to live",
      "to walk"
    ],
    "answer": "almost"
  },
  {
    "question": "het raam",
    "options": [
      "window",
      "almost",
      "to move (house)",
      "to live"
    ],
    "answer": "window"
  },
  {
    "question": "de muur",
    "options": [
      "wall",
      "window",
      "almost",
      "to move (house)"
    ],
    "answer": "wall"
  },
  {
    "question": "de deur",
    "options": [
      "door",
      "wall",
      "window",
      "almost"
    ],
    "answer": "door"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vloer",
    "options": [
      "floor",
      "door",
      "wall",
      "window"
    ],
    "answer": "floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "de banaan",
    "options": [
      "bananas",
      "groceries",
      "lemon",
      "to do"
    ],
    "answer": "bananas"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boodschappen",
    "options": [
      "to buy",
      "groceries",
      "chicken",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "groceries"
  },
  {
    "question": "de citroen",
    "options": [
      "to talk",
      "lemon",
      "nice",
      "vegetable"
    ],
    "answer": "lemon"
  },
  {
    "question": "doen",
    "options": [
      "to do",
      "to want",
      "to say",
      "to eat"
    ],
    "answer": "to do"
  },
  {
    "question": "dus",
    "options": [
      "so",
      "or",
      "onion",
      "home"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "al",
    "options": [
      "already",
      "greeting",
      "cold",
      "mother"
    ],
    "answer": "already"
  },
  {
    "question": "alles",
    "options": [
      "everything",
      "coffee",
      "father",
      "week"
    ],
    "answer": "everything"
  },
  {
    "question": "altijd",
    "options": [
      "always",
      "bad",
      "to offer",
      "party"
    ],
    "answer": "always"
  },
  {
    "question": "beterschap",
    "options": [
      "get well",
      "to meet",
      "nice",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "get well"
  },
  {
    "question": "de groet",
    "options": [
      "greeting",
      "to drink",
      "sick",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "greeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hoofdpijn",
    "options": [
      "headache",
      "to sleep",
      "to come along",
      "fine"
    ],
    "answer": "headache"
  },
  {
    "question": "de moeder",
    "options": [
      "mother",
      "party",
      "milk",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vader",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "to invite",
      "to drink",
      "weather"
    ],
    "answer": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vriend",
    "options": [
      "friend",
      "tea",
      "satisfied",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "friend"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vriendin",
    "options": [
      "girlfriend",
      "coffee",
      "noise",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "girlfriend"
  },
  {
    "question": "de week",
    "options": [
      "week",
      "late",
      "sick",
      "a pity"
    ],
    "answer": "week"
  },
  {
    "question": "een beetje",
    "options": [
      "a little bit",
      "to be located",
      "party",
      "nice"
    ],
    "answer": "a little bit"
  },
  {
    "question": "goed",
    "options": [
      "good",
      "to visit",
      "to get",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "good"
  },
  {
    "question": "heerlijk",
    "options": [
      "wonderful",
      "to offer",
      "fine",
      "busy"
    ],
    "answer": "wonderful"
  },
  {
    "question": "het contact",
    "options": [
      "contact",
      "happy",
      "to sleep",
      "snow"
    ],
    "answer": "contact"
  },
  {
    "question": "het weer",
    "options": [
      "weather",
      "to invite",
      "to marry",
      "luckily"
    ],
    "answer": "weather"
  },
  {
    "question": "koud",
    "options": [
      "cold",
      "to see",
      "to have to",
      "soon"
    ],
    "answer": "cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "lekker",
    "options": [
      "nice",
      "sick",
      "to begin",
      "music"
    ],
    "answer": "nice"
  },
  {
    "question": "nooit",
    "options": [
      "never",
      "sugar",
      "to come in",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "never"
  },
  {
    "question": "ontmoeten",
    "options": [
      "to meet",
      "a pity",
      "to come along",
      "milk"
    ],
    "answer": "to meet"
  },
  {
    "question": "slecht",
    "options": [
      "bad",
      "to sleep",
      "coffee",
      "cold"
    ],
    "answer": "bad"
  },
  {
    "question": "vaak",
    "options": [
      "often",
      "to get",
      "water",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "often"
  },
  {
    "question": "vervelend",
    "options": [
      "unpleasant",
      "happy",
      "to offer",
      "music"
    ],
    "answer": "unpleasant"
  },
  {
    "question": "warm",
    "options": [
      "warm",
      "party",
      "to begin",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "warm"
  },
  {
    "question": "ziek",
    "options": [
      "sick",
      "to be possible",
      "father",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "sick"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanbieden",
    "options": [
      "to offer",
      "to get",
      "to come in",
      "good"
    ],
    "answer": "to offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "binnenkomen",
    "options": [
      "to come in",
      "to marry",
      "milk",
      "happy"
    ],
    "answer": "to come in"
  },
  {
    "question": "boven",
    "options": [
      "upstairs",
      "nice",
      "to drink",
      "to visit"
    ],
    "answer": "upstairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "de baby",
    "options": [
      "baby",
      "a lot",
      "to begin",
      "sick"
    ],
    "answer": "baby"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koffie",
    "options": [
      "coffee",
      "to see",
      "to have",
      "party"
    ],
    "answer": "coffee"
  },
  {
    "question": "de melk",
    "options": [
      "milk",
      "to have",
      "to get",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "milk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de suiker",
    "options": [
      "sugar",
      "to meet",
      "to be located",
      "nice"
    ],
    "answer": "sugar"
  },
  {
    "question": "de thee",
    "options": [
      "tea",
      "to invite",
      "to drink",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "drinken",
    "options": [
      "to drink",
      "fine",
      "to visit",
      "to be located"
    ],
    "answer": "to drink"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bezoek",
    "options": [
      "to visit",
      "a little bit",
      "to get",
      "happy"
    ],
    "answer": "to visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "klein",
    "options": [
      "small",
      "to sleep",
      "music",
      "late"
    ],
    "answer": "small"
  },
  {
    "question": "leuk",
    "options": [
      "nice",
      "to come in",
      "party",
      "to be possible"
    ],
    "answer": "nice"
  },
  {
    "question": "makkelijk",
    "options": [
      "easy",
      "to have",
      "to marry",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "mama",
    "options": [
      "Mummy",
      "to drink",
      "to be located",
      "happy"
    ],
    "answer": "Mummy"
  },
  {
    "question": "meegaan",
    "options": [
      "to come along",
      "to have to",
      "nice",
      "sick"
    ],
    "answer": "to come along"
  },
  {
    "question": "nemen",
    "options": [
      "to take",
      "to get",
      "to have",
      "party"
    ],
    "answer": "to take"
  },
  {
    "question": "oud",
    "options": [
      "old",
      "music",
      "to visit",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "old"
  },
  {
    "question": "papa",
    "options": [
      "Daddy",
      "to begin",
      "to drink",
      "nice"
    ],
    "answer": "Daddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "prima",
    "options": [
      "fine",
      "to invite",
      "to be located",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "fine"
  },
  {
    "question": "slapen",
    "options": [
      "to sleep",
      "to get",
      "to see",
      "coffee"
    ],
    "answer": "to sleep"
  },
  {
    "question": "het water",
    "options": [
      "water",
      "to marry",
      "to begin",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "water"
  },
  {
    "question": "zelf",
    "options": [
      "self",
      "party",
      "to have to",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "self"
  },
  {
    "question": "zien",
    "options": [
      "to see",
      "to have to",
      "to drink",
      "music"
    ],
    "answer": "to see"
  },
  {
    "question": "zitten",
    "options": [
      "to be located",
      "to get",
      "to meet",
      "fine"
    ],
    "answer": "to be located"
  },
  {
    "question": "hebben",
    "options": [
      "to have",
      "to come along",
      "to sleep",
      "to visit"
    ],
    "answer": "to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "beginnen",
    "options": [
      "to begin",
      "to drink",
      "to see",
      "sick"
    ],
    "answer": "to begin"
  },
  {
    "question": "blij",
    "options": [
      "happy",
      "to have to",
      "to marry",
      "coffee"
    ],
    "answer": "happy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de baan",
    "options": [
      "job",
      "to have to",
      "to see",
      "tea"
    ],
    "answer": "job"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ouders",
    "options": [
      "parents",
      "to drink",
      "to get",
      "music"
    ],
    "answer": "parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tv",
    "options": [
      "TV",
      "to be located",
      "to have",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "TV"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vakantie",
    "options": [
      "holiday",
      "to have to",
      "to invite",
      "to see"
    ],
    "answer": "holiday"
  },
  {
    "question": "eten",
    "options": [
      "to eat",
      "to marry",
      "to sleep",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "to eat"
  },
  {
    "question": "gezellig",
    "options": [
      "enjoyable",
      "to invite",
      "party",
      "nice"
    ],
    "answer": "enjoyable"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kwartier",
    "options": [
      "quarter of an hour",
      "to have",
      "to come along",
      "to see"
    ],
    "answer": "quarter of an hour"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lawaai",
    "options": [
      "noise",
      "to sleep",
      "to begin",
      "music"
    ],
    "answer": "noise"
  },
  {
    "question": "jammer",
    "options": [
      "a pity",
      "to have to",
      "to get",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "a pity"
  },
  {
    "question": "kunnen",
    "options": [
      "to be possible",
      "to begin",
      "to see",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "to be possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "kwart",
    "options": [
      "quarter",
      "to come in",
      "to visit",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "quarter"
  },
  {
    "question": "laat",
    "options": [
      "late",
      "to marry",
      "to have",
      "to be located"
    ],
    "answer": "late"
  },
  {
    "question": "mooi",
    "options": [
      "great",
      "to get",
      "to have",
      "nice"
    ],
    "answer": "great"
  },
  {
    "question": "om",
    "options": [
      "at",
      "to sleep",
      "to begin",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "at"
  },
  {
    "question": "sorry",
    "options": [
      "sorry",
      "to be located",
      "to meet",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "sorry"
  },
  {
    "question": "tevreden",
    "options": [
      "satisfied",
      "to have to",
      "to drink",
      "music"
    ],
    "answer": "satisfied"
  },
  {
    "question": "toch",
    "options": [
      "after all",
      "to begin",
      "to see",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "after all"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitnodigen",
    "options": [
      "to invite",
      "to drink",
      "to get",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "to invite"
  },
  {
    "question": "vanavond",
    "options": [
      "tonight",
      "to have",
      "to be located",
      "to visit"
    ],
    "answer": "tonight"
  },
  {
    "question": "voetbal",
    "options": [
      "football",
      "to drink",
      "to get",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "football"
  },
  {
    "question": "vroeg",
    "options": [
      "early",
      "to have to",
      "to marry",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "early"
  },
  {
    "question": "druk",
    "options": [
      "busy",
      "to be located",
      "to begin",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "busy"
  },
  {
    "question": "benieuwd",
    "options": [
      "curious",
      "to visit",
      "to have to",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "curious"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kleren",
    "options": [
      "clothes",
      "to drink",
      "to begin",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "de muziek",
    "options": [
      "music",
      "to have",
      "to get",
      "to visit"
    ],
    "answer": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitnodiging",
    "options": [
      "invitation",
      "to sleep",
      "to see",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "invitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "erg",
    "options": [
      "very",
      "to have to",
      "to begin",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "very"
  },
  {
    "question": "februari",
    "options": [
      "February",
      "to marry",
      "to get",
      "to drink"
    ],
    "answer": "February"
  },
  {
    "question": "gauw",
    "options": [
      "soon",
      "to be located",
      "to drink",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "soon"
  },
  {
    "question": "gebeuren",
    "options": [
      "to happen",
      "to have to",
      "to see",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "to happen"
  },
  {
    "question": "gefeliciteerd",
    "options": [
      "congratulations",
      "to get",
      "to drink",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "congratulations"
  },
  {
    "question": "gelukkig",
    "options": [
      "luckily",
      "to sleep",
      "to visit",
      "to have to"
    ],
    "answer": "luckily"
  },
  {
    "question": "geven",
    "options": [
      "to give",
      "to see",
      "to drink",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "to give"
  },
  {
    "question": "groot",
    "options": [
      "big",
      "to marry",
      "to visit",
      "to have to"
    ],
    "answer": "big"
  },
  {
    "question": "heel",
    "options": [
      "very",
      "to get",
      "to begin",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "very"
  },
  {
    "question": "helemaal",
    "options": [
      "completely",
      "to see",
      "to drink",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "completely"
  },
  {
    "question": "het feest",
    "options": [
      "party",
      "to drink",
      "to marry",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "party"
  },
  {
    "question": "het nieuws",
    "options": [
      "news",
      "to be located",
      "to begin",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "news"
  },
  {
    "question": "het werk",
    "options": [
      "work",
      "to marry",
      "to drink",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "work"
  },
  {
    "question": "iemand",
    "options": [
      "somebody",
      "to get",
      "to visit",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "somebody"
  },
  {
    "question": "jarig",
    "options": [
      "having his/her birthday",
      "to drink",
      "to marry",
      "to see"
    ],
    "answer": "having his/her birthday"
  },
  {
    "question": "krijgen",
    "options": [
      "to get",
      "to see",
      "to sleep",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "to get"
  },
  {
    "question": "moeten",
    "options": [
      "to have to",
      "to begin",
      "to drink",
      "to get"
    ],
    "answer": "to have to"
  },
  {
    "question": "trouwen",
    "options": [
      "to marry",
      "to get",
      "to drink",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "to marry"
  },
  {
    "question": "veel",
    "options": [
      "a lot",
      "to visit",
      "to drink",
      "to marry"
    ],
    "answer": "a lot"
  },
  {
    "question": "wanneer",
    "options": [
      "when",
      "to begin",
      "to get",
      "to see"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "allerlei",
    "options": [
      "all sorts",
      "offer",
      "soup",
      "house"
    ],
    "answer": "all sorts"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aanbieding",
    "options": [
      "offer",
      "butter",
      "refrigerator",
      "sandwich"
    ],
    "answer": "offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "het avondeten",
    "options": [
      "supper",
      "cookie",
      "fries",
      "egg"
    ],
    "answer": "supper"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boter",
    "options": [
      "butter",
      "bottle",
      "cake",
      "kale"
    ],
    "answer": "butter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de fles",
    "options": [
      "bottle",
      "bread",
      "sweet",
      "interview"
    ],
    "answer": "bottle"
  },
  {
    "question": "de knoflook",
    "options": [
      "garlic",
      "herbs",
      "to cook",
      "bean"
    ],
    "answer": "garlic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koelkast",
    "options": [
      "refrigerator",
      "to stand",
      "to use",
      "to lose weight"
    ],
    "answer": "refrigerator"
  },
  {
    "question": "de soep",
    "options": [
      "soup",
      "fat",
      "sandwich",
      "to like"
    ],
    "answer": "soup"
  },
  {
    "question": "de worst",
    "options": [
      "sausage",
      "sweet",
      "to answer",
      "leg"
    ],
    "answer": "sausage"
  },
  {
    "question": "de yoghurt",
    "options": [
      "yogurt",
      "fat",
      "salt",
      "orange juice"
    ],
    "answer": "yogurt"
  },
  {
    "question": "het brood",
    "options": [
      "bread",
      "to weigh",
      "cake",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "bread"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huis",
    "options": [
      "house",
      "doctor",
      "moment",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "house"
  },
  {
    "question": "het stuk",
    "options": [
      "piece",
      "later",
      "almost",
      "everything"
    ],
    "answer": "piece"
  },
  {
    "question": "het toetje",
    "options": [
      "dessert",
      "to take along",
      "to cook",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "dessert"
  },
  {
    "question": "het volkorenbrood",
    "options": [
      "whole grain bread",
      "to like",
      "to stand",
      "sandwich"
    ],
    "answer": "whole grain bread"
  },
  {
    "question": "het zout",
    "options": [
      "salt",
      "bottle",
      "soup",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "klaar",
    "options": [
      "ready",
      "cake",
      "disgusting",
      "to lose weight"
    ],
    "answer": "ready"
  },
  {
    "question": "langs",
    "options": [
      "by",
      "sausage",
      "fat",
      "now and then"
    ],
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "question": "meenemen",
    "options": [
      "to take along",
      "to like",
      "to answer",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "to take along"
  },
  {
    "question": "niks",
    "options": [
      "nothing",
      "cookie",
      "to use",
      "to pick up"
    ],
    "answer": "nothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "nodig hebben",
    "options": [
      "to need",
      "fat",
      "to stand",
      "to lose weight"
    ],
    "answer": "to need"
  },
  {
    "question": "staan",
    "options": [
      "to stand",
      "ready",
      "baked",
      "fat"
    ],
    "answer": "to stand"
  },
  {
    "question": "straks",
    "options": [
      "later",
      "to cook",
      "to smell",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "later"
  },
  {
    "question": "we",
    "options": [
      "we",
      "cake",
      "soup",
      "egg"
    ],
    "answer": "we"
  },
  {
    "question": "zonder",
    "options": [
      "without",
      "to find",
      "fat",
      "to take along"
    ],
    "answer": "without"
  },
  {
    "question": "het pak",
    "options": [
      "pack",
      "sweet",
      "sandwich",
      "interview"
    ],
    "answer": "pack"
  },
  {
    "question": "af en toe",
    "options": [
      "now and then , occasionally , from time to time",
      "to like",
      "to lose weight",
      "cookie"
    ],
    "answer": "now and then , occasionally , from time to time"
  },
  {
    "question": "de patat",
    "options": [
      "fries",
      "house",
      "to cook",
      "to use"
    ],
    "answer": "fries"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rijst",
    "options": [
      "rice",
      "to stand",
      "bottle",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "beantwoorden",
    "options": [
      "to answer",
      "baked",
      "to weigh",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "to answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boerenkool",
    "options": [
      "kale",
      "cake",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "kale"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boterham",
    "options": [
      "sandwich",
      "sausage",
      "to find",
      "to take along"
    ],
    "answer": "sandwich"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kruiden",
    "options": [
      "herbs",
      "to enjoy",
      "fat",
      "to answer"
    ],
    "answer": "herbs"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lunch",
    "options": [
      "lunch",
      "to smell",
      "to like",
      "cookie"
    ],
    "answer": "lunch"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pap",
    "options": [
      "porridge",
      "soup",
      "to cook",
      "to stand"
    ],
    "answer": "porridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "gebruiken",
    "options": [
      "to use",
      "fat",
      "bottle",
      "to answer"
    ],
    "answer": "to use"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bier",
    "options": [
      "beer",
      "to weigh",
      "to enjoy",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "beer"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ei",
    "options": [
      "egg",
      "cookie",
      "bottle",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "egg"
  },
  {
    "question": "het interview",
    "options": [
      "interview",
      "to like",
      "to find",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "interview"
  },
  {
    "question": "het jaar",
    "options": [
      "year",
      "fat",
      "to stand",
      "to lose weight"
    ],
    "answer": "year"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ontbijt",
    "options": [
      "breakfast",
      "bottle",
      "to answer",
      "fat"
    ],
    "answer": "breakfast"
  },
  {
    "question": "houden van",
    "options": [
      "to like",
      "to cook",
      "cake",
      "to weigh"
    ],
    "answer": "to like"
  },
  {
    "question": "jullie",
    "options": [
      "you (plural)",
      "fat",
      "to find",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "you (plural)"
  },
  {
    "question": "vinden",
    "options": [
      "to find",
      "to lose weight",
      "fat",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "to find"
  },
  {
    "question": "weleens",
    "options": [
      "sometimes",
      "cake",
      "to answer",
      "to weigh"
    ],
    "answer": "sometimes"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoet",
    "options": [
      "sweet",
      "fat",
      "cookie",
      "to stand"
    ],
    "answer": "sweet"
  },
  {
    "question": "zout",
    "options": [
      "salty",
      "to cook",
      "to find",
      "to answer"
    ],
    "answer": "salty"
  },
  {
    "question": "de eieren",
    "options": [
      "eggs",
      "to like",
      "bottle",
      "to use"
    ],
    "answer": "eggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "afvallen",
    "options": [
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook",
      "to enjoy",
      "fat"
    ],
    "answer": "to lose weight"
  },
  {
    "question": "bijna",
    "options": [
      "almost",
      "cookie",
      "to stand",
      "to answer"
    ],
    "answer": "almost"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buik",
    "options": [
      "belly",
      "to like",
      "fat",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "belly"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dokter",
    "options": [
      "doctor",
      "to find",
      "to enjoy",
      "to lose weight"
    ],
    "answer": "doctor"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hamburger",
    "options": [
      "hamburger",
      "to cook",
      "to stand",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "hamburger"
  },
  {
    "question": "dik",
    "options": [
      "fat",
      "cake",
      "to find",
      "to like"
    ],
    "answer": "fat"
  },
  {
    "question": "echt",
    "options": [
      "really",
      "to answer",
      "to enjoy",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "really"
  },
  {
    "question": "eigenlijk",
    "options": [
      "actually",
      "to cook",
      "to weigh",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "actually"
  },
  {
    "question": "gewoon",
    "options": [
      "simply",
      "to stand",
      "to like",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "simply"
  },
  {
    "question": "gezond",
    "options": [
      "healthy",
      "to use",
      "fat",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "healthy"
  },
  {
    "question": "halen",
    "options": [
      "to pick up",
      "to find",
      "to stand",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "to pick up"
  },
  {
    "question": "hebben",
    "options": [
      "to have",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook",
      "to answer"
    ],
    "answer": "to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bed",
    "options": [
      "bed",
      "cake",
      "to stand",
      "to like"
    ],
    "answer": "bed"
  },
  {
    "question": "het been",
    "options": [
      "leg",
      "to answer",
      "fat",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "leg"
  },
  {
    "question": "het koekje",
    "options": [
      "cookie",
      "to enjoy",
      "to stand",
      "to use"
    ],
    "answer": "cookie"
  },
  {
    "question": "koken",
    "options": [
      "to cook",
      "to lose weight",
      "to find",
      "to like"
    ],
    "answer": "to cook"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sinaasappelsap",
    "options": [
      "orange juice",
      "fat",
      "to stand",
      "to use"
    ],
    "answer": "orange juice"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sla",
    "options": [
      "lettuce",
      "to cook",
      "to like",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "lettuce"
  },
  {
    "question": "de snackbar",
    "options": [
      "snack bar",
      "to find",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "snack bar"
  },
  {
    "question": "het probleem",
    "options": [
      "problem",
      "to enjoy",
      "cake",
      "to like"
    ],
    "answer": "problem"
  },
  {
    "question": "het snoepje",
    "options": [
      "sweet",
      "to cook",
      "to stand",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "sweet"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vet",
    "options": [
      "fat",
      "to lose weight",
      "to like",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "fat"
  },
  {
    "question": "minder",
    "options": [
      "less",
      "to find",
      "to cook",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "less"
  },
  {
    "question": "te",
    "options": [
      "too",
      "to like",
      "to answer",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "too"
  },
  {
    "question": "wegen",
    "options": [
      "to weigh",
      "to cook",
      "to stand",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "to weigh"
  },
  {
    "question": "dat",
    "options": [
      "that",
      "to enjoy",
      "to smell",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "that"
  },
  {
    "question": "de alcohol",
    "options": [
      "alcohol",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook",
      "to answer"
    ],
    "answer": "alcohol"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boon",
    "options": [
      "bean",
      "to stand",
      "to cook",
      "to like"
    ],
    "answer": "bean"
  },
  {
    "question": "de cola",
    "options": [
      "cola",
      "to enjoy",
      "to cook",
      "to stand"
    ],
    "answer": "cola"
  },
  {
    "question": "de couscous",
    "options": [
      "couscous",
      "to weigh",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "couscous"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mayonaise",
    "options": [
      "mayonnaise",
      "to find",
      "to enjoy",
      "to stand"
    ],
    "answer": "mayonnaise"
  },
  {
    "question": "de taart",
    "options": [
      "cake",
      "to cook",
      "to lose weight",
      "to stand"
    ],
    "answer": "cake"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wereld",
    "options": [
      "world",
      "to like",
      "to cook",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "world"
  },
  {
    "question": "gebakken",
    "options": [
      "baked",
      "to enjoy",
      "to lose weight",
      "to stand"
    ],
    "answer": "baked"
  },
  {
    "question": "genieten",
    "options": [
      "to enjoy",
      "to find",
      "to cook",
      "to lose weight"
    ],
    "answer": "to enjoy"
  },
  {
    "question": "heel",
    "options": [
      "very",
      "to like",
      "to cook",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "very"
  },
  {
    "question": "het broodje",
    "options": [
      "sandwich",
      "to find",
      "to weigh",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "sandwich"
  },
  {
    "question": "het glas",
    "options": [
      "glass",
      "to cook",
      "to like",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "glass"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lam",
    "options": [
      "lamb",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "lamb"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lievelingseten",
    "options": [
      "favourite food",
      "to stand",
      "to enjoy",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "favourite food"
  },
  {
    "question": "het moment",
    "options": [
      "moment",
      "to cook",
      "to lose weight",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "ieder",
    "options": [
      "every",
      "to find",
      "to enjoy",
      "to cook"
    ],
    "answer": "every"
  },
  {
    "question": "precies",
    "options": [
      "exactly",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "exactly"
  },
  {
    "question": "ruiken",
    "options": [
      "to smell",
      "to cook",
      "to find",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "to smell"
  },
  {
    "question": "smaken",
    "options": [
      "to taste",
      "to lose weight",
      "to cook",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "to taste"
  },
  {
    "question": "tussendoor",
    "options": [
      "in between",
      "to cook",
      "to enjoy",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "in between"
  },
  {
    "question": "vies",
    "options": [
      "disgusting",
      "to stand",
      "to cook",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "disgusting"
  },
  {
    "question": "weinig",
    "options": [
      "not much",
      "to cook",
      "to lose weight",
      "to enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "not much"
  },
  {
    "question": "mager",
    "options": [
      "low fat",
      "to cook",
      "to lose weight",
      "to find"
    ],
    "answer": "low fat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tafel",
    "options": [
      "table",
      "to drink",
      "to have",
      "to sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "table"
  },
  {
    "question": "alle",
    "options": [
      "all",
      "busy",
      "garden",
      "key"
    ],
    "answer": "all"
  },
  {
    "question": "beneden",
    "options": [
      "downstairs",
      "light",
      "to pay",
      "summer"
    ],
    "answer": "downstairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "betalen",
    "options": [
      "to pay",
      "to clean up",
      "to help",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "to pay"
  },
  {
    "question": "buiten",
    "options": [
      "outside",
      "to share",
      "quiet",
      "dark"
    ],
    "answer": "outside"
  },
  {
    "question": "de badkamer",
    "options": [
      "bathroom",
      "chair",
      "block of flats",
      "price"
    ],
    "answer": "bathroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "de broer",
    "options": [
      "brother",
      "neighbours",
      "to doubt",
      "furniture"
    ],
    "answer": "brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buren",
    "options": [
      "neighbours",
      "to watch",
      "attic",
      "note"
    ],
    "answer": "neighbours"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huur",
    "options": [
      "rent",
      "customer",
      "discount",
      "summer"
    ],
    "answer": "rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kamer",
    "options": [
      "room",
      "number",
      "laptop",
      "public holiday"
    ],
    "answer": "room"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tuin",
    "options": [
      "garden",
      "summer",
      "to move",
      "to swap"
    ],
    "answer": "garden"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verdieping",
    "options": [
      "floor",
      "dark",
      "to choose",
      "key"
    ],
    "answer": "floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woonkamer",
    "options": [
      "living room",
      "customer",
      "to pay",
      "leaflet"
    ],
    "answer": "living room"
  },
  {
    "question": "delen",
    "options": [
      "to share",
      "to sell",
      "quiet",
      "to hang"
    ],
    "answer": "to share"
  },
  {
    "question": "druk",
    "options": [
      "busy",
      "to pick up",
      "blue",
      "window"
    ],
    "answer": "busy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het appartement",
    "options": [
      "apartment",
      "to doubt",
      "red",
      "furniture"
    ],
    "answer": "apartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "het centrum",
    "options": [
      "centre",
      "to help",
      "to cost",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "het licht",
    "options": [
      "light",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch",
      "to swap"
    ],
    "answer": "light"
  },
  {
    "question": "het liefst",
    "options": [
      "preferably",
      "dark",
      "quiet",
      "note"
    ],
    "answer": "preferably"
  },
  {
    "question": "hij",
    "options": [
      "he",
      "to choose",
      "to hang",
      "customer"
    ],
    "answer": "he"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoeveel",
    "options": [
      "how much",
      "to pay",
      "to share",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "how much"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoog",
    "options": [
      "high",
      "chair",
      "to doubt",
      "red"
    ],
    "answer": "high"
  },
  {
    "question": "laag",
    "options": [
      "low",
      "to move",
      "to sell",
      "to choose"
    ],
    "answer": "low"
  },
  {
    "question": "maken",
    "options": [
      "to make",
      "to swap",
      "discount",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "to make"
  },
  {
    "question": "per",
    "options": [
      "per",
      "quiet",
      "leaflet",
      "blue"
    ],
    "answer": "per"
  },
  {
    "question": "ruilen",
    "options": [
      "to swap",
      "to clean up",
      "to pick up",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "to swap"
  },
  {
    "question": "rustig",
    "options": [
      "quiet",
      "to help",
      "dark",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "quiet"
  },
  {
    "question": "verhuizen",
    "options": [
      "to move",
      "to pay",
      "to hang",
      "to share"
    ],
    "answer": "to move"
  },
  {
    "question": "vlakbij",
    "options": [
      "nearby",
      "to watch",
      "to clean up",
      "red"
    ],
    "answer": "nearby"
  },
  {
    "question": "want",
    "options": [
      "because",
      "to sell",
      "to doubt",
      "to choose"
    ],
    "answer": "because"
  },
  {
    "question": "wat voor",
    "options": [
      "what kind of",
      "to help",
      "to pick up",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "what kind of"
  },
  {
    "question": "zij",
    "options": [
      "she",
      "to pay",
      "to clean up",
      "discount"
    ],
    "answer": "she"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoeken",
    "options": [
      "to search",
      "to share",
      "to hang",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "to search"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ervaring",
    "options": [
      "experience",
      "to watch",
      "to move",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "de fiets",
    "options": [
      "bicycle",
      "to clean up",
      "quiet",
      "to pick up"
    ],
    "answer": "bicycle"
  },
  {
    "question": "de flat",
    "options": [
      "block of flats",
      "to hang",
      "to move",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "block of flats"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hulp",
    "options": [
      "help",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell",
      "quiet"
    ],
    "answer": "help"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ingang",
    "options": [
      "entrance",
      "to pick up",
      "to watch",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "entrance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de poes",
    "options": [
      "pussycat",
      "to clean up",
      "to hang",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "pussycat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sleutel",
    "options": [
      "key",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell",
      "to share"
    ],
    "answer": "key"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stoep",
    "options": [
      "sidewalk",
      "to help",
      "to move",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "sidewalk"
  },
  {
    "question": "deze",
    "options": [
      "these",
      "to pick up",
      "to doubt",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "these"
  },
  {
    "question": "gek op",
    "options": [
      "fond of",
      "to sell",
      "to share",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "fond of"
  },
  {
    "question": "hangen",
    "options": [
      "to hang",
      "to move",
      "to help",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "to hang"
  },
  {
    "question": "helpen",
    "options": [
      "to help",
      "to doubt",
      "to pick up",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "to help"
  },
  {
    "question": "het briefje",
    "options": [
      "note",
      "to sell",
      "to move",
      "to share"
    ],
    "answer": "note"
  },
  {
    "question": "het nummer",
    "options": [
      "number",
      "to hang",
      "to help",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "klussen",
    "options": [
      "small jobs",
      "to watch",
      "to clean up",
      "to pick up"
    ],
    "answer": "small jobs"
  },
  {
    "question": "leeg",
    "options": [
      "empty",
      "to move",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "empty"
  },
  {
    "question": "mij",
    "options": [
      "me",
      "to help",
      "to clean up",
      "to hang"
    ],
    "answer": "me"
  },
  {
    "question": "ophalen",
    "options": [
      "to pick up",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell",
      "to share"
    ],
    "answer": "to pick up"
  },
  {
    "question": "oppassen",
    "options": [
      "to watch",
      "to help",
      "to clean up",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "to watch"
  },
  {
    "question": "opruimen",
    "options": [
      "to clean up",
      "to sell",
      "to pick up",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "to clean up"
  },
  {
    "question": "uw",
    "options": [
      "your",
      "to hang",
      "to help",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "your"
  },
  {
    "question": "zijn",
    "options": [
      "his",
      "to doubt",
      "to pick up",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "his"
  },
  {
    "question": "zorgen voor",
    "options": [
      "to take care of",
      "to sell",
      "to clean up",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "to take care of"
  },
  {
    "question": "alleen",
    "options": [
      "on your own",
      "to help",
      "to doubt",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "on your own"
  },
  {
    "question": "blauw",
    "options": [
      "blue",
      "to hang",
      "to watch",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "daar",
    "options": [
      "there",
      "to help",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "there"
  },
  {
    "question": "de laptop",
    "options": [
      "laptop",
      "to pick up",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "laptop"
  },
  {
    "question": "de plek",
    "options": [
      "place",
      "to doubt",
      "to help",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "place"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stoel",
    "options": [
      "chair",
      "to help",
      "to move",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "chair"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tafel",
    "options": [
      "table",
      "to doubt",
      "to clean up",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "table"
  },
  {
    "question": "de winter",
    "options": [
      "winter",
      "to pick up",
      "to help",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "winter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zolder",
    "options": [
      "attic",
      "to doubt",
      "to clean up",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "attic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zomer",
    "options": [
      "summer",
      "to hang",
      "to watch",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "summer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zon",
    "options": [
      "sun",
      "to sell",
      "to move",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "dit",
    "options": [
      "this",
      "to pick up",
      "to doubt",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "this"
  },
  {
    "question": "donker",
    "options": [
      "dark",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "dark"
  },
  {
    "question": "het idee",
    "options": [
      "idea",
      "to move",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "het raam",
    "options": [
      "window",
      "to help",
      "to hang",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "window"
  },
  {
    "question": "jou",
    "options": [
      "you",
      "to sell",
      "to move",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "you"
  },
  {
    "question": "mezelf",
    "options": [
      "myself",
      "to doubt",
      "to help",
      "to pick up"
    ],
    "answer": "myself"
  },
  {
    "question": "trouwens",
    "options": [
      "by the way",
      "to move",
      "to watch",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "by the way"
  },
  {
    "question": "twijfelen",
    "options": [
      "to doubt",
      "to pick up",
      "to clean up",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "to doubt"
  },
  {
    "question": "waarom",
    "options": [
      "why",
      "to help",
      "to move",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "why"
  },
  {
    "question": "net",
    "options": [
      "just",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "just"
  },
  {
    "question": "de feestdag",
    "options": [
      "public holiday",
      "to pick up",
      "to help",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "public holiday"
  },
  {
    "question": "de folder",
    "options": [
      "leaflet",
      "to sell",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "leaflet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de helft",
    "options": [
      "half",
      "to help",
      "to doubt",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "half"
  },
  {
    "question": "de informatie",
    "options": [
      "information",
      "to watch",
      "to sell",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "information"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kast",
    "options": [
      "cupboard",
      "to clean up",
      "to pick up",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "cupboard"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klant",
    "options": [
      "customer",
      "to help",
      "to sell",
      "to move"
    ],
    "answer": "customer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de korting",
    "options": [
      "discount",
      "to doubt",
      "to pick up",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "discount"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lamp",
    "options": [
      "lamp",
      "to watch",
      "to move",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "lamp"
  },
  {
    "question": "de meubels",
    "options": [
      "furniture",
      "to help",
      "to clean up",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "furniture"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opruiming",
    "options": [
      "clearance sale",
      "to sell",
      "to move",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "clearance sale"
  },
  {
    "question": "de prijs",
    "options": [
      "price",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "price"
  },
  {
    "question": "de soort",
    "options": [
      "type of",
      "to doubt",
      "to help",
      "to pick up"
    ],
    "answer": "type of"
  },
  {
    "question": "de website",
    "options": [
      "website",
      "to sell",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "website"
  },
  {
    "question": "het procent",
    "options": [
      "percent",
      "to help",
      "to doubt",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "percent"
  },
  {
    "question": "kiezen",
    "options": [
      "to choose",
      "to clean up",
      "to move",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "to choose"
  },
  {
    "question": "kosten",
    "options": [
      "to cost",
      "to doubt",
      "to pick up",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "to cost"
  },
  {
    "question": "onze",
    "options": [
      "our",
      "to sell",
      "to move",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "our"
  },
  {
    "question": "rood",
    "options": [
      "red",
      "to clean up",
      "to watch",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "samen",
    "options": [
      "together",
      "to doubt",
      "to help",
      "to sell"
    ],
    "answer": "together"
  },
  {
    "question": "verkopen",
    "options": [
      "to sell",
      "to move",
      "to clean up",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "to sell"
  },
  {
    "question": "welk",
    "options": [
      "which",
      "to doubt",
      "to pick up",
      "to watch"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "wij",
    "options": [
      "we",
      "to sell",
      "to help",
      "to clean up"
    ],
    "answer": "we"
  },
  {
    "question": "wit",
    "options": [
      "white",
      "to move",
      "to help",
      "to doubt"
    ],
    "answer": "white"
  },
  {
    "question": "bedankt",
    "options": [
      "thanks",
      "teacher",
      "route",
      "delay"
    ],
    "answer": "thanks"
  },
  {
    "question": "centraal",
    "options": [
      "central",
      "car",
      "bag",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "central"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aankomst",
    "options": [
      "arrival",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "to walk"
    ],
    "answer": "arrival"
  },
  {
    "question": "de intercity",
    "options": [
      "Intercity train",
      "hurry",
      "to app",
      "station"
    ],
    "answer": "Intercity train"
  },
  {
    "question": "de metro",
    "options": [
      "subway",
      "car",
      "to walk",
      "message"
    ],
    "answer": "subway"
  },
  {
    "question": "de reis",
    "options": [
      "trip",
      "to explain",
      "delay",
      "to check in"
    ],
    "answer": "trip"
  },
  {
    "question": "de reistijd",
    "options": [
      "travel time",
      "to plan",
      "quiet",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "travel time"
  },
  {
    "question": "de richting",
    "options": [
      "direction",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "to walk"
    ],
    "answer": "direction"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sprinter",
    "options": [
      "Sprinter train",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "Sprinter train"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tas",
    "options": [
      "bag",
      "road",
      "departure",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "de trein",
    "options": [
      "train",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "broken"
    ],
    "answer": "train"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verbinding",
    "options": [
      "connection",
      "to dream",
      "teacher",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "connection"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vertraging",
    "options": [
      "delay",
      "teacher",
      "to travel",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "delay"
  },
  {
    "question": "heen",
    "options": [
      "to(wards)",
      "quiet",
      "to explain",
      "to check in"
    ],
    "answer": "to(wards)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het spoor",
    "options": [
      "platform",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "to walk"
    ],
    "answer": "platform"
  },
  {
    "question": "het station",
    "options": [
      "station",
      "to plan",
      "shopping mall",
      "dry"
    ],
    "answer": "station"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vertrek",
    "options": [
      "departure",
      "to leave",
      "to app",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "departure"
  },
  {
    "question": "overstappen",
    "options": [
      "to change trains",
      "to walk",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to change trains"
  },
  {
    "question": "plannen",
    "options": [
      "to plan",
      "dry",
      "to rain",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "to plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "reizen",
    "options": [
      "to travel",
      "to app",
      "to walk",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to travel"
  },
  {
    "question": "tonen",
    "options": [
      "to show",
      "to dream",
      "teacher",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to show"
  },
  {
    "question": "vinden",
    "options": [
      "to find",
      "to check in",
      "broken",
      "to walk"
    ],
    "answer": "to find"
  },
  {
    "question": "vertrekken",
    "options": [
      "to leave",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to leave"
  },
  {
    "question": "volgende",
    "options": [
      "next",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "next"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bus",
    "options": [
      "bus",
      "to send",
      "quiet",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "bus"
  },
  {
    "question": "aankomen",
    "options": [
      "arrive",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "arrive"
  },
  {
    "question": "de linkerkant",
    "options": [
      "left side",
      "to plan",
      "to dream",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "left side"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rechterkant",
    "options": [
      "right side",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "right side"
  },
  {
    "question": "de route",
    "options": [
      "route",
      "to dream",
      "teacher",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "route"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitleg",
    "options": [
      "explanation",
      "to check in",
      "broken",
      "to walk"
    ],
    "answer": "explanation"
  },
  {
    "question": "duidelijk",
    "options": [
      "clear",
      "to leave",
      "to app",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "clear"
  },
  {
    "question": "eerst",
    "options": [
      "first",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "first"
  },
  {
    "question": "geloven",
    "options": [
      "to believe",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to believe"
  },
  {
    "question": "haar",
    "options": [
      "her",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "her"
  },
  {
    "question": "het werkblad",
    "options": [
      "worksheet",
      "to send",
      "quiet",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "worksheet"
  },
  {
    "question": "het winkelcentrum",
    "options": [
      "shopping mall",
      "to walk",
      "broken",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "shopping mall"
  },
  {
    "question": "links",
    "options": [
      "left",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "left"
  },
  {
    "question": "linksaf",
    "options": [
      "to the left",
      "dry",
      "to rain",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "to the left"
  },
  {
    "question": "lopen",
    "options": [
      "to walk",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "mam",
    "options": [
      "Mum",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "Mum"
  },
  {
    "question": "naartoe",
    "options": [
      "to",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "rechtdoor",
    "options": [
      "straight ahead",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "straight ahead"
  },
  {
    "question": "rechts",
    "options": [
      "right",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "right"
  },
  {
    "question": "rechtsaf",
    "options": [
      "to the right",
      "dry",
      "to rain",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "to the right"
  },
  {
    "question": "slim",
    "options": [
      "smart",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "smart"
  },
  {
    "question": "tegenover",
    "options": [
      "opposite",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "opposite"
  },
  {
    "question": "tekenen",
    "options": [
      "to sign",
      "to draw",
      "to walk",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to sign"
  },
  {
    "question": "tekenen",
    "options": [
      "to draw",
      "to sign",
      "to walk",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to draw"
  },
  {
    "question": "terug",
    "options": [
      "back",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "back"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitleggen",
    "options": [
      "to explain",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to explain"
  },
  {
    "question": "volgens",
    "options": [
      "according to",
      "to walk",
      "broken",
      "to send"
    ],
    "answer": "according to"
  },
  {
    "question": "winkelen",
    "options": [
      "to shop",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to shop"
  },
  {
    "question": "appen",
    "options": [
      "to app",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to app"
  },
  {
    "question": "beste",
    "options": [
      "dear",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "dear"
  },
  {
    "question": "dank",
    "options": [
      "thanks",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "thanks"
  },
  {
    "question": "de docent",
    "options": [
      "teacher",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "de les",
    "options": [
      "lesson",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "lesson"
  },
  {
    "question": "geachte",
    "options": [
      "esteemed",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "esteemed"
  },
  {
    "question": "groet",
    "options": [
      "regards",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "regards"
  },
  {
    "question": "groetjes",
    "options": [
      "greetings",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "greetings"
  },
  {
    "question": "hartelijke",
    "options": [
      "kind",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "kind"
  },
  {
    "question": "helaas",
    "options": [
      "unfortunately",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "unfortunately"
  },
  {
    "question": "het appje",
    "options": [
      "app",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "app"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bericht",
    "options": [
      "message",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "message"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoi",
    "options": [
      "hi",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "hi"
  },
  {
    "question": "kapot",
    "options": [
      "broken",
      "to send",
      "quiet",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "broken"
  },
  {
    "question": "later",
    "options": [
      "later",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "later"
  },
  {
    "question": "lieve",
    "options": [
      "dear",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "dear"
  },
  {
    "question": "moe",
    "options": [
      "tired",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "tired"
  },
  {
    "question": "ongeveer",
    "options": [
      "approximately",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "approximately"
  },
  {
    "question": "sturen",
    "options": [
      "to send",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to send"
  },
  {
    "question": "vriendelijke",
    "options": [
      "warm",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "warm"
  },
  {
    "question": "wat",
    "options": [
      "a bit",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "a bit"
  },
  {
    "question": "achter",
    "options": [
      "behind",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "behind"
  },
  {
    "question": "de auto",
    "options": [
      "car",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "car"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bushalte",
    "options": [
      "bus stop",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "bus stop"
  },
  {
    "question": "de chauffeur",
    "options": [
      "driver",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "driver"
  },
  {
    "question": "de deur",
    "options": [
      "door",
      "to rain",
      "teacher",
      "hurry"
    ],
    "answer": "door"
  },
  {
    "question": "de keer",
    "options": [
      "times",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "times"
  },
  {
    "question": "de mensen",
    "options": [
      "people",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "people"
  },
  {
    "question": "de weg",
    "options": [
      "road",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "road"
  },
  {
    "question": "dromen",
    "options": [
      "to dream",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to dream"
  },
  {
    "question": "droog",
    "options": [
      "dry",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "dry"
  },
  {
    "question": "elke",
    "options": [
      "each",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "each"
  },
  {
    "question": "eruit",
    "options": [
      "(get) out",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "(get) out"
  },
  {
    "question": "het strand",
    "options": [
      "beach",
      "to check in",
      "broken",
      "car"
    ],
    "answer": "beach"
  },
  {
    "question": "het verhaal",
    "options": [
      "story",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "story"
  },
  {
    "question": "iedereen",
    "options": [
      "everybody",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "everybody"
  },
  {
    "question": "inchecken",
    "options": [
      "to check in",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to check in"
  },
  {
    "question": "instappen",
    "options": [
      "to get in",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to get in"
  },
  {
    "question": "nat",
    "options": [
      "wet",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "dry"
    ],
    "answer": "wet"
  },
  {
    "question": "niemand",
    "options": [
      "nobody",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "nobody"
  },
  {
    "question": "opengaan",
    "options": [
      "to open",
      "to send",
      "broken",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to open"
  },
  {
    "question": "regenen",
    "options": [
      "to rain",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "stil",
    "options": [
      "quiet",
      "to walk",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "quiet"
  },
  {
    "question": "stoppen",
    "options": [
      "to stop",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "to stop"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitstappen",
    "options": [
      "to get off",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "to get off"
  },
  {
    "question": "vol",
    "options": [
      "full",
      "to app",
      "to plan",
      "wet"
    ],
    "answer": "full"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanvragen",
    "options": [
      "to request",
      "appointment",
      "assistant",
      "pharmacy"
    ],
    "answer": "to request"
  },
  {
    "question": "de afspraak",
    "options": [
      "appointment",
      "drugstore",
      "assistant",
      "fever"
    ],
    "answer": "appointment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de apotheek",
    "options": [
      "pharmacy",
      "stress",
      "quarrel",
      "specialist"
    ],
    "answer": "pharmacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de assistente",
    "options": [
      "assistant",
      "emergency",
      "general practitioner",
      "practice"
    ],
    "answer": "assistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "de drogist",
    "options": [
      "drugstore",
      "medicine",
      "home visit",
      "consulting hours"
    ],
    "answer": "drugstore"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisarts",
    "options": [
      "general practitioner",
      "earache",
      "sentence",
      "medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "general practitioner"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisartsenpost",
    "options": [
      "GP out-of-hours service",
      "line",
      "to tell",
      "pain"
    ],
    "answer": "GP out-of-hours service"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koorts",
    "options": [
      "fever",
      "to fall",
      "to last",
      "to pay"
    ],
    "answer": "fever"
  },
  {
    "question": "de praktijk",
    "options": [
      "practice",
      "ointment",
      "back",
      "sentence"
    ],
    "answer": "practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ruzie",
    "options": [
      "quarrel",
      "ointment",
      "medicine",
      "cream"
    ],
    "answer": "quarrel"
  },
  {
    "question": "de specialist",
    "options": [
      "specialist",
      "deodorant",
      "ointment",
      "nose drops"
    ],
    "answer": "specialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "de spoed",
    "options": [
      "emergency",
      "consulting hours",
      "general practitioner",
      "to dial"
    ],
    "answer": "emergency"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stress",
    "options": [
      "stress",
      "to reschedule",
      "to request",
      "to compare"
    ],
    "answer": "stress"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vraag",
    "options": [
      "question",
      "to be sorry",
      "medicine",
      "cream"
    ],
    "answer": "question"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zin",
    "options": [
      "sentence",
      "to pay",
      "emergency",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "sentence"
  },
  {
    "question": "duren",
    "options": [
      "to last",
      "to fall",
      "to tell",
      "to dial"
    ],
    "answer": "to last"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huisbezoek",
    "options": [
      "home visit",
      "to request",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "home visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "het medicijn",
    "options": [
      "medicine",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "het spoedgeval",
    "options": [
      "emergency case",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "emergency case"
  },
  {
    "question": "het spreekuur",
    "options": [
      "consulting hours",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "consulting hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "het weekend",
    "options": [
      "weekend",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "weekend"
  },
  {
    "question": "toetsen",
    "options": [
      "to dial",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to dial"
  },
  {
    "question": "tussen",
    "options": [
      "between",
      "front",
      "on",
      "to"
    ],
    "answer": "between"
  },
  {
    "question": "verkouden",
    "options": [
      "a cold",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "a cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "zeggen tegen",
    "options": [
      "to tell",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to tell"
  },
  {
    "question": "blijven",
    "options": [
      "to remain",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to remain"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buikpijn",
    "options": [
      "abdominal pain",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "abdominal pain"
  },
  {
    "question": "de diarree",
    "options": [
      "diarrhoea",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "diarrhoea"
  },
  {
    "question": "de griep",
    "options": [
      "flu",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "flu"
  },
  {
    "question": "de keelpijn",
    "options": [
      "sore throat",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "sore throat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klacht",
    "options": [
      "complaint",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lijn",
    "options": [
      "line",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "line"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oorpijn",
    "options": [
      "earache",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "earache"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pijn",
    "options": [
      "ache",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "ache"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rug",
    "options": [
      "back",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "back"
  },
  {
    "question": "erg",
    "options": [
      "very",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "very"
  },
  {
    "question": "goeiemorgen",
    "options": [
      "good morning",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "good morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoelang",
    "options": [
      "how long",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "how long"
  },
  {
    "question": "maar",
    "options": [
      "but",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "but"
  },
  {
    "question": "me",
    "options": [
      "me",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "me"
  },
  {
    "question": "meer",
    "options": [
      "more",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "more"
  },
  {
    "question": "mogelijk",
    "options": [
      "possible",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "morgen",
    "options": [
      "tomorrow",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "question": "morgenmiddag",
    "options": [
      "tomorrow afternoon",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "tomorrow afternoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "morgenochtend",
    "options": [
      "tomorrow morning",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "tomorrow morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "nou",
    "options": [
      "well",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "well"
  },
  {
    "question": "spijten",
    "options": [
      "to be sorry",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to be sorry"
  },
  {
    "question": "verzetten",
    "options": [
      "to reschedule",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to reschedule"
  },
  {
    "question": "vrij",
    "options": [
      "free",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "free"
  },
  {
    "question": "overgaan",
    "options": [
      "to pass",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to pass"
  },
  {
    "question": "afrekenen",
    "options": [
      "to pay",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to pay"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aanbieding",
    "options": [
      "offer",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de deodorant",
    "options": [
      "deodorant",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "deodorant"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kassa",
    "options": [
      "cash desk",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "cash desk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de luier",
    "options": [
      "diaper",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "diaper"
  },
  {
    "question": "de make-up",
    "options": [
      "make-up",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "make-up"
  },
  {
    "question": "de neusdruppels",
    "options": [
      "nose drops",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "nose drops"
  },
  {
    "question": "de paracetamol",
    "options": [
      "paracetamol",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "paracetamol"
  },
  {
    "question": "de shampoo",
    "options": [
      "shampoo",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "shampoo"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tandenborstel",
    "options": [
      "toothbrush",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "toothbrush"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tandpasta",
    "options": [
      "toothpaste",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "toothpaste"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verkoopster",
    "options": [
      "saleswoman",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "saleswoman"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vitamine",
    "options": [
      "vitamin",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "vitamin"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zeep",
    "options": [
      "soap",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "soap"
  },
  {
    "question": "ergens",
    "options": [
      "somewhere",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "somewhere"
  },
  {
    "question": "het advies",
    "options": [
      "advice",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "advice"
  },
  {
    "question": "het merk",
    "options": [
      "brand",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "brand"
  },
  {
    "question": "het parfum",
    "options": [
      "perfume",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "perfume"
  },
  {
    "question": "meelopen",
    "options": [
      "to walk along",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to walk along"
  },
  {
    "question": "nergens",
    "options": [
      "nowhere",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "nowhere"
  },
  {
    "question": "ons",
    "options": [
      "our",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "our"
  },
  {
    "question": "pinnen",
    "options": [
      "to pay by debit card",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to pay by debit card"
  },
  {
    "question": "toevallig",
    "options": [
      "coincidentally",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "coincidentally"
  },
  {
    "question": "verder",
    "options": [
      "anything else",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "anything else"
  },
  {
    "question": "pas",
    "options": [
      "only",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "only"
  },
  {
    "question": "de crème",
    "options": [
      "cream",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "cream"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gezondheid",
    "options": [
      "health",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "health"
  },
  {
    "question": "de maaltijd",
    "options": [
      "meal",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nacht",
    "options": [
      "night",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "night"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pijnstiller",
    "options": [
      "painkiller",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "painkiller"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pil",
    "options": [
      "pill",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "pill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zalf",
    "options": [
      "ointment",
      "cream",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "ointment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorg",
    "options": [
      "worry",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "worry"
  },
  {
    "question": "genoeg",
    "options": [
      "enough",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "enough"
  },
  {
    "question": "hem",
    "options": [
      "him",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "him"
  },
  {
    "question": "het doosje",
    "options": [
      "(small) box",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "(small) box"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geld",
    "options": [
      "money",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "money"
  },
  {
    "question": "het recept",
    "options": [
      "prescription",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "prescription"
  },
  {
    "question": "innemen",
    "options": [
      "to take",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to take"
  },
  {
    "question": "maal",
    "options": [
      "time",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "time"
  },
  {
    "question": "moeilijk",
    "options": [
      "difficult",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "difficult"
  },
  {
    "question": "overleden",
    "options": [
      "passed away",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "passed away"
  },
  {
    "question": "vallen",
    "options": [
      "to fall",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to fall"
  },
  {
    "question": "vergelijken",
    "options": [
      "to compare",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "to compare"
  },
  {
    "question": "verschrikkelijk",
    "options": [
      "terribly",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "terribly"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tablet",
    "options": [
      "tablet",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "tablet"
  },
  {
    "question": "haar",
    "options": [
      "her",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "her"
  },
  {
    "question": "slecht",
    "options": [
      "poorly",
      "ointment",
      "ointment",
      "ointment"
    ],
    "answer": "poorly"
  },
  {
    "question": "haast",
    "options": [
      "hurry",
      "to leave",
      "dry",
      "teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "hurry"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwart",
    "options": [
      "black",
      "to clean up",
      "to sell",
      "to help"
    ],
    "answer": "black"
  },
  {
    "question": "het eten",
    "options": [
      "to eat",
      "to buy",
      "sweet",
      "meat"
    ],
    "answer": "to eat"
  },
  {
    "question": "fijn",
    "options": [
      "nice",
      "today",
      "to go",
      "thank you"
    ],
    "answer": "nice"
  },
  {
    "question": "het fruit",
    "options": [
      "fruit",
      "tomato",
      "carrot",
      "fish"
    ],
    "answer": "fruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "gaan",
    "options": [
      "to go",
      "to do",
      "to talk",
      "to want"
    ],
    "answer": "to go"
  },
  {
    "question": "de groente",
    "options": [
      "vegetable",
      "orange",
      "chicken",
      "potato"
    ],
    "answer": "vegetable"
  },
  {
    "question": "jij",
    "options": [
      "you",
      "sir",
      "thank you",
      "to say"
    ],
    "answer": "you"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kip",
    "options": [
      "chicken",
      "carrot",
      "tomato",
      "home"
    ],
    "answer": "chicken"
  },
  {
    "question": "kopen",
    "options": [
      "to buy",
      "to do",
      "to want",
      "to talk"
    ],
    "answer": "to buy"
  },
  {
    "question": "lief",
    "options": [
      "sweet",
      "far",
      "welcome",
      "usually"
    ],
    "answer": "sweet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de markt",
    "options": [
      "market",
      "vegetable",
      "orange",
      "bag"
    ],
    "answer": "market"
  },
  {
    "question": "of",
    "options": [
      "or",
      "carrot",
      "today",
      "tomato"
    ],
    "answer": "or"
  },
  {
    "question": "ook",
    "options": [
      "also",
      "sir",
      "potato",
      "vegetable"
    ],
    "answer": "also"
  },
  {
    "question": "over",
    "options": [
      "about",
      "to go",
      "to talk",
      "usually"
    ],
    "answer": "about"
  },
  {
    "question": "praten",
    "options": [
      "to talk",
      "to eat",
      "to want",
      "to know"
    ],
    "answer": "to talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sinaasappel",
    "options": [
      "orange",
      "tomato",
      "potato",
      "chicken"
    ],
    "answer": "orange"
  },
  {
    "question": "de supermarkt",
    "options": [
      "supermarket",
      "carrot",
      "to buy",
      "home"
    ],
    "answer": "supermarket"
  },
  {
    "question": "thuis",
    "options": [
      "home",
      "nice",
      "market",
      "bag"
    ],
    "answer": "home"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tomaat",
    "options": [
      "tomato",
      "potato",
      "fruit",
      "chicken"
    ],
    "answer": "tomato"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ui",
    "options": [
      "onion",
      "carrot",
      "orange",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "onion"
  },
  {
    "question": "vandaag",
    "options": [
      "today",
      "tomato",
      "to talk",
      "to eat"
    ],
    "answer": "today"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vis",
    "options": [
      "fish",
      "potato",
      "meat",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vlees",
    "options": [
      "meat",
      "fruit",
      "vegetable",
      "onion"
    ],
    "answer": "meat"
  },
  {
    "question": "willen",
    "options": [
      "to want",
      "to know",
      "to do",
      "to say"
    ],
    "answer": "to want"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wortel",
    "options": [
      "carrot",
      "potato",
      "tomato",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "carrot"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aardappel",
    "options": [
      "potato",
      "carrot",
      "tomato",
      "onion"
    ],
    "answer": "potato"
  },
  {
    "question": "alstublieft",
    "options": [
      "here you go",
      "please",
      "thank you",
      "welcome"
    ],
    "answer": "here you go"
  },
  {
    "question": "de beurt",
    "options": [
      "turn",
      "hour",
      "day",
      "home"
    ],
    "answer": "turn"
  },
  {
    "question": "bijvoorbeeld",
    "options": [
      "for example",
      "usually",
      "sometimes",
      "today"
    ],
    "answer": "for example"
  },
  {
    "question": "de boodschappenlijst",
    "options": [
      "shopping list",
      "market",
      "fruit",
      "potato"
    ],
    "answer": "shopping list"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dag",
    "options": [
      "day",
      "hour",
      "today",
      "to go"
    ],
    "answer": "day"
  },
  {
    "question": "dank u",
    "options": [
      "thank you",
      "please",
      "here you go",
      "welcome"
    ],
    "answer": "thank you"
  },
  {
    "question": "de euro",
    "options": [
      "euro",
      "weight",
      "gram",
      "kilo"
    ],
    "answer": "euro"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gewicht",
    "options": [
      "weight",
      "gram",
      "kilo",
      "potato"
    ],
    "answer": "weight"
  },
  {
    "question": "graag",
    "options": [
      "please",
      "thank you",
      "welcome",
      "here you go"
    ],
    "answer": "please"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gram",
    "options": [
      "gram",
      "kilo",
      "pound",
      "weight"
    ],
    "answer": "gram"
  },
  {
    "question": "iets",
    "options": [
      "something",
      "anything",
      "nothing",
      "everything"
    ],
    "answer": "something"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kaas",
    "options": [
      "cheese",
      "fish",
      "meat",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "cheese"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kilo",
    "options": [
      "kilo",
      "gram",
      "pound",
      "weight"
    ],
    "answer": "kilo"
  },
  {
    "question": "meneer",
    "options": [
      "sir",
      "madam",
      "neighbor",
      "salesperson"
    ],
    "answer": "sir"
  },
  {
    "question": "mevrouw",
    "options": [
      "madam",
      "sir",
      "neighbor",
      "salesperson"
    ],
    "answer": "madam"
  },
  {
    "question": "nee",
    "options": [
      "no",
      "yes",
      "maybe",
      "please"
    ],
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ons",
    "options": [
      "100 grams",
      "500 grams",
      "1 kilo",
      "200 grams"
    ],
    "answer": "100 grams"
  },
  {
    "question": "op",
    "options": [
      "on",
      "under",
      "beside",
      "in"
    ],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "question": "het pond",
    "options": [
      "500 grams",
      "100 grams",
      "1 kilo",
      "200 grams"
    ],
    "answer": "500 grams"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verkoper",
    "options": [
      "salesperson",
      "sir",
      "madam",
      "neighbor"
    ],
    "answer": "salesperson"
  },
  {
    "question": "u",
    "options": [
      "you",
      "I",
      "he",
      "she"
    ],
    "answer": "you"
  },
  {
    "question": "zeggen",
    "options": [
      "to say",
      "to talk",
      "to do",
      "to want"
    ],
    "answer": "to say"
  },
  {
    "question": "ander",
    "options": [
      "other",
      "same",
      "new",
      "old"
    ],
    "answer": "other"
  },
  {
    "question": "bij",
    "options": [
      "at",
      "on",
      "in",
      "under"
    ],
    "answer": "at"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buurvrouw",
    "options": [
      "female neighbour",
      "male neighbour",
      "friend",
      "stranger"
    ],
    "answer": "female neighbour"
  },
  {
    "question": "dank je",
    "options": [
      "thank you",
      "please",
      "welcome",
      "sorry"
    ],
    "answer": "thank you"
  },
  {
    "question": "de buurt",
    "options": [
      "neighbourhood",
      "city",
      "village",
      "street"
    ],
    "answer": "neighbourhood"
  },
  {
    "question": "duur",
    "options": [
      "expensive",
      "cheap",
      "nice",
      "far"
    ],
    "answer": "expensive"
  },
  {
    "question": "goedkoop",
    "options": [
      "cheap",
      "expensive",
      "new",
      "old"
    ],
    "answer": "cheap"
  },
  {
    "question": "heten",
    "options": [
      "to be called",
      "to eat",
      "to drink",
      "to know"
    ],
    "answer": "to be called"
  },
  {
    "question": "hier",
    "options": [
      "here",
      "there",
      "home",
      "market"
    ],
    "answer": "here"
  },
  {
    "question": "kennen",
    "options": [
      "to know",
      "to want",
      "to see",
      "to hear"
    ],
    "answer": "to know"
  },
  {
    "question": "meestal",
    "options": [
      "usually",
      "sometimes",
      "always",
      "never"
    ],
    "answer": "usually"
  },
  {
    "question": "natuurlijk",
    "options": [
      "of course",
      "never",
      "maybe",
      "sometimes"
    ],
    "answer": "of course"
  },
  {
    "question": "nieuw",
    "options": [
      "new",
      "old",
      "nice",
      "sweet"
    ],
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "question": "soms",
    "options": [
      "sometimes",
      "always",
      "never",
      "usually"
    ],
    "answer": "sometimes"
  },
  {
    "question": "de straat",
    "options": [
      "street",
      "road",
      "avenue",
      "lane"
    ],
    "answer": "street"
  },
  {
    "question": "ver",
    "options": [
      "far",
      "near",
      "close",
      "next"
    ],
    "answer": "far"
  },
  {
    "question": "wel",
    "options": [
      "though",
      "because",
      "and",
      "but"
    ],
    "answer": "though"
  },
  {
    "question": "welkom",
    "options": [
      "welcome",
      "goodbye",
      "hello",
      "please"
    ],
    "answer": "welcome"
  },
  {
    "question": "waar",
    "options": [
      "where",
      "what",
      "when",
      "who"
    ],
    "answer": "where"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bank",
    "options": [
      "couch",
      "chair",
      "table",
      "bed"
    ],
    "answer": "couch"
  },
  {
    "question": "begrijpen",
    "options": [
      "to understand",
      "to know",
      "to think",
      "to say"
    ],
    "answer": "to understand"
  },
  {
    "question": "de chips",
    "options": [
      "potato chips",
      "chips",
      "cookies",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "potato chips"
  },
  {
    "question": "denken",
    "options": [
      "to think",
      "to say",
      "to know",
      "to want"
    ],
    "answer": "to think"
  },
  {
    "question": "dinsdag",
    "options": [
      "Tuesday",
      "Wednesday",
      "Monday",
      "Thursday"
    ],
    "answer": "Tuesday"
  },
  {
    "question": "donderdag",
    "options": [
      "Thursday",
      "Tuesday",
      "Monday",
      "Friday"
    ],
    "answer": "Thursday"
  },
  {
    "question": "het internet",
    "options": [
      "Internet",
      "computer",
      "phone",
      "network"
    ],
    "answer": "Internet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de keuken",
    "options": [
      "kitchen",
      "living room",
      "bedroom",
      "bathroom"
    ],
    "answer": "kitchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "kijken",
    "options": [
      "to look",
      "to see",
      "to watch",
      "to know"
    ],
    "answer": "to look"
  },
  {
    "question": "leeg",
    "options": [
      "empty",
      "full",
      "half",
      "clean"
    ],
    "answer": "empty"
  },
  {
    "question": "liggen",
    "options": [
      "to lie",
      "to stand",
      "to sit",
      "to run"
    ],
    "answer": "to lie"
  },
  {
    "question": "maandag",
    "options": [
      "Monday",
      "Tuesday",
      "Wednesday",
      "Thursday"
    ],
    "answer": "Monday"
  },
  {
    "question": "open",
    "options": [
      "open",
      "closed",
      "locked",
      "shut"
    ],
    "answer": "open"
  },
  {
    "question": "de openingstijden",
    "options": [
      "opening hours",
      "closing hours",
      "break time",
      "lunch hours"
    ],
    "answer": "opening hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "'s avonds",
    "options": [
      "in the evening",
      "in the morning",
      "at night",
      "in the afternoon"
    ],
    "answer": "in the evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "'s middags",
    "options": [
      "in the afternoon",
      "in the evening",
      "in the morning",
      "at night"
    ],
    "answer": "in the afternoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "'s nachts",
    "options": [
      "at night",
      "in the evening",
      "in the morning",
      "in the afternoon"
    ],
    "answer": "at night"
  },
  {
    "question": "snappen",
    "options": [
      "to understand",
      "to say",
      "to talk",
      "to know"
    ],
    "answer": "to understand"
  },
  {
    "question": "'s ochtends",
    "options": [
      "in the morning",
      "in the evening",
      "at night",
      "in the afternoon"
    ],
    "answer": "in the morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "tot",
    "options": [
      "until",
      "after",
      "before",
      "during"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uur",
    "options": [
      "hour",
      "minute",
      "second",
      "day"
    ],
    "answer": "hour"
  },
  {
    "question": "vrijdag",
    "options": [
      "Friday",
      "Monday",
      "Tuesday",
      "Wednesday"
    ],
    "answer": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "question": "weten",
    "options": [
      "to know",
      "to think",
      "to say",
      "to want"
    ],
    "answer": "to know"
  },
  {
    "question": "woensdag",
    "options": [
      "Wednesday",
      "Monday",
      "Tuesday",
      "Thursday"
    ],
    "answer": "Wednesday"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zak",
    "options": [
      "bag",
      "box",
      "bottle",
      "cup"
    ],
    "answer": "bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "zaterdag",
    "options": [
      "Saturday",
      "Sunday",
      "Friday",
      "Monday"
    ],
    "answer": "Saturday"
  },
  {
    "question": "zin",
    "options": [
      "desire",
      "need",
      "want",
      "wish"
    ],
    "answer": "desire"
  },
  {
    "question": "zondag",
    "options": [
      "Sunday",
      "Saturday",
      "Friday",
      "Monday"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunday"
  },
  {
    "question": "het dorp",
    "options": [
      "to spell",
      "last name",
      "village",
      "boy"
    ],
    "answer": "village"
  },
  {
    "question": "een",
    "options": [
      "nationality",
      "to work",
      "a",
      "one"
    ],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "geboren",
    "options": [
      "form",
      "to tell about",
      "born",
      "alphabet"
    ],
    "answer": "born"
  },
  {
    "question": "hallo",
    "options": [
      "municipality",
      "hello",
      "gender",
      "house number"
    ],
    "answer": "hello"
  },
  {
    "question": "ik",
    "options": [
      "I",
      "to read",
      "yes",
      "to be allowed to"
    ],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "question": "in",
    "options": [
      "in",
      "the Netherlands",
      "gender",
      "a short while"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "je",
    "options": [
      "to learn",
      "your",
      "to tell about",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "your"
  },
  {
    "question": "komen",
    "options": [
      "telephone",
      "number",
      "okay",
      "to come"
    ],
    "answer": "to come"
  },
  {
    "question": "het land",
    "options": [
      "country",
      "okay",
      "go ahead",
      "city"
    ],
    "answer": "country"
  },
  {
    "question": "lezen",
    "options": [
      "to be correct",
      "I",
      "first name",
      "to read"
    ],
    "answer": "to read"
  },
  {
    "question": "luisteren",
    "options": [
      "country",
      "three",
      "to listen",
      "seven"
    ],
    "answer": "to listen"
  },
  {
    "question": "nu",
    "options": [
      "now",
      "to fill in",
      "form",
      "then"
    ],
    "answer": "now"
  },
  {
    "question": "schrijven",
    "options": [
      "hello",
      "to write",
      "school",
      "own"
    ],
    "answer": "to write"
  },
  {
    "question": "spreken",
    "options": [
      "to write down",
      "with",
      "to speak",
      "to live"
    ],
    "answer": "to speak"
  },
  {
    "question": "de stad",
    "options": [
      "name",
      "city",
      "five",
      "my"
    ],
    "answer": "city"
  },
  {
    "question": "uit",
    "options": [
      "from",
      "two",
      "in",
      "last name"
    ],
    "answer": "from"
  },
  {
    "question": "wie",
    "options": [
      "to wait",
      "who",
      "yes",
      "no"
    ],
    "answer": "who"
  },
  {
    "question": "wonen",
    "options": [
      "classroom",
      "to live",
      "telephone",
      "married"
    ],
    "answer": "to live"
  },
  {
    "question": "zijn",
    "options": [
      "three",
      "who",
      "to go",
      "to be"
    ],
    "answer": "to be"
  },
  {
    "question": "acht",
    "options": [
      "eight",
      "my",
      "how",
      "to go"
    ],
    "answer": "eight"
  },
  {
    "question": "het cijfer",
    "options": [
      "number",
      "girl",
      "to speak",
      "then"
    ],
    "answer": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dochter",
    "options": [
      "then",
      "go ahead",
      "to tell about",
      "daughter"
    ],
    "answer": "daughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "drie",
    "options": [
      "to read",
      "child",
      "three",
      "municipality"
    ],
    "answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "question": "één",
    "options": [
      "six",
      "one",
      "two",
      "village"
    ],
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "question": "gaan",
    "options": [
      "telephone",
      "now",
      "to go",
      "to call"
    ],
    "answer": "to go"
  },
  {
    "question": "geen",
    "options": [
      "to be correct",
      "six",
      "no",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "getrouwd",
    "options": [
      "and",
      "with",
      "married",
      "to go"
    ],
    "answer": "married"
  },
  {
    "question": "hebben",
    "options": [
      "with",
      "to live",
      "to have",
      "to tell about"
    ],
    "answer": "to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "de jongen",
    "options": [
      "boy",
      "to tell about",
      "my",
      "next to"
    ],
    "answer": "boy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kind",
    "options": [
      "first name",
      "girl",
      "to wait",
      "child"
    ],
    "answer": "child"
  },
  {
    "question": "leren",
    "options": [
      "woman",
      "to learn",
      "to tell about",
      "country"
    ],
    "answer": "to learn"
  },
  {
    "question": "de maand",
    "options": [
      "postal code",
      "month",
      "to listen",
      "nationality"
    ],
    "answer": "month"
  },
  {
    "question": "het meisje",
    "options": [
      "man",
      "girl",
      "to work",
      "letter"
    ],
    "answer": "girl"
  },
  {
    "question": "naar",
    "options": [
      "next to",
      "to",
      "to be",
      "to fill in"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nederland",
    "options": [
      "seven",
      "yes",
      "the Netherlands",
      "six"
    ],
    "answer": "the Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nederlands",
    "options": [
      "and",
      "girl",
      "number",
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "answer": "Dutch"
  },
  {
    "question": "negen",
    "options": [
      "who",
      "municipality",
      "village",
      "nine"
    ],
    "answer": "nine"
  },
  {
    "question": "niet",
    "options": [
      "city",
      "to",
      "to ask",
      "not"
    ],
    "answer": "not"
  },
  {
    "question": "de school",
    "options": [
      "a",
      "school",
      "son",
      "five"
    ],
    "answer": "school"
  },
  {
    "question": "tien",
    "options": [
      "ten",
      "maybe",
      "to call",
      "hello"
    ],
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "question": "twee",
    "options": [
      "nine",
      "fast",
      "to tell about",
      "two"
    ],
    "answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "question": "vertellen over",
    "options": [
      "to be correct",
      "ten",
      "to tell about",
      "email"
    ],
    "answer": "to tell about"
  },
  {
    "question": "vier",
    "options": [
      "now",
      "four",
      "municipality",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "question": "vijf",
    "options": [
      "next to",
      "five",
      "letter",
      "own"
    ],
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "question": "werken",
    "options": [
      "to work",
      "to put",
      "to learn",
      "married"
    ],
    "answer": "to work"
  },
  {
    "question": "de winkel",
    "options": [
      "form",
      "yes",
      "store",
      "now"
    ],
    "answer": "store"
  },
  {
    "question": "zes",
    "options": [
      "no",
      "your",
      "to come",
      "six"
    ],
    "answer": "six"
  },
  {
    "question": "zeven",
    "options": [
      "yes",
      "postal code",
      "my",
      "seven"
    ],
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zoon",
    "options": [
      "to come",
      "to put",
      "son",
      "classroom"
    ],
    "answer": "son"
  },
  {
    "question": "het alfabet",
    "options": [
      "alphabet",
      "nationality",
      "I",
      "a short while"
    ],
    "answer": "alphabet"
  },
  {
    "question": "en",
    "options": [
      "to write down",
      "and",
      "alphabet",
      "to live"
    ],
    "answer": "and"
  },
  {
    "question": "even",
    "options": [
      "then",
      "yes",
      "a short while",
      "street"
    ],
    "answer": "a short while"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoe",
    "options": [
      "a",
      "one",
      "how",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "how"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoor",
    "options": [
      "email",
      "you know, really , indeed",
      "go ahead",
      "a short while"
    ],
    "answer": "you know, really , indeed"
  },
  {
    "question": "ja",
    "options": [
      "yes",
      "to fill in",
      "street",
      "okay"
    ],
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "je",
    "options": [
      "woman",
      "your",
      "to ask",
      "city of residence"
    ],
    "answer": "your"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klas",
    "options": [
      "email",
      "month",
      "telephone",
      "classroom"
    ],
    "answer": "classroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "kloppen",
    "options": [
      "to be correct",
      "no",
      "daughter",
      "yes"
    ],
    "answer": "to be correct"
  },
  {
    "question": "de letter",
    "options": [
      "classroom",
      "five",
      "letter",
      "a short while"
    ],
    "answer": "letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "mijn",
    "options": [
      "to be",
      "man",
      "my",
      "municipality"
    ],
    "answer": "my"
  },
  {
    "question": "misschien",
    "options": [
      "maybe",
      "nine",
      "to write",
      "street"
    ],
    "answer": "maybe"
  },
  {
    "question": "mogen",
    "options": [
      "a short while",
      "letter",
      "to be allowed to",
      "to read"
    ],
    "answer": "to be allowed to"
  },
  {
    "question": "de naam",
    "options": [
      "three",
      "name",
      "to be correct",
      "telephone number"
    ],
    "answer": "name"
  },
  {
    "question": "naast",
    "options": [
      "now",
      "to ask",
      "country",
      "next to"
    ],
    "answer": "next to"
  },
  {
    "question": "oké",
    "options": [
      "okay",
      "form",
      "to speak",
      "to ask"
    ],
    "answer": "okay"
  },
  {
    "question": "opschrijven",
    "options": [
      "house number",
      "to write down",
      "classroom",
      "city of residence"
    ],
    "answer": "to write down"
  },
  {
    "question": "schrijven",
    "options": [
      "one",
      "two",
      "to call",
      "to write"
    ],
    "answer": "to write"
  },
  {
    "question": "spellen",
    "options": [
      "to call",
      "one",
      "hello",
      "to spell"
    ],
    "answer": "to spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "de telefoon",
    "options": [
      "place of birth",
      "my",
      "to put",
      "telephone"
    ],
    "answer": "telephone"
  },
  {
    "question": "het telefoonnummer",
    "options": [
      "form",
      "nationality",
      "I",
      "telephone number"
    ],
    "answer": "telephone number"
  },
  {
    "question": "wachten",
    "options": [
      "yes",
      "place of birth",
      "to go",
      "to wait"
    ],
    "answer": "to wait"
  },
  {
    "question": "zetten",
    "options": [
      "to read",
      "married",
      "to write",
      "to put"
    ],
    "answer": "to put"
  },
  {
    "question": "zitten",
    "options": [
      "not",
      "to sit",
      "seven",
      "and"
    ],
    "answer": "to sit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de achternaam",
    "options": [
      "last name",
      "fast",
      "the Netherlands",
      "how"
    ],
    "answer": "last name"
  },
  {
    "question": "het adres",
    "options": [
      "address",
      "to come",
      "girl",
      "city"
    ],
    "answer": "address"
  },
  {
    "question": "bellen",
    "options": [
      "ten",
      "four",
      "seven",
      "to call"
    ],
    "answer": "to call"
  },
  {
    "question": "dan",
    "options": [
      "month",
      "then",
      "not",
      "classroom"
    ],
    "answer": "then"
  },
  {
    "question": "eigen",
    "options": [
      "to speak",
      "to fill in",
      "own",
      "to spell"
    ],
    "answer": "own"
  },
  {
    "question": "de e-mail",
    "options": [
      "to learn",
      "email",
      "in",
      "to ask"
    ],
    "answer": "email"
  },
  {
    "question": "het formulier",
    "options": [
      "child",
      "in",
      "gender",
      "form"
    ],
    "answer": "form"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geboortedatum",
    "options": [
      "nine",
      "date of birth",
      "fast",
      "your"
    ],
    "answer": "date of birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geboorteplaats",
    "options": [
      "place of birth",
      "maybe",
      "form",
      "two"
    ],
    "answer": "place of birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gemeente",
    "options": [
      "to sit",
      "last name",
      "gender",
      "municipality"
    ],
    "answer": "municipality"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geslacht",
    "options": [
      "then",
      "one",
      "gender",
      "and"
    ],
    "answer": "gender"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huisnummer",
    "options": [
      "address",
      "to come",
      "to live",
      "house number"
    ],
    "answer": "house number"
  },
  {
    "question": "invullen",
    "options": [
      "to fill in",
      "three",
      "hello",
      "to write down"
    ],
    "answer": "to fill in"
  },
  {
    "question": "de man",
    "options": [
      "store",
      "school",
      "man",
      "to be"
    ],
    "answer": "man"
  },
  {
    "question": "met",
    "options": [
      "ten",
      "a short while",
      "with",
      "nine"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nationaliteit",
    "options": [
      "form",
      "place of birth",
      "nationality",
      "maybe"
    ],
    "answer": "nationality"
  },
  {
    "question": "de postcode",
    "options": [
      "from",
      "postal code",
      "to spell",
      "last name"
    ],
    "answer": "postal code"
  },
  {
    "question": "snel",
    "options": [
      "who",
      "email",
      "fast",
      "to sit"
    ],
    "answer": "fast"
  },
  {
    "question": "de straat",
    "options": [
      "name",
      "street",
      "alphabet",
      "to have"
    ],
    "answer": "street"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voornaam",
    "options": [
      "seven",
      "to ask",
      "then",
      "first name"
    ],
    "answer": "first name"
  },
  {
    "question": "vragen",
    "options": [
      "ten",
      "five",
      "to ask",
      "my"
    ],
    "answer": "to ask"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vrouw",
    "options": [
      "municipality",
      "so",
      "woman",
      "to sit"
    ],
    "answer": "woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "wat",
    "options": [
      "to learn",
      "how",
      "to put",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "what"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woonplaats",
    "options": [
      "the Netherlands",
      "city of residence",
      "so",
      "to speak"
    ],
    "answer": "city of residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "zo",
    "options": [
      "so",
      "what",
      "form",
      "street"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "zijn",
    "options": [
      "his",
      "municipality",
      "to ask",
      "to speak"
    ],
    "answer": "his"
  }
]